1	GDP	O	S-TERM	0	0
2	for	O	O	0	0
3	Panalpina	S-GPE	S-TERM	1	5
4	's	O	O	0	0
5	Frankfurt	S-GPE	B-TERM	0	0
6	logistics	O	I-TERM	0	0
7	centre	O	E-TERM	0	0

1	Panalpina	S-GPE	S-TERM	1	5
2	's	O	O	0	0
3	healthcare	O	B-TERM	0	0
4	logistics	O	I-TERM	0	0
5	centre	O	E-TERM	1	8
6	near	O	O	0	0
7	Frankfurt	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
8	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	0	0
9	has	O	O	0	0
10	obtained	O	O	0	0
11	Good	O	B-TERM	0	0
12	Distribution	O	I-TERM	0	0
13	Practice	O	E-TERM	0	0
14	(	O	O	0	0
15	GDP	O	S-TERM	0	0
16	)	O	O	0	0
17	certification	O	O	0	0
18	,	O	O	0	0
19	bringing	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	certified	O	O	0	0
22	network	O	O	0	0
23	to	O	O	0	0
24	38	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
25	locations	O	O	0	0
26	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	Weiterstadt	S-GPE	B-TERM	0	0
3	facility	O	E-TERM	0	0
4	is	O	O	0	0
5	located	O	O	0	0
6	near	O	O	0	0
7	the	O	O	0	0
8	airport	O	O	0	0
9	as	O	O	0	0
10	well	O	O	0	0
11	as	O	O	0	0
12	close	O	O	0	0
13	to	O	O	0	0
14	major	O	O	0	0
15	highways	O	O	0	0
16	and	O	O	0	0
17	Germany	S-GPE	O	0	0
18	's	O	O	0	0
19	federal	O	O	0	0
20	road	O	O	0	0
21	infrastructure	O	O	0	0
22	,	O	O	0	0
23	allowing	O	O	0	0
24	customers	O	O	0	0
25	to	O	O	0	0
26	shorten	O	O	0	0
27	lead	O	O	0	0
28	times	O	O	0	0
29	for	O	O	0	0
30	intra-European	S-NORP	O	0	0
31	and	O	O	0	0
32	global	O	O	0	0
33	shipments	O	O	0	0
34	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	facility	O	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	Panalpina	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	6
5	's	O	O	0	0
6	third	S-ORDINAL	O	1	9
7	in	O	O	0	0
8	the	O	O	0	0
9	Rhein-Main	S-LOC	O	1	12
10	region	O	O	0	0
11	alongside	O	O	0	0
12	Moerfelden	S-GPE	O	0	14
13	and	O	O	0	0
14	Neu-Isenburg	S-GPE	O	1	20
15	,	O	O	0	0
16	passed	O	O	0	0
17	an	O	O	0	0
18	audit	O	O	0	0
19	by	O	O	0	0
20	SGS	S-ORG	O	0	0
21	.	O	O	0	0

1	It	O	O	0	0
2	is	O	O	0	0
3	equipped	O	O	0	0
4	for	O	O	0	0
5	hub	O	O	0	0
6	services	O	O	0	0
7	for	O	O	0	0
8	multimodal	O	O	0	0
9	transport	O	O	0	0
10	including	O	O	0	0
11	last-mile	O	O	0	0
12	delivery	O	O	0	0
13	and	O	O	0	0
14	linked	O	O	0	0
15	to	O	O	0	0
16	Panalpina	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
17	's	O	O	0	0
18	global	O	O	0	0
19	network	O	O	0	0
20	offering	O	O	0	0
21	temperature-controlled	O	O	0	0
22	air	O	O	0	0
23	and	O	O	0	0
24	ocean	O	O	0	0
25	freight	O	O	0	0
26	services	O	O	0	0
27	.	O	O	0	0

1	Of	O	O	0	0
2	the	O	O	0	0
3	healthcare	O	O	0	0
4	part	O	O	0	0
5	,	O	O	0	0
6	3,500	B-QUANTITY	O	0	0
7	sq	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
8	m	E-QUANTITY	O	1	12
9	covers	O	O	0	0
10	temperature	O	O	0	0
11	from	O	O	0	0
12	15-25C	S-CARDINAL	O	1	14
13	with	O	O	0	0
14	three	S-CARDINAL	O	1	17
15	dedicated	O	O	0	0
16	truck	O	B-TERM	0	0
17	docks	O	E-TERM	1	22
18	,	O	O	0	0
19	and	O	O	0	0
20	1,000	B-QUANTITY	O	0	0
21	sq	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
22	m	E-QUANTITY	O	1	26
23	covers	O	O	0	0
24	temperature	O	O	0	0
25	from	O	O	0	0
26	2-8C	S-CARDINAL	O	1	28
27	with	O	O	0	0
28	two	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
29	dedicated	O	O	0	0
30	truck	O	B-TERM	0	0
31	docks	O	E-TERM	0	0
32	.	O	O	0	0

1	Volker	B-PERSON	O	0	0
2	Werner	E-PERSON	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	Panalpina	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	10
5	's	O	O	0	0
6	district	O	O	0	0
7	manager	O	O	0	0
8	for	O	O	0	0
9	Central	B-GPE	B-TERM	0	0
10	Germany	E-GPE	E-TERM	0	0
11	says	O	O	0	0
12	:	O	O	0	0
13	"	O	O	0	0
14	The	O	O	0	0
15	facility	O	O	0	0
16	is	O	O	0	0
17	not	O	O	0	0
18	only	O	O	0	0
19	set	O	O	0	0
20	up	O	O	0	0
21	for	O	O	0	0
22	multimodal	O	O	0	0
23	transport	O	O	0	0
24	;	O	O	0	0
25	we	O	O	0	0
26	have	O	O	0	0
27	fully	O	O	0	0
28	equipped	O	O	0	0
29	it	O	O	0	0
30	to	O	O	0	0
31	meet	O	O	0	0
32	all	O	O	0	0
33	possible	O	O	0	0
34	requirements	O	O	0	0
35	of	O	O	0	0
36	our	O	O	0	0
37	pharma	O	O	0	0
38	customers	O	O	0	0
39	.	O	O	0	0

1	Stephen	B-PERSON	O	0	0
2	Kay	E-PERSON	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	regional	O	O	0	0
5	manager	O	O	0	0
6	of	O	O	0	0
7	Panalpina	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	21
8	's	O	O	0	0
9	healthcare	O	O	0	0
10	industry	O	O	0	0
11	vertical	O	O	0	0
12	says	O	O	0	0
13	:	O	O	0	0
14	"	O	O	0	0
15	In	O	O	0	0
16	combination	O	O	0	0
17	with	O	O	0	0
18	Panalpina	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
19	's	O	O	0	0
20	other	O	O	0	0
21	European	S-NORP	O	0	0
22	centres	O	O	0	0
23	of	O	O	0	0
24	excellence	O	O	0	0
25	,	O	O	0	0
26	we	O	O	0	0
27	have	O	O	0	0
28	a	O	O	0	0
29	highly	O	O	0	0
30	flexible	O	O	0	0
31	set-up	O	O	0	0
32	,	O	O	0	0
33	where	O	O	0	0
34	we	O	O	0	0
35	can	O	O	0	0
36	move	O	O	0	0
37	products	O	O	0	0
38	to	O	O	0	0
39	every	O	O	0	0
40	continent	O	O	0	0
41	by	O	O	0	0
42	air	O	O	0	0
43	or	O	O	0	0
44	ocean	O	O	0	0
45	freight	O	O	0	0
46	and	O	O	0	0
47	using	O	O	0	0
48	either	O	O	0	0
49	active	O	O	0	0
50	or	O	O	0	0
51	passive	O	O	0	0
52	cooling	O	O	0	0
53	.	O	O	0	0

1	Based	O	O	0	0
2	on	O	O	0	0
3	the	O	O	0	0
4	customers	O	O	0	0
5	'	O	O	0	0
6	requirements	O	O	0	0
7	,	O	O	0	0
8	we	O	O	0	0
9	can	O	O	0	0
10	also	O	O	0	0
11	choose	O	O	0	0
12	between	O	O	0	0
13	commercial	O	O	0	0
14	carriers	O	O	0	0
15	or	O	O	0	0
16	the	B-ORG	O	0	0
17	Panalpina	I-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
18	Charter	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
19	Network	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	26
20	with	O	O	0	0
21	its	O	O	0	0
22	main	O	O	0	0
23	hub	O	O	0	0
24	in	O	O	0	0
25	nearby	O	O	0	0
26	Luxembourg	S-GPE	O	0	0
27	.	O	O	0	0
28	"	O	O	0	0

1	Qatar	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Airways	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	8
3	signs	O	O	0	0
4	deal	O	O	0	0
5	to	O	O	0	0
6	use	O	O	0	0
7	DoKaSch	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
8	Opticooler	E-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
9	containers	O	E-TERM	0	0

1	Qatar	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Airways	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
3	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
4	has	O	O	0	0
5	enhanced	O	O	0	0
6	its	O	O	0	0
7	pharma	O	O	0	0
8	services	O	O	0	0
9	by	O	O	0	0
10	signing	O	O	0	0
11	an	O	O	0	0
12	agreement	O	O	0	0
13	with	O	O	0	0
14	DoKaSch	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
15	Temperature	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
16	Solutions	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	20
17	to	O	O	0	0
18	use	O	O	0	0
19	its	O	O	0	0
20	Opticooler	S-PRODUCT	B-TERM	1	23
21	range	O	E-TERM	0	0
22	of	O	O	0	0
23	containers	O	S-TERM	0	0
24	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	solution	O	O	0	0
3	safeguards	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	efficacy	O	O	0	0
6	of	O	O	0	0
7	vita	O	O	0	0
8	pharmaceuticals	O	O	0	0
9	throughout	O	O	0	0
10	the	O	O	0	0
11	transportation	O	O	0	0
12	chain	O	O	0	0
13	,	O	O	0	0
14	and	O	O	0	0
15	the	O	O	0	0
16	containers	O	S-TERM	1	29
17	keep	O	O	0	0
18	the	O	O	0	0
19	cargo	O	O	0	0
20	within	O	O	0	0
21	a	O	O	0	0
22	temperature	O	O	0	0
23	range	O	O	0	0
24	of	O	O	0	0
25	2	B-QUANTITY	O	0	0
26	and	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
27	8	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
28	degrees	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
29	Celsius	E-QUANTITY	O	1	31
30	or	O	O	0	0
31	15	S-CARDINAL	O	1	34
32	to	O	O	0	0
33	25	B-QUANTITY	O	0	0
34	degrees	E-QUANTITY	O	0	0
35	.	O	O	0	0

1	DoKaSch	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Temperature	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
3	Solutions	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
4	managing	O	O	0	0
5	director	O	O	0	0
6	,	O	O	0	0
7	Andreas	B-PERSON	O	0	0
8	Seitz	E-PERSON	O	0	0
9	says	O	O	0	0
10	:	O	O	0	0
11	"	O	O	0	0
12	We	O	O	0	0
13	are	O	O	0	0
14	very	O	O	0	0
15	pleased	O	O	0	0
16	to	O	O	0	0
17	make	O	O	0	0
18	our	O	O	0	0
19	Opticooler	B-ORG	O	0	0
20	®	E-ORG	O	1	21
21	containers	O	S-TERM	0	0
22	available	O	O	0	0
23	through	O	O	0	0
24	one	O	O	0	0
25	of	O	O	0	0
26	the	O	O	0	0
27	world	O	O	0	0
28	's	O	O	0	0
29	largest	O	O	0	0
30	international	O	O	0	0
31	cargo	O	O	0	0
32	carriers	O	O	0	0
33	.	O	O	0	0

1	We	O	O	0	0
2	are	O	O	0	0
3	convinced	O	O	0	0
4	that	O	O	0	0
5	with	O	O	0	0
6	Qatar	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
7	Airways	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
8	Cargo	I-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
9	's	E-ORG	O	0	0
10	extensive	O	O	0	0
11	and	O	O	0	0
12	rapidly-growing	O	O	0	0
13	network	O	O	0	0
14	,	O	O	0	0
15	and	O	O	0	0
16	our	O	O	0	0
17	joint	O	O	0	0
18	commitment	O	O	0	0
19	to	O	O	0	0
20	quality	O	O	0	0
21	and	O	O	0	0
22	customer	O	O	0	0
23	satisfaction	O	O	0	0
24	,	O	O	0	0
25	this	O	O	0	0
26	partnership	O	O	0	0
27	will	O	O	0	0
28	provide	O	O	0	0
29	a	O	O	0	0
30	great	O	O	0	0
31	solution	O	O	0	0
32	for	O	O	0	0
33	the	O	O	0	0
34	global	O	O	0	0
35	Pharma	S-ORG	O	0	0
36	cool	O	O	0	0
37	chain	O	O	0	0
38	.	O	O	0	0
39	"	O	O	0	0

1	Pharmaceutical	O	O	0	0
2	volumes	O	O	0	0
3	across	O	O	0	0
4	Qatar	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
5	Airways	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
6	Cargo	I-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
7	's	E-ORG	O	1	12
8	network	O	O	0	0
9	grew	O	O	0	0
10	42	B-PERCENT	O	0	0
11	per	I-PERCENT	O	0	0
12	cent	E-PERCENT	O	0	0
13	in	O	O	0	0
14	2016-17	S-DATE	O	0	0
15	compared	O	O	0	0
16	to	O	O	0	0
17	2015-16	S-DATE	O	0	0
18	.	O	O	0	0

1	Schiphol	O	B-TERM	0	0
2	data	O	E-TERM	0	0
3	sharing	O	O	0	0
4	platform	O	O	0	0
5	blooms	O	O	0	0

1	As	O	O	0	0
2	part	O	O	0	0
3	of	O	O	0	0
4	its	O	O	0	0
5	Smart	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
6	Cargo	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
7	Mainport	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
8	Program	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	10
9	(	O	O	0	0
10	SCMP	S-ORG	O	1	15
11	)	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	Amsterdam	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
14	Airport	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
15	Schiphol	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	22
16	is	O	O	0	0
17	now	O	O	0	0
18	linking	O	O	0	0
19	critical	O	B-TERM	0	0
20	flower	O	I-TERM	0	0
21	shipment	O	I-TERM	0	0
22	data	O	E-TERM	1	30
23	to	O	O	0	0
24	air	O	O	0	0
25	waybills	O	O	0	0
26	at	O	O	0	0
27	source	O	O	0	0
28	,	O	O	0	0
29	the	O	O	0	0
30	Dutch	S-NORP	O	1	38
31	gateway	O	O	0	0
32	announced	O	O	0	0
33	at	O	O	0	0
34	the	B-EVENT	O	0	0
35	IATA	I-EVENT	B-TERM	0	0
36	World	I-EVENT	I-TERM	0	0
37	Cargo	I-EVENT	I-TERM	0	0
38	Symposium	E-EVENT	E-TERM	1	43
39	currently	O	O	0	0
40	under	O	O	0	0
41	way	O	O	0	0
42	in	O	O	0	0
43	Dallas	S-GPE	O	0	45
44	,	O	O	0	0
45	Texas	S-GPE	O	0	0
46	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	next	O	O	0	0
3	step	O	O	0	0
4	is	O	O	0	0
5	to	O	O	0	0
6	present	O	O	0	0
7	the	O	O	0	0
8	data	O	S-TERM	1	20
9	to	O	O	0	0
10	the	O	O	0	0
11	end	O	O	0	0
12	customer	O	O	0	0
13	in	O	O	0	0
14	a	O	O	0	0
15	user-friendly	O	O	0	0
16	way	O	O	0	0
17	;	O	O	0	0
18	Holland	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
19	Flower	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
20	Alliance	E-ORG	I-TERM	1	31
21	partners	O	E-TERM	0	0
22	are	O	O	0	0
23	working	O	O	0	0
24	on	O	O	0	0
25	this	O	O	0	0
26	,	O	O	0	0
27	alongside	O	O	0	0
28	forwarders	O	O	0	0
29	Kuehne	B-ORG	O	0	0
30	+	I-ORG	O	0	0
31	Nagel	E-ORG	O	0	33
32	and	O	O	0	0
33	Panalpina	S-ORG	O	0	0
34	.	O	O	0	0

1	Turkish	S-NORP	O	1	4
2	hub	O	O	0	0
3	at	O	O	0	0
4	Istanbul	S-GPE	O	0	0
5	awarded	O	O	0	0
6	CEIV	O	B-TERM	0	0
7	pharma	O	I-TERM	0	0
8	certificate	O	E-TERM	0	0

1	Turkish	B-ORG	B-TERM	1	21
2	Airlines	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	4
3	says	O	O	0	0
4	CEIV	S-ORG	O	0	0
5	crowns	O	O	0	0
6	its	O	O	0	0
7	"	O	O	0	0
8	success	O	O	0	0
9	in	O	O	0	0
10	all	O	O	0	0
11	processes	O	O	0	0
12	of	O	O	0	0
13	the	O	O	0	0
14	air	O	O	0	0
15	transportation	O	O	0	0
16	of	O	O	0	0
17	healthcare	O	O	0	0
18	products	O	O	0	0
19	during	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	cargo	O	B-TERM	0	0
22	operations	O	E-TERM	1	1
23	it	O	O	0	0
24	carries	O	O	0	0
25	out	O	O	0	0
26	under	O	O	0	0
27	the	O	O	0	0
28	Turkish	S-NORP	B-TERM	0	0
29	Cargo	S-PRODUCT	I-TERM	0	0
30	brand	O	E-TERM	0	0
31	"	O	O	0	0
32	.	O	O	0	0

1	At	O	O	0	0
2	Istanbul	B-FAC	O	0	0
3	Ataturk	E-FAC	O	0	6
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	Turkish	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
6	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	11
7	has	O	O	0	0
8	a	O	O	0	0
9	3,000	B-QUANTITY	O	0	0
10	square	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
11	metre	E-QUANTITY	O	1	16
12	special	O	O	0	0
13	storage	O	O	0	0
14	areas	O	O	0	0
15	covering	O	O	0	0
16	four	S-CARDINAL	O	1	23
17	different	O	O	0	0
18	temperature	O	O	0	0
19	ranges	O	O	0	0
20	(	O	O	0	0
21	from	O	O	0	0
22	-20	B-QUANTITY	O	0	0
23	°C	E-QUANTITY	O	1	28
24	to	O	O	0	0
25	+	O	O	0	0
26	25	B-QUANTITY	O	0	0
27	°C	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
28	)	E-QUANTITY	O	1	36
29	in	O	O	0	0
30	an	O	O	0	0
31	indoor	O	O	0	0
32	area	O	O	0	0
33	of	O	O	0	0
34	43,000	B-QUANTITY	O	0	0
35	square	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
36	metre	E-QUANTITY	O	1	46
37	area	O	O	0	0
38	,	O	O	0	0
39	across	O	O	0	0
40	a	O	O	0	0
41	total	O	O	0	0
42	area	O	O	0	0
43	of	O	O	0	0
44	71,000	B-QUANTITY	O	0	0
45	square	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
46	metres	E-QUANTITY	O	0	0
47	.	O	O	0	0

1	With	O	O	0	0
2	its	O	O	0	0
3	thermal	O	O	0	0
4	blanket	O	O	0	0
5	and	O	O	0	0
6	active	O	O	0	0
7	container	O	O	0	0
8	services	O	O	0	0
9	,	O	O	0	0
10	Turkish	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
11	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
12	says	O	O	0	0
13	it	O	O	0	0
14	aims	O	O	0	0
15	to	O	O	0	0
16	minimise	O	O	0	0
17	the	O	O	0	0
18	risk	O	O	0	0
19	to	O	O	0	0
20	highly	O	O	0	0
21	sensitive	O	O	0	0
22	healthcare	O	O	0	0
23	products	O	O	0	0
24	.	O	O	0	0

1	Turkish	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	14
3	explains	O	O	0	0
4	it	O	O	0	0
5	is	O	O	0	0
6	also	O	O	0	0
7	planning	O	O	0	0
8	to	O	O	0	0
9	commission	O	O	0	0
10	the	B-ORG	O	0	0
11	'	I-ORG	O	0	0
12	Thermal	I-ORG	O	0	0
13	Dolly	I-ORG	O	0	0
14	'	E-ORG	O	0	0
15	service	O	O	0	0
16	and	O	O	0	0
17	using	O	O	0	0
18	it	O	O	0	0
19	for	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	temperature	O	O	0	0
22	and	O	O	0	0
23	time-critical	O	O	0	0
24	consignments	O	O	0	0
25	soon	O	O	0	0
26	.	O	O	0	0

1	K+N	S-ORG	O	1	6
2	expands	O	O	0	0
3	perishables	O	O	0	0
4	network	O	O	0	0
5	with	O	O	0	0
6	US	S-GPE	O	0	8
7	and	O	O	0	0
8	Kenyan	S-NORP	S-TERM	0	0
9	acquisitions	O	S-TERM	0	0

1	Kuehne	B-ORG	O	0	0
2	+	I-ORG	O	0	0
3	Nagel	I-ORG	O	0	0
4	(	I-ORG	O	0	0
5	K+N	I-ORG	O	0	0
6	)	E-ORG	O	1	12
7	has	O	O	0	0
8	expanded	O	O	0	0
9	its	O	O	0	0
10	global	O	B-TERM	0	0
11	perishables	O	I-TERM	0	0
12	network	O	E-TERM	1	15
13	with	O	O	0	0
14	the	O	O	0	0
15	acquisition	O	S-TERM	1	22
16	of	O	O	0	0
17	sector	O	O	0	0
18	specialist	O	O	0	0
19	forwarders	O	O	0	0
20	Commodity	B-ORG	O	0	0
21	Forwarders	I-ORG	O	0	0
22	Inc.	E-ORG	O	1	24
23	(	O	O	0	0
24	CFI	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	28
25	)	O	O	0	0
26	in	O	O	0	0
27	the	O	O	0	0
28	US	S-GPE	O	0	30
29	and	O	O	0	0
30	Trillvane	S-GPE	S-TERM	1	32
31	in	O	O	0	0
32	Kenya	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
33	.	O	O	0	0

1	Switzerland-based	O	O	0	0
2	K+N	S-ORG	O	1	6
3	said	O	O	0	0
4	that	O	O	0	0
5	the	O	O	0	0
6	two	S-CARDINAL	O	1	13
7	acquisitions	O	S-TERM	0	0
8	would	O	O	0	0
9	add	O	O	0	0
10	more	B-QUANTITY	O	0	0
11	than	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
12	150,000	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
13	tons	E-QUANTITY	O	0	0
14	of	O	O	0	0
15	annual	S-DATE	O	0	0
16	perishables	O	O	0	0
17	traffic	O	O	0	0
18	to	O	O	0	0
19	its	O	O	0	0
20	network	O	O	0	0
21	and	O	O	0	0
22	"	O	O	0	0
23	further	O	O	0	0
24	strengthens	O	O	0	0
25	its	O	O	0	0
26	position	O	O	0	0
27	in	O	O	0	0
28	providing	O	O	0	0
29	end-to-end	O	O	0	0
30	international	O	O	0	0
31	and	O	O	0	0
32	domestic	O	O	0	0
33	fresh	O	O	0	0
34	chain	O	O	0	0
35	solutions	O	O	0	0
36	"	O	O	0	0
37	.	O	O	0	0

1	Together	O	O	0	0
2	with	O	O	0	0
3	CFI	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	5
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	K+N	S-ORG	O	1	9
6	becomes	O	O	0	0
7	the	O	O	0	0
8	number	O	O	0	0
9	two	S-CARDINAL	O	1	14
10	airfreight	O	O	0	0
11	forwarder	O	O	0	0
12	in	O	O	0	0
13	the	O	O	0	0
14	US	S-GPE	O	1	17
15	and	O	O	0	0
16	the	O	O	0	0
17	acquisition	O	S-TERM	1	19
18	of	O	O	0	0
19	Trillvane	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	25
20	confirms	O	O	0	0
21	our	O	O	0	0
22	leading	O	O	0	0
23	position	O	O	0	0
24	in	O	O	0	0
25	Kenya	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
26	.	O	O	0	0
27	"	O	O	0	0

1	CFI	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
2	—	O	O	0	0
3	established	O	O	0	0
4	in	O	O	0	0
5	1974	S-DATE	O	0	0
6	by	O	O	0	0
7	Alfred	B-PERSON	B-TERM	0	0
8	Kuehlewind	E-PERSON	E-TERM	0	0
9	as	O	O	0	0
10	one-man	O	O	0	0
11	office	O	O	0	0
12	in	O	O	0	0
13	Los	B-GPE	O	0	0
14	Angeles	E-GPE	O	1	18
15	shipping	O	O	0	0
16	strawberries	O	O	0	0
17	to	O	O	0	0
18	Europe	S-LOC	O	1	22
19	—	O	O	0	0
20	today	S-DATE	O	0	0
21	operates	O	O	0	0
22	14	S-CARDINAL	O	1	26
23	locations	O	O	0	0
24	throughout	O	O	0	0
25	the	O	O	0	0
26	US	S-GPE	O	1	29
27	,	O	O	0	0
28	including	O	O	0	0
29	Alaska	S-GPE	O	0	31
30	and	O	O	0	0
31	Hawaii	S-GPE	O	1	36
32	,	O	O	0	0
33	with	O	O	0	0
34	more	B-CARDINAL	O	0	0
35	than	I-CARDINAL	O	0	0
36	700	E-CARDINAL	O	0	0
37	employees	O	O	0	0
38	.	O	O	0	0

1	CFI	S-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	chief	O	I-TERM	0	0
3	executive	O	I-TERM	0	0
4	Kuehlewind	S-PERSON	E-TERM	0	0
5	said	O	O	0	0
6	:	O	O	0	0
7	"	O	O	0	0
8	We	O	O	0	0
9	are	O	O	0	0
10	looking	O	O	0	0
11	forward	O	O	0	0
12	to	O	O	0	0
13	become	O	O	0	0
14	part	O	O	0	0
15	of	O	O	0	0
16	the	B-ORG	O	0	0
17	K+N	I-ORG	O	0	0
18	Group	E-ORG	O	0	0
19	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	planned	O	O	0	0
3	transaction	O	O	0	0
4	will	O	O	0	0
5	offer	O	O	0	0
6	us	O	O	0	0
7	new	O	O	0	0
8	growth	O	O	0	0
9	perspectives	O	O	0	0
10	and	O	O	0	0
11	access	O	O	0	0
12	to	O	O	0	0
13	a	O	O	0	0
14	global	O	B-TERM	0	0
15	logistics	O	I-TERM	0	0
16	network	O	E-TERM	0	0
17	.	O	O	0	0

1	K+N	S-ORG	O	1	5
2	said	O	O	0	0
3	that	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	acquisition	O	S-TERM	1	7
6	of	O	O	0	0
7	Trillvane	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
8	will	O	O	0	0
9	enable	O	O	0	0
10	the	O	O	0	0
11	logistics	O	O	0	0
12	giant	O	O	0	0
13	to	O	O	0	0
14	"	O	O	0	0
15	strengthen	O	O	0	0
16	its	O	O	0	0
17	position	O	O	0	0
18	in	O	O	0	0
19	perishables	O	O	0	0
20	operations	O	O	0	0
21	between	O	O	0	0
22	Kenya	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	24
23	and	O	O	0	0
24	Europe	S-LOC	O	1	30
25	,	O	O	0	0
26	in	O	O	0	0
27	particular	O	O	0	0
28	to	O	O	0	0
29	the	O	O	0	0
30	UK	S-GPE	O	0	0
31	"	O	O	0	0
32	.	O	O	0	0

1	It	O	O	0	0
2	continued	O	O	0	0
3	:	O	O	0	0
4	"	O	O	0	0
5	With	O	O	0	0
6	its	O	O	0	0
7	130	S-CARDINAL	O	1	9
8	employees	O	O	0	0
9	Trillvane	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
10	is	O	O	0	0
11	specialised	O	O	0	0
12	in	O	O	0	0
13	the	O	O	0	0
14	export	O	O	0	0
15	of	O	O	0	0
16	flowers	O	O	0	0
17	and	O	O	0	0
18	vegetables	O	O	0	0
19	.	O	O	0	0

1	Its	O	O	0	0
2	location	O	O	0	0
3	at	O	O	0	0
4	the	B-FAC	O	0	0
5	Jomo	I-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
6	Kenyatta	I-FAC	I-TERM	0	0
7	International	I-FAC	I-TERM	0	0
8	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	1	10
9	in	O	O	0	0
10	Nairobi	S-GPE	O	0	0
11	provides	O	O	0	0
12	easy	O	O	0	0
13	and	O	O	0	0
14	quick	O	O	0	0
15	access	O	O	0	0
16	to	O	O	0	0
17	all	O	O	0	0
18	major	O	O	0	0
19	airlines	O	O	0	0
20	allowing	O	O	0	0
21	for	O	O	0	0
22	later	O	O	0	0
23	cut-offs	O	O	0	0
24	and	O	O	0	0
25	shorter	O	O	0	0
26	transit	O	O	0	0
27	times	O	O	0	0
28	leading	O	O	0	0
29	to	O	O	0	0
30	both	O	O	0	0
31	cost	O	O	0	0
32	savings	O	O	0	0
33	and	O	O	0	0
34	optimal	O	O	0	0
35	handling	O	O	0	0
36	of	O	O	0	0
37	temperature	O	O	0	0
38	sensitive	O	O	0	0
39	goods	O	O	0	0
40	.	O	O	0	0
41	"	O	O	0	0

1	Ruud	S-PERSON	O	0	0
2	added	O	O	0	0
3	:	O	O	0	0
4	"	O	O	0	0
5	The	O	O	0	0
6	two	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
7	acquisitions	O	S-TERM	0	0
8	mark	O	O	0	0
9	another	O	O	0	0
10	important	O	O	0	0
11	step	O	O	0	0
12	in	O	O	0	0
13	our	O	O	0	0
14	global	O	O	0	0
15	perishable	O	O	0	0
16	logistics	O	O	0	0
17	strategy	O	O	0	0
18	.	O	O	0	0

1	Another	O	O	0	0
2	European	S-NORP	O	1	7
3	mega-forwarder	O	O	0	0
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	Panalpina	S-PERSON	S-TERM	0	0
6	of	O	O	0	0
7	Switzerland	S-GPE	O	1	16
8	,	O	O	0	0
9	in	O	O	0	0
10	May	B-DATE	O	0	0
11	this	I-DATE	O	0	0
12	year	E-DATE	O	0	0
13	bought	O	O	0	0
14	family-owned	O	O	0	0
15	Air	B-ORG	O	0	0
16	Connection	E-ORG	O	1	19
17	,	O	O	0	0
18	a	O	O	0	0
19	Kenya-based	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
20	perishables	O	O	0	0
21	specialist	O	O	0	0
22	in	O	O	0	0
23	the	O	O	0	0
24	export	O	O	0	0
25	of	O	O	0	0
26	flowers	O	O	0	0
27	and	O	O	0	0
28	vegetables	O	O	0	0
29	.	O	O	0	0

1	That	O	O	0	0
2	deal	O	O	0	0
3	came	O	O	0	0
4	two	B-DATE	O	0	0
5	years	E-DATE	O	0	0
6	after	O	O	0	0
7	Panalpina	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	42
8	increased	O	O	0	0
9	its	O	O	0	0
10	presence	O	O	0	0
11	in	O	O	0	0
12	Kenyan	S-NORP	S-TERM	1	19
13	flower	O	O	0	0
14	logistics	O	O	0	0
15	by	O	O	0	0
16	acquiring	O	O	0	0
17	perishables	O	O	0	0
18	specialist	O	O	0	0
19	Airflo	S-ORG	O	0	21
20	,	O	O	0	0
21	Kenya	S-GPE	S-TERM	1	23
22	's	O	O	0	0
23	second	S-ORDINAL	O	1	7
24	largest	O	O	0	0
25	airfreight	O	O	0	0
26	forwarder	O	O	0	0
27	,	O	O	0	0
28	and	O	O	0	0
29	only	B-DATE	O	0	0
30	two	I-DATE	O	0	0
31	weeks	E-DATE	O	0	0
32	after	O	O	0	0
33	Panalpina	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
34	formally	O	O	0	0
35	announced	O	O	0	0
36	the	O	O	0	0
37	launch	O	O	0	0
38	of	O	O	0	0
39	its	O	O	0	0
40	global	O	B-TERM	0	0
41	Perishables	B-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
42	Network	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
43	.	O	O	0	0

1	LUG	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	5
2	increases	O	O	0	0
3	Health	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
4	Care	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
5	Center	E-ORG	I-TERM	1	9
6	capacity	O	E-TERM	0	0
7	and	O	O	0	0
8	undergoes	O	O	0	0
9	IATA	S-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
10	CEIV	O	E-TERM	0	0

1	LUG	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	12
2	aircargo	O	O	0	0
3	handling	O	O	0	0
4	has	O	O	0	0
5	increased	O	O	0	0
6	the	O	O	0	0
7	capacity	O	O	0	0
8	of	O	O	0	0
9	its	O	O	0	0
10	Health	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
11	Care	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
12	Center	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	14
13	(	O	O	0	0
14	HCC	S-ORG	O	1	19
15	)	O	O	0	0
16	to	O	O	0	0
17	650	B-QUANTITY	O	0	0
18	square	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
19	metres	E-QUANTITY	O	1	25
20	as	O	O	0	0
21	it	O	O	0	0
22	undergoes	O	O	0	0
23	IATA	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
24	CEIV	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
25	Pharma	E-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
26	certification	O	E-TERM	0	0
27	.	O	O	0	0

1	Staff	O	O	0	0
2	training	O	O	0	0
3	complements	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	investments	O	O	0	0
6	in	O	O	0	0
7	infrastructure	O	O	0	0
8	,	O	O	0	0
9	technical	O	O	0	0
10	equipment	O	O	0	0
11	and	O	O	0	0
12	processes	O	O	0	0
13	,	O	O	0	0
14	and	O	O	0	0
15	LUG	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
16	should	O	O	0	0
17	be	O	O	0	0
18	certified	O	O	0	0
19	by	O	O	0	0
20	the	B-DATE	O	0	0
21	end	I-DATE	O	0	0
22	of	I-DATE	O	0	0
23	the	I-DATE	O	0	0
24	first	I-DATE	O	0	0
25	quarter	I-DATE	O	0	0
26	of	I-DATE	O	0	0
27	2018	E-DATE	O	0	0
28	.	O	O	0	0

1	Misskampf	S-PERSON	O	0	0
2	says	O	O	0	0
3	he	O	O	0	0
4	has	O	O	0	0
5	gained	O	O	0	0
6	a	O	O	0	0
7	very	O	O	0	0
8	good	O	O	0	0
9	impression	O	O	0	0
10	of	O	O	0	0
11	the	O	O	0	0
12	daily	O	O	0	0
13	operations	O	O	0	0
14	and	O	O	0	0
15	capabilities	O	O	0	0
16	of	O	O	0	0
17	the	O	O	0	0
18	staff	O	O	0	0
19	at	O	O	0	0
20	LUG	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
21	,	O	O	0	0
22	saying	O	O	0	0
23	:	O	O	0	0
24	"	O	O	0	0
25	I	O	O	0	0
26	am	O	O	0	0
27	delighted	O	O	0	0
28	to	O	O	0	0
29	be	O	O	0	0
30	part	O	O	0	0
31	of	O	O	0	0
32	the	O	O	0	0
33	LUG	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
34	team	O	O	0	0
35	and	O	O	0	0
36	to	O	O	0	0
37	make	O	O	0	0
38	a	O	O	0	0
39	contribution	O	O	0	0
40	to	O	O	0	0
41	the	O	O	0	0
42	expansion	O	O	0	0
43	of	O	O	0	0
44	the	O	O	0	0
45	HCC	S-ORG	O	0	0
46	.	O	O	0	0

1	First	S-ORDINAL	O	1	7
2	air	O	O	0	0
3	cargo	O	O	0	0
4	digital	O	O	0	0
5	corridor	O	O	0	0
6	between	O	O	0	0
7	India	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	9
8	and	O	O	0	0
9	Netherlands	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
10	established	O	O	0	0

1	Kale	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Logistics	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
3	Solutions	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
4	has	O	O	0	0
5	signed	O	O	0	0
6	a	O	O	0	0
7	memorandum	O	O	0	0
8	of	O	O	0	0
9	understanding	O	O	0	0
10	(	O	O	0	0
11	MoU	O	O	0	0
12	)	O	O	0	0
13	with	O	O	0	0
14	Cargonaut	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	21
15	,	O	O	0	0
16	an	O	O	0	0
17	established	O	O	0	0
18	cargo	O	B-TERM	0	0
19	community	O	I-TERM	0	0
20	service	O	I-TERM	0	0
21	provider	O	E-TERM	1	25
22	based	O	O	0	0
23	in	O	O	0	0
24	the	O	O	0	0
25	Netherlands	S-GPE	S-TERM	1	32
26	to	O	O	0	0
27	create	O	O	0	0
28	a	O	O	0	0
29	digital	O	B-TERM	0	0
30	air	O	I-TERM	0	0
31	freight	O	I-TERM	0	0
32	corridor	O	E-TERM	1	35
33	between	O	O	0	0
34	the	O	O	0	0
35	two	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
36	countries	O	O	0	0
37	that	O	O	0	0
38	will	O	O	0	0
39	enhance	O	O	0	0
40	shipment	O	O	0	0
41	visibility	O	O	0	0
42	and	O	O	0	0
43	optimise	O	O	0	0
44	flow	O	O	0	0
45	of	O	O	0	0
46	cargo	O	O	0	0
47	data	O	O	0	0
48	.	O	O	0	0

1	In	O	O	0	0
2	the	O	O	0	0
3	first	S-ORDINAL	O	1	8
4	of	O	O	0	0
5	its	O	O	0	0
6	kind	O	O	0	0
7	,	O	O	0	0
8	Mumbai	S-GPE	O	1	11
9	airport	O	O	0	0
10	,	O	O	0	0
11	India	S-GPE	S-TERM	1	16
12	and	O	O	0	0
13	Schiphol	S-GPE	O	1	16
14	airport	O	O	0	0
15	,	O	O	0	0
16	Netherlands	S-GPE	S-TERM	1	23
17	along	O	O	0	0
18	with	O	O	0	0
19	their	O	O	0	0
20	partners	O	O	0	0
21	for	O	O	0	0
22	Cargo	B-ORG	O	0	0
23	Community	E-ORG	O	1	28
24	systems	O	O	0	0
25	,	O	O	0	0
26	Kale	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
27	Logistics	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
28	Solutions	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	30
29	and	O	O	0	0
30	Cargonaut	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	40
31	have	O	O	0	0
32	pioneered	O	O	0	0
33	an	O	O	0	0
34	initiative	O	O	0	0
35	towards	O	O	0	0
36	creating	O	O	0	0
37	a	O	O	0	0
38	digital	O	B-TERM	0	0
39	air	O	I-TERM	0	0
40	corridor	O	E-TERM	1	11
41	between	O	O	0	0
42	India	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
43	and	O	O	0	0
44	the	O	O	0	0
45	Netherlands	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
46	.	O	O	0	0

1	Following	O	O	0	0
2	the	O	O	0	0
3	signing	O	O	0	0
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	both	O	O	0	0
6	companies	O	O	0	0
7	will	O	O	0	0
8	collaboratively	O	O	0	0
9	develop	O	O	0	0
10	a	O	O	0	0
11	shared	O	O	0	0
12	interface	O	O	0	0
13	between	O	O	0	0
14	their	O	O	0	0
15	respective	O	B-TERM	0	0
16	air	O	I-TERM	0	0
17	cargo	O	I-TERM	0	0
18	community	O	I-TERM	0	0
19	systems	O	E-TERM	0	0
20	.	O	O	0	0

1	Amar	B-PERSON	O	0	0
2	More	E-PERSON	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	CEO	O	O	0	0
5	,	O	O	0	0
6	Kale	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
7	Logistics	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
8	Solutions	E-ORG	I-TERM	1	7
9	CEO	O	I-TERM	0	0
10	Amar	B-PERSON	E-TERM	0	0
11	More	E-PERSON	O	0	0
12	says	O	O	0	0
13	:	O	O	0	0
14	"	O	O	0	0
15	Kale	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
16	Logistics	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
17	has	O	O	0	0
18	always	O	O	0	0
19	been	O	O	0	0
20	at	O	O	0	0
21	the	O	O	0	0
22	forefront	O	O	0	0
23	of	O	O	0	0
24	driving	O	O	0	0
25	trade	O	O	0	0
26	facilitation	O	O	0	0
27	across	O	O	0	0
28	the	O	O	0	0
29	logistics	O	O	0	0
30	and	O	O	0	0
31	supply	O	O	0	0
32	chain	O	O	0	0
33	sector	O	O	0	0
34	.	O	O	0	0

1	Collaborating	O	O	0	0
2	with	O	O	0	0
3	an	O	O	0	0
4	accomplished	O	O	0	0
5	partner	O	O	0	0
6	like	O	O	0	0
7	Cargonaut	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
8	,	O	O	0	0
9	has	O	O	0	0
10	certainly	O	O	0	0
11	given	O	O	0	0
12	us	O	O	0	0
13	an	O	O	0	0
14	edge	O	O	0	0
15	to	O	O	0	0
16	extend	O	O	0	0
17	our	O	O	0	0
18	Trade	B-ORG	O	0	0
19	Facilitation	E-ORG	O	1	22
20	initiatives	O	O	0	0
21	across	O	O	0	0
22	Europe	S-LOC	O	0	0
23	.	O	O	0	0

1	Nanne	B-PERSON	O	0	0
2	Onland	E-PERSON	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	CEO	O	O	0	0
5	,	O	O	0	0
6	Cargonaut	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	29
7	adds	O	O	0	0
8	:	O	O	0	0
9	"	O	O	0	0
10	The	O	O	0	0
11	collaboration	O	O	0	0
12	between	O	O	0	0
13	Kale	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
14	Logistics	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	6
15	and	O	O	0	0
16	Cargonaut	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
17	fits	O	O	0	0
18	perfectly	O	O	0	0
19	in	O	O	0	0
20	our	O	O	0	0
21	mutual	O	O	0	0
22	aim	O	O	0	0
23	to	O	O	0	0
24	create	O	O	0	0
25	a	B-ORG	O	0	0
26	Network	I-ORG	O	0	0
27	of	I-ORG	O	0	0
28	Trusted	I-ORG	O	0	0
29	Networks	E-ORG	O	0	0
30	.	O	O	0	0

1	Together	O	O	0	0
2	we	O	O	0	0
3	can	O	O	0	0
4	establish	O	O	0	0
5	a	O	O	0	0
6	'	O	O	0	0
7	virtual	O	O	0	0
8	'	O	O	0	0
9	platform	O	O	0	0
10	for	O	O	0	0
11	our	O	O	0	0
12	joined	O	O	0	0
13	customers	O	O	0	0
14	in	O	O	0	0
15	India	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	18
16	and	O	O	0	0
17	The	B-GPE	O	0	0
18	Netherlands	E-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
19	.	O	O	0	0

1	Pictured	O	O	0	0
2	:	O	O	0	0
3	Amar	B-PERSON	O	0	0
4	More	E-PERSON	O	0	0
5	(	O	O	0	0
6	first	S-ORDINAL	O	1	14
7	from	O	O	0	0
8	left	O	O	0	0
9	)	O	O	0	0
10	and	O	O	0	0
11	Bart	B-PERSON	O	0	0
12	Pouwels	E-PERSON	O	0	0
13	(	O	O	0	0
14	second	S-ORDINAL	O	1	19
15	from	O	O	0	0
16	right	O	O	0	0
17	)	O	O	0	0
18	from	O	O	0	0
19	Schiphol	S-GPE	O	1	22
20	signing	O	O	0	0
21	the	O	O	0	0
22	MoU	S-ORG	O	0	0
23	in	O	O	0	0
24	the	O	O	0	0
25	presence	O	O	0	0
26	of	O	O	0	0
27	Vandana	B-PERSON	O	0	0
28	Aggarwal	E-PERSON	O	0	0
29	,	O	O	0	0
30	economic	O	O	0	0
31	advisor	O	O	0	0
32	,	O	O	0	0
33	Ministry	B-ORG	O	0	0
34	of	I-ORG	O	0	0
35	Civil	I-ORG	O	0	0
36	Aviation	E-ORG	O	1	38
37	(	O	O	0	0
38	India	S-GPE	S-TERM	1	6
39	)	O	O	0	0
40	;	O	O	0	0
41	Manoj	B-PERSON	O	0	0
42	Singh	E-PERSON	O	0	0
43	,	O	O	0	0
44	senior	O	O	0	0
45	vice	O	O	0	0
46	president	O	O	0	0
47	and	O	O	0	0
48	head	O	O	0	0
49	–	O	O	0	0
50	cargo	O	O	0	0
51	,	O	O	0	0
52	Mumbai	B-ORG	O	0	0
53	International	I-ORG	O	0	0
54	Airport	E-ORG	O	1	38
55	(	O	O	0	0
56	India	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
57	)	O	O	0	0
58	and	O	O	0	0
59	Angshumali	B-PERSON	O	0	0
60	Rastogi	E-PERSON	O	0	0
61	,	O	O	0	0
62	director	O	O	0	0
63	,	O	O	0	0
64	ministry	O	O	0	0
65	of	O	O	0	0
66	civil	O	O	0	0
67	aviation	O	O	0	0
68	,	O	O	0	0
69	(	O	O	0	0
70	India	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
71	)	O	O	0	0
72	(	O	O	0	0
73	first	S-ORDINAL	O	0	0
74	from	O	O	0	0
75	right	O	O	0	0
76	)	O	O	0	0

1	India	S-GPE	S-TERM	1	3
2	's	O	O	0	0
3	first	S-ORDINAL	O	1	5
4	online	O	O	0	0
5	e-Booking	S-PRODUCT	O	1	6
6	platform	O	S-TERM	1	9
7	for	O	O	0	0
8	air	O	B-TERM	0	0
9	cargo	O	E-TERM	0	0
10	launched	O	O	0	0

1	Kale	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Logistics	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
3	Solutions	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
4	is	O	O	0	0
5	offering	O	O	0	0
6	a	O	O	0	0
7	comprehensive	O	O	0	0
8	suite	O	O	0	0
9	of	O	O	0	0
10	IT	O	O	0	0
11	solutions	O	O	0	0
12	for	O	O	0	0
13	the	O	O	0	0
14	logistics	O	B-TERM	0	0
15	domain	O	E-TERM	0	0
16	.	O	O	0	0

1	Recently	O	O	0	0
2	,	O	O	0	0
3	the	O	O	0	0
4	company	O	O	0	0
5	launched	O	O	0	0
6	a	O	O	0	0
7	specialised	O	O	0	0
8	e-Booking	S-ORG	O	1	9
9	platform	O	S-TERM	1	13
10	under	O	O	0	0
11	the	O	O	0	0
12	brand	O	O	0	0
13	RIGEL	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	17
14	at	O	O	0	0
15	WINGS	B-PRODUCT	B-TERM	0	0
16	INDIA	I-PRODUCT	E-TERM	0	0
17	2018	E-PRODUCT	O	1	19
18	at	O	O	0	0
19	Hyderabad	S-GPE	O	0	16
20	,	O	O	0	0
21	India	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
22	(	O	O	0	0
23	pictured	O	O	0	0
24	)	O	O	0	0
25	.	O	O	0	0

1	This	B-ORG	O	0	0
2	One	I-ORG	O	0	0
3	Stop	I-ORG	O	0	0
4	e-Booking	I-ORG	O	0	0
5	Platform	E-ORG	S-TERM	1	7
6	is	O	O	0	0
7	India	S-GPE	S-TERM	1	9
8	's	O	O	0	0
9	first	S-ORDINAL	O	1	5
10	comprehensive	O	O	0	0
11	online	O	O	0	0
12	platform	O	S-TERM	0	0
13	to	O	O	0	0
14	assist	O	O	0	0
15	cargo	O	O	0	0
16	rate	O	O	0	0
17	discovery	O	O	0	0
18	and	O	O	0	0
19	booking	O	O	0	0
20	procedures	O	O	0	0
21	for	O	O	0	0
22	the	O	O	0	0
23	air	O	B-TERM	0	0
24	cargo	O	I-TERM	0	0
25	industry	O	E-TERM	0	0
26	.	O	O	0	0

1	With	O	O	0	0
2	Kale	S-ORG	O	1	6
3	's	O	O	0	0
4	online	O	O	0	0
5	e-Booking	O	O	0	0
6	platform	O	S-TERM	0	0
7	,	O	O	0	0
8	routes	O	O	0	0
9	,	O	O	0	0
10	rates	O	O	0	0
11	and	O	O	0	0
12	schedules	O	O	0	0
13	for	O	O	0	0
14	cargo	O	O	0	0
15	booking	O	O	0	0
16	are	O	O	0	0
17	readily	O	O	0	0
18	accessible	O	O	0	0
19	through	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	system	O	O	0	0
22	,	O	O	0	0
23	thereby	O	O	0	0
24	benefitting	O	O	0	0
25	the	O	O	0	0
26	concerned	O	O	0	0
27	stakeholders	O	O	0	0
28	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	platform	O	S-TERM	0	0
3	is	O	O	0	0
4	equipped	O	O	0	0
5	with	O	O	0	0
6	comprehensive	O	O	0	0
7	modules	O	O	0	0
8	for	O	O	0	0
9	such	O	O	0	0
10	as	O	O	0	0
11	quote	O	O	0	0
12	management	O	O	0	0
13	,	O	O	0	0
14	multi-channel	O	O	0	0
15	booking	O	O	0	0
16	with	O	O	0	0
17	EDI	O	O	0	0
18	communication	O	O	0	0
19	with	O	O	0	0
20	airlines	O	O	0	0
21	,	O	O	0	0
22	GST	O	O	0	0
23	invoicing	O	O	0	0
24	,	O	O	0	0
25	e-payment	O	O	0	0
26	gateway	O	O	0	0
27	,	O	O	0	0
28	tracking	O	O	0	0
29	and	O	O	0	0
30	reporting	O	O	0	0
31	for	O	O	0	0
32	all	O	O	0	0
33	stakeholders	O	O	0	0
34	.	O	O	0	0

1	Commenting	O	O	0	0
2	on	O	O	0	0
3	the	O	O	0	0
4	launch	O	O	0	0
5	,	O	O	0	0
6	Indian	B-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
7	Ministry	I-ORG	O	0	0
8	of	I-ORG	O	0	0
9	Civil	I-ORG	O	0	0
10	Aviation	E-ORG	O	0	0
11	secretary	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	Rajiv	B-PERSON	B-TERM	0	0
14	Nayan	I-PERSON	I-TERM	0	0
15	Choubey	E-PERSON	E-TERM	0	0
16	says	O	O	0	0
17	:	O	O	0	0
18	"	O	O	0	0
19	Platforms	O	S-TERM	0	0
20	such	O	O	0	0
21	as	O	O	0	0
22	RIGEL	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
23	have	O	O	0	0
24	become	O	O	0	0
25	a	O	O	0	0
26	necessity	O	O	0	0
27	in	O	O	0	0
28	today	S-DATE	O	0	0
29	's	O	O	0	0
30	trade	O	O	0	0
31	eco-system	O	O	0	0
32	.	O	O	0	0

1	Trade	O	O	0	0
2	facilitation	O	O	0	0
3	initiatives	O	O	0	0
4	like	O	O	0	0
5	RIGEL	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
6	provide	O	O	0	0
7	the	O	O	0	0
8	much	O	O	0	0
9	necessary	O	O	0	0
10	digital	O	O	0	0
11	support	O	O	0	0
12	to	O	O	0	0
13	drive	O	O	0	0
14	ease	O	O	0	0
15	of	O	O	0	0
16	business	O	O	0	0
17	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	Moreover	O	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	it	O	O	0	0
5	also	O	O	0	0
6	brings	O	O	0	0
7	stakeholders	O	O	0	0
8	,	O	O	0	0
9	including	O	O	0	0
10	the	O	O	0	0
11	shippers	O	O	0	0
12	from	O	O	0	0
13	the	O	O	0	0
14	hinterlands	O	O	0	0
15	of	O	O	0	0
16	India	S-GPE	S-TERM	1	21
17	,	O	O	0	0
18	under	O	O	0	0
19	a	O	O	0	0
20	single	O	O	0	0
21	platform	O	S-TERM	0	0
22	thus	O	O	0	0
23	allowing	O	O	0	0
24	an	O	O	0	0
25	opportunity	O	O	0	0
26	to	O	O	0	0
27	discuss	O	O	0	0
28	and	O	O	0	0
29	find	O	O	0	0
30	constructive	O	O	0	0
31	solutions	O	O	0	0
32	for	O	O	0	0
33	the	O	O	0	0
34	furtherance	O	O	0	0
35	of	O	O	0	0
36	the	O	O	0	0
37	industry	O	O	0	0
38	along	O	O	0	0
39	with	O	O	0	0
40	necessary	O	O	0	0
41	compliance	O	O	0	0
42	being	O	O	0	0
43	met	O	O	0	0
44	.	O	O	0	0

1	RIGEL	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
2	reaffirms	O	O	0	0
3	the	O	O	0	0
4	role	O	O	0	0
5	of	O	O	0	0
6	technology	O	O	0	0
7	in	O	O	0	0
8	streamlining	O	O	0	0
9	and	O	O	0	0
10	improving	O	O	0	0
11	the	O	O	0	0
12	air	O	B-TERM	0	0
13	cargo	O	I-TERM	0	0
14	trade	O	I-TERM	0	0
15	scenario	O	E-TERM	0	0
16	.	O	O	0	0

1	Lufthansa	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	5
3	broadens	O	O	0	0
4	digitalization	O	B-TERM	0	0
5	efforts	O	E-TERM	0	0
6	with	O	O	0	0
7	cargo.one	O	O	0	0
8	investment	O	O	0	0

1	Lufthansa	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
3	is	O	O	0	0
4	further	O	O	0	0
5	ramping	O	O	0	0
6	up	O	O	0	0
7	its	O	O	0	0
8	foothold	O	O	0	0
9	in	O	O	0	0
10	the	O	O	0	0
11	tech	O	O	0	0
12	sphere	O	O	0	0
13	by	O	O	0	0
14	increasing	O	O	0	0
15	its	O	O	0	0
16	cooperation	O	O	0	0
17	with	O	O	0	0
18	Berlin-based	O	O	0	0
19	software-as-a-service	O	O	0	0
20	(	O	O	0	0
21	SaaS	S-ORG	O	0	0
22	)	O	O	0	0
23	provider	O	O	0	0
24	,	O	O	0	0
25	cargo.one	O	O	0	0
26	.	O	O	0	0

1	To	O	O	0	0
2	date	O	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	some	O	O	0	0
5	of	O	O	0	0
6	cargo.one	S-ORG	O	1	8
7	's	O	O	0	0
8	customers	O	S-TERM	1	12
9	include	O	O	0	0
10	industry	O	O	0	0
11	giants	O	O	0	0
12	Agility	S-ORG	O	0	14
13	,	O	O	0	0
14	Hellmann	S-ORG	O	0	16
15	and	O	O	0	0
16	Dachser	S-ORG	O	0	0
17	.	O	O	0	0

1	Peter	B-PERSON	O	0	0
2	Gerber	E-PERSON	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	CEO	O	O	0	0
5	of	O	O	0	0
6	the	B-ORG	O	0	0
7	Lufthansa	I-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
8	Group	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
9	said	O	O	0	0
10	that	O	O	0	0
11	the	O	O	0	0
12	investment	O	O	0	0
13	is	O	O	0	0
14	another	O	O	0	0
15	step	O	O	0	0
16	toward	O	O	0	0
17	the	O	O	0	0
18	company	O	O	0	0
19	's	O	O	0	0
20	goal	O	O	0	0
21	to	O	O	0	0
22	lead	O	O	0	0
23	digitalization	O	O	0	0
24	in	O	O	0	0
25	the	O	O	0	0
26	air	O	B-TERM	0	0
27	freight	O	I-TERM	0	0
28	industry	O	E-TERM	0	0
29	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	Our	O	O	0	0
3	customers	O	S-TERM	0	0
4	'	O	O	0	0
5	overall	O	O	0	0
6	experience	O	O	0	0
7	is	O	O	0	0
8	now	O	O	0	0
9	strongly	O	O	0	0
10	improved	O	O	0	0
11	by	O	O	0	0
12	being	O	O	0	0
13	able	O	O	0	0
14	to	O	O	0	0
15	more	O	O	0	0
16	efficiently	O	O	0	0
17	book	O	O	0	0
18	air	O	B-TERM	0	0
19	cargo	O	I-TERM	0	0
20	capacity	O	E-TERM	0	0
21	.	O	O	0	0
22	"	O	O	0	0

1	Lufthansa	S-ORG	O	0	0
2	began	O	O	0	0
3	its	O	O	0	0
4	relationship	O	O	0	0
5	with	O	O	0	0
6	cargo.one	O	O	0	0
7	in	O	O	0	0
8	July	B-DATE	O	0	0
9	of	I-DATE	O	0	0
10	this	I-DATE	O	0	0
11	year	E-DATE	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	following	O	O	0	0
14	its	O	O	0	0
15	announcement	O	O	0	0
16	in	O	O	0	0
17	March	S-DATE	O	0	0
18	to	O	O	0	0
19	charge	O	O	0	0
20	an	O	O	0	0
21	extra	O	O	0	0
22	€12	S-MONEY	O	1	28
23	processing	O	O	0	0
24	fee	O	O	0	0
25	per	O	O	0	0
26	transaction	O	O	0	0
27	for	O	O	0	0
28	customers	O	S-TERM	0	0
29	that	O	O	0	0
30	choose	O	O	0	0
31	not	O	O	0	0
32	to	O	O	0	0
33	opt	O	O	0	0
34	for	O	O	0	0
35	its	O	O	0	0
36	electronic	O	O	0	0
37	air	O	O	0	0
38	waybills	O	O	0	0
39	.	O	O	0	0

1	Such	O	O	0	0
2	moves	O	O	0	0
3	are	O	O	0	0
4	part	O	O	0	0
5	of	O	O	0	0
6	the	O	O	0	0
7	carrier	O	O	0	0
8	's	O	O	0	0
9	"	O	O	0	0
10	strategic	O	O	0	0
11	commitment	O	O	0	0
12	to	O	O	0	0
13	elevating	O	O	0	0
14	the	O	O	0	0
15	air	O	B-TERM	0	0
16	cargo	O	I-TERM	0	0
17	industry	O	E-TERM	0	0
18	to	O	O	0	0
19	a	O	O	0	0
20	higher	O	O	0	0
21	level	O	O	0	0
22	of	O	O	0	0
23	digital	O	O	0	0
24	maturity	O	O	0	0
25	,	O	O	0	0
26	"	O	O	0	0
27	said	O	O	0	0
28	Boris	B-PERSON	O	0	0
29	Hueske	E-PERSON	O	0	0
30	,	O	O	0	0
31	the	O	O	0	0
32	head	O	O	0	0
33	of	O	O	0	0
34	digital	O	O	0	0
35	transformation	O	O	0	0
36	at	O	O	0	0
37	Lufthansa	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
38	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
39	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	German	S-NORP	O	0	0
3	carrier	O	O	0	0
4	has	O	O	0	0
5	fostered	O	O	0	0
6	relationships	O	O	0	0
7	with	O	O	0	0
8	other	O	O	0	0
9	tech	O	O	0	0
10	startups	O	O	0	0
11	over	O	O	0	0
12	the	B-DATE	O	0	0
13	year	E-DATE	O	0	0
14	,	O	O	0	0
15	including	O	O	0	0
16	an	O	O	0	0
17	investment	O	O	0	0
18	in	O	O	0	0
19	Fleet	B-ORG	O	0	0
20	Logistics	E-ORG	O	1	23
21	,	O	O	0	0
22	a	O	O	0	0
23	Portland	S-GPE	O	0	25
24	,	O	O	0	0
25	Ore.-based	S-GPE	O	1	34
26	digital	O	O	0	0
27	marketplace	O	O	0	0
28	that	O	O	0	0
29	serves	O	O	0	0
30	to	O	O	0	0
31	match	O	O	0	0
32	carriers	O	O	0	0
33	with	O	O	0	0
34	customers	O	S-TERM	1	44
35	,	O	O	0	0
36	and	O	O	0	0
37	a	O	O	0	0
38	cooperation	O	O	0	0
39	with	O	O	0	0
40	a	O	O	0	0
41	California-based	O	O	0	0
42	accelerator	O	O	0	0
43	,	O	O	0	0
44	Plug	S-ORG	O	0	46
45	and	O	O	0	0
46	Play	S-ORG	O	0	0
47	,	O	O	0	0
48	which	O	O	0	0
49	has	O	O	0	0
50	a	O	O	0	0
51	focus	O	O	0	0
52	on	O	O	0	0
53	supply	O	O	0	0
54	chain-oriented	O	O	0	0
55	startups	O	O	0	0
56	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	The	O	O	0	0
3	close	O	O	0	0
4	cooperation	O	O	0	0
5	between	O	O	0	0
6	Lufthansa	B-ORG	B-TERM	1	40
7	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	15
8	and	O	O	0	0
9	technology	O	O	0	0
10	startups	O	O	0	0
11	melds	O	O	0	0
12	comprehensive	O	B-TERM	0	0
13	air	O	I-TERM	0	0
14	cargo	O	I-TERM	0	0
15	experience	O	E-TERM	0	0
16	with	O	O	0	0
17	a	O	O	0	0
18	technology-driven	O	O	0	0
19	,	O	O	0	0
20	fresh	O	O	0	0
21	view	O	O	0	0
22	of	O	O	0	0
23	global	O	O	0	0
24	logistics	O	O	0	0
25	processes	O	O	0	0
26	"	O	O	0	0
27	,	O	O	0	0
28	Hueske	S-ORG	O	1	6
29	said	O	O	0	0
30	,	O	O	0	0
31	although	O	O	0	0
32	the	O	O	0	0
33	details	O	O	0	0
34	of	O	O	0	0
35	Lufthansa	S-ORG	O	0	0
36	's	O	O	0	0
37	partnerships	O	O	0	0
38	with	O	O	0	0
39	the	O	O	0	0
40	two	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
41	above-named	O	O	0	0
42	organizations	O	O	0	0
43	has	O	O	0	0
44	not	O	O	0	0
45	been	O	O	0	0
46	made	O	O	0	0
47	explicit	O	O	0	0
48	.	O	O	0	0

1	Those	O	O	0	0
2	interested	O	O	0	0
3	in	O	O	0	0
4	learning	O	O	0	0
5	more	O	O	0	0
6	about	O	O	0	0
7	the	O	O	0	0
8	digitalization	O	O	0	0
9	of	O	O	0	0
10	the	O	O	0	0
11	air	O	B-TERM	0	0
12	freight	O	I-TERM	0	0
13	industry	O	E-TERM	1	21
14	are	O	O	0	0
15	invited	O	O	0	0
16	to	O	O	0	0
17	join	O	O	0	0
18	us	O	O	0	0
19	Cargo	B-EVENT	B-TERM	0	0
20	Facts	I-EVENT	I-TERM	0	0
21	EMEA	E-EVENT	E-TERM	1	32
22	,	O	O	0	0
23	to	O	O	0	0
24	be	O	O	0	0
25	held	O	O	0	0
26	4-6	B-DATE	O	0	0
27	February	E-DATE	O	0	0
28	at	O	O	0	0
29	The	B-FAC	O	0	0
30	Westin	I-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
31	Grand	I-FAC	I-TERM	0	0
32	Frankfurt	E-FAC	E-TERM	0	0
33	.	O	O	0	0

1	Hyderabad	B-FAC	S-TERM	0	0
2	Airport	E-FAC	O	1	5
3	launches	O	O	0	0
4	"	O	O	0	0
5	first	S-ORDINAL	O	0	0
6	of	O	O	0	0
7	its	O	O	0	0
8	kind	O	O	0	0
9	"	O	O	0	0
10	cargo	O	B-TERM	0	0
11	charter	O	I-TERM	0	0
12	programme	O	E-TERM	0	0

1	GMR	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Hyderabad	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
3	Airport	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
4	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	9
5	has	O	O	0	0
6	launched	O	O	0	0
7	a	O	O	0	0
8	"	O	O	0	0
9	first	S-ORDINAL	O	1	16
10	of	O	O	0	0
11	its	O	O	0	0
12	kind	O	O	0	0
13	"	O	O	0	0
14	cargo	O	B-TERM	0	0
15	charter	O	I-TERM	0	0
16	programme	O	E-TERM	0	0
17	that	O	O	0	0
18	offers	O	O	0	0
19	enhanced	O	O	0	0
20	services	O	O	0	0
21	for	O	O	0	0
22	its	O	O	0	0
23	members	O	O	0	0
24	as	O	O	0	0
25	it	O	O	0	0
26	continues	O	O	0	0
27	to	O	O	0	0
28	target	O	O	0	0
29	the	O	O	0	0
30	market	O	O	0	0
31	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	airport	O	S-TERM	1	7
3	's	O	O	0	0
4	Hyderabad	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
5	Cargo	I-FAC	I-TERM	0	0
6	Charter	I-FAC	I-TERM	0	0
7	Circle	E-FAC	E-TERM	0	0
8	(	O	O	0	0
9	HC3	O	O	0	0
10	)	O	O	0	0
11	platform	O	O	0	0
12	will	O	O	0	0
13	provide	O	O	0	0
14	additional	O	O	0	0
15	free	O	O	0	0
16	cargo	O	O	0	0
17	storage	O	O	0	0
18	time	O	O	0	0
19	;	O	O	0	0
20	single	O	O	0	0
21	point	O	O	0	0
22	of	O	O	0	0
23	contact	O	O	0	0
24	for	O	O	0	0
25	all	O	O	0	0
26	aspects	O	O	0	0
27	related	O	O	0	0
28	to	O	O	0	0
29	cargo	O	O	0	0
30	handling	O	O	0	0
31	;	O	O	0	0
32	priority	O	O	0	0
33	storage	O	O	0	0
34	allocation	O	O	0	0
35	and	O	O	0	0
36	end-to-end	O	O	0	0
37	logistics	O	O	0	0
38	support	O	O	0	0
39	within	O	O	0	0
40	the	O	O	0	0
41	terminal	O	O	0	0
42	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	GMR	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
3	Hyderabad	I-ORG	I-TERM	1	18
4	Airport	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
5	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	3
6	has	O	O	0	0
7	taken	O	O	0	0
8	a	O	O	0	0
9	strategic	O	O	0	0
10	step	O	O	0	0
11	to	O	O	0	0
12	develop	O	O	0	0
13	Hyderabad	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
14	as	O	O	0	0
15	an	B-LOC	O	0	0
16	Air	I-LOC	B-TERM	0	0
17	Charter	I-LOC	I-TERM	0	0
18	Hub	E-LOC	E-TERM	1	21
19	for	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	South	S-LOC	O	1	24
22	[	O	O	0	0
23	of	O	O	0	0
24	India	S-GPE	O	0	0
25	]	O	O	0	0
26	and	O	O	0	0
27	boost	O	O	0	0
28	the	O	O	0	0
29	regional	O	O	0	0
30	direct	O	O	0	0
31	connectivity	O	O	0	0
32	and	O	O	0	0
33	link	O	O	0	0
34	it	O	O	0	0
35	to	O	O	0	0
36	the	O	O	0	0
37	main	O	O	0	0
38	hubs	O	O	0	0
39	across	O	O	0	0
40	the	O	O	0	0
41	globe	O	O	0	0
42	,	O	O	0	0
43	"	O	O	0	0
44	the	O	O	0	0
45	airport	O	S-TERM	0	0
46	said	O	O	0	0
47	.	O	O	0	0

1	SGK	B-PERSON	O	0	0
2	Kishore	E-PERSON	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	chief	O	O	0	0
5	executive	O	O	0	0
6	,	O	O	0	0
7	GMR	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
8	Hyderabad	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
9	Airport	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
10	Cargo	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
11	Limited	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	13
12	(	O	O	0	0
13	GHAL	S-ORG	O	1	20
14	)	O	O	0	0
15	,	O	O	0	0
16	said	O	O	0	0
17	:	O	O	0	0
18	"	O	O	0	0
19	Cargo	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
20	Charters	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	22
21	in	O	O	0	0
22	India	S-GPE	O	0	0
23	as	O	O	0	0
24	a	O	O	0	0
25	concept	O	O	0	0
26	is	O	O	0	0
27	still	O	O	0	0
28	in	O	O	0	0
29	a	O	O	0	0
30	nascent	O	O	0	0
31	phase	O	O	0	0
32	.	O	O	0	0

1	It	O	O	0	0
2	contributes	O	O	0	0
3	a	O	O	0	0
4	small	O	O	0	0
5	proportion	O	O	0	0
6	of	O	O	0	0
7	the	O	O	0	0
8	volume	O	O	0	0
9	handled	O	O	0	0
10	by	O	O	0	0
11	the	O	O	0	0
12	Indian	S-NORP	O	1	23
13	airports	O	S-TERM	0	0
14	currently	O	O	0	0
15	,	O	O	0	0
16	but	O	O	0	0
17	as	O	O	0	0
18	an	O	O	0	0
19	emerging	O	O	0	0
20	market	O	O	0	0
21	,	O	O	0	0
22	cargo	O	B-TERM	0	0
23	charters	O	E-TERM	0	0
24	holds	O	O	0	0
25	a	O	O	0	0
26	lot	O	O	0	0
27	of	O	O	0	0
28	promise	O	O	0	0
29	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	Realising	O	O	0	0
3	this	O	O	0	0
4	potential	O	O	0	0
5	,	O	O	0	0
6	we	O	O	0	0
7	have	O	O	0	0
8	launched	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	HC3	S-ORG	O	0	0
11	platform	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	which	O	O	0	0
14	will	O	O	0	0
15	act	O	O	0	0
16	as	O	O	0	0
17	an	O	O	0	0
18	industry	O	O	0	0
19	forum	O	O	0	0
20	led	O	O	0	0
21	by	O	O	0	0
22	Hyderabad	B-FAC	S-TERM	0	0
23	Airport	E-FAC	O	0	0
24	to	O	O	0	0
25	give	O	O	0	0
26	the	O	O	0	0
27	value	O	O	0	0
28	add	O	O	0	0
29	and	O	O	0	0
30	advantage	O	O	0	0
31	to	O	O	0	0
32	this	O	O	0	0
33	segment	O	O	0	0
34	of	O	O	0	0
35	the	O	O	0	0
36	industry	O	O	0	0
37	and	O	O	0	0
38	help	O	O	0	0
39	boost	O	O	0	0
40	trade	O	O	0	0
41	and	O	O	0	0
42	logistics	O	O	0	0
43	.	O	O	0	0
44	"	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	airport	O	S-TERM	0	0
3	said	O	O	0	0
4	that	O	O	0	0
5	it	O	O	0	0
6	had	O	O	0	0
7	seen	O	O	0	0
8	growing	O	O	0	0
9	demand	O	O	0	0
10	for	O	O	0	0
11	charter	O	O	0	0
12	flights	O	O	0	0
13	covering	O	O	0	0
14	pharma	O	O	0	0
15	,	O	O	0	0
16	engineering	O	O	0	0
17	goods	O	O	0	0
18	,	O	O	0	0
19	telecoms	O	O	0	0
20	,	O	O	0	0
21	defence	O	O	0	0
22	and	O	O	0	0
23	aerospace	O	O	0	0
24	shipments	O	O	0	0
25	.	O	O	0	0

1	of	O	O	0	0
2	India	S-GPE	O	1	6
3	's	O	O	0	0
4	vision	O	O	0	0
5	,	O	O	0	0
6	GHIAL	S-ORG	O	1	12
7	is	O	O	0	0
8	progressively	O	O	0	0
9	working	O	O	0	0
10	towards	O	O	0	0
11	making	O	O	0	0
12	Hyderabad	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
13	as	O	O	0	0
14	a	O	O	0	0
15	strong	O	O	0	0
16	cargo	O	O	0	0
17	hub	O	O	0	0
18	,	O	O	0	0
19	"	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	operator	O	O	0	0
22	said	O	O	0	0
23	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	It	O	O	0	0
3	has	O	O	0	0
4	been	O	O	0	0
5	the	O	O	0	0
6	airport	O	S-TERM	0	0
7	's	O	O	0	0
8	continuous	O	O	0	0
9	endeavour	O	O	0	0
10	to	O	O	0	0
11	create	O	O	0	0
12	requisite	O	O	0	0
13	infrastructure	O	O	0	0
14	facilities	O	O	0	0
15	to	O	O	0	0
16	rally	O	O	0	0
17	towards	O	O	0	0
18	this	O	O	0	0
19	goal	O	O	0	0
20	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	Growing	O	O	0	0
3	at	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	pace	O	O	0	0
6	of	O	O	0	0
7	double	O	O	0	0
8	digit	O	O	0	0
9	cargo	O	O	0	0
10	growth	O	O	0	0
11	historically	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	Hyderabad	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
14	International	I-FAC	E-TERM	0	0
15	Airport	E-FAC	O	0	0
16	has	O	O	0	0
17	been	O	O	0	0
18	taking	O	O	0	0
19	steps	O	O	0	0
20	towards	O	O	0	0
21	expanding	O	O	0	0
22	the	O	O	0	0
23	existing	O	O	0	0
24	facilities	O	O	0	0
25	,	O	O	0	0
26	adding	O	O	0	0
27	new	O	O	0	0
28	infrastructure	O	O	0	0
29	,	O	O	0	0
30	transhipment	O	O	0	0
31	facilities	O	O	0	0
32	,	O	O	0	0
33	integrated	O	O	0	0
34	express	O	O	0	0
35	terminal	O	O	0	0
36	,	O	O	0	0
37	dedicated	O	O	0	0
38	perishable	O	O	0	0
39	facilities	O	O	0	0
40	,	O	O	0	0
41	pack	O	O	0	0
42	houses	O	O	0	0
43	and	O	O	0	0
44	a	O	O	0	0
45	strong	O	O	0	0
46	network	O	O	0	0
47	–	O	O	0	0
48	international	O	O	0	0
49	and	O	O	0	0
50	domestic	O	O	0	0
51	(	O	O	0	0
52	air	O	O	0	0
53	and	O	O	0	0
54	road	O	O	0	0
55	)	O	O	0	0
56	,	O	O	0	0
57	multimodal	O	O	0	0
58	connectivity	O	O	0	0
59	and	O	O	0	0
60	ease	O	O	0	0
61	of	O	O	0	0
62	operations	O	O	0	0
63	in	O	O	0	0
64	the	O	O	0	0
65	air	O	O	0	0
66	cargo	O	O	0	0
67	terminals	O	O	0	0
68	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	GMR	B-ORG	O	0	0
3	Group	E-ORG	O	1	7
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	with	O	O	0	0
6	its	O	O	0	0
7	Hyderabad	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	10
8	and	O	O	0	0
9	Delhi	B-ORG	O	0	0
10	Airports	E-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
11	,	O	O	0	0
12	is	O	O	0	0
13	working	O	O	0	0
14	towards	O	O	0	0
15	contributing	O	O	0	0
16	to	O	O	0	0
17	the	O	O	0	0
18	country	O	O	0	0
19	's	O	O	0	0
20	vision	O	O	0	0
21	of	O	O	0	0
22	becoming	O	O	0	0
23	[	O	O	0	0
24	one	S-CARDINAL	O	1	29
25	of	O	O	0	0
26	]	O	O	0	0
27	the	O	O	0	0
28	top	O	O	0	0
29	five	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
30	airfreight	O	O	0	0
31	markets	O	O	0	0
32	by	O	O	0	0
33	2025	S-DATE	O	0	0
34	.	O	O	0	0
35	"	O	O	0	0

1	DHL	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	9
2	to	O	O	0	0
3	ramp	O	O	0	0
4	up	O	O	0	0
5	technology	O	O	0	0
6	deployment	O	O	0	0
7	in	O	O	0	0
8	North	B-LOC	B-TERM	0	0
9	America	E-LOC	E-TERM	0	0
10	to	O	O	0	0
11	meet	O	O	0	0
12	the	O	O	0	0
13	need	O	O	0	0
14	for	O	O	0	0
15	speed	O	S-TERM	0	0

1	DHL	B-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
2	Supply	I-ORG	O	0	0
3	Chain	E-ORG	S-TERM	1	6
4	will	O	O	0	0
5	invest	O	O	0	0
6	$300m	S-MONEY	O	1	14
7	in	O	O	0	0
8	deploying	O	O	0	0
9	new	O	O	0	0
10	technology	O	O	0	0
11	and	O	O	0	0
12	transportation	O	B-TERM	0	0
13	control	O	I-TERM	0	0
14	towers	O	E-TERM	1	16
15	in	O	O	0	0
16	350	S-CARDINAL	O	1	19
17	of	O	O	0	0
18	its	O	O	0	0
19	430	S-CARDINAL	B-TERM	1	21
20	North	B-NORP	I-TERM	0	0
21	American	E-NORP	I-TERM	0	0
22	facilities	O	E-TERM	0	0
23	as	O	O	0	0
24	it	O	O	0	0
25	looks	O	O	0	0
26	to	O	O	0	0
27	improve	O	O	0	0
28	productivity	O	O	0	0
29	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	logistics	O	O	0	0
3	giant	O	O	0	0
4	said	O	O	0	0
5	that	O	O	0	0
6	deployment	O	O	0	0
7	of	O	O	0	0
8	the	O	O	0	0
9	technologies	O	S-TERM	0	0
10	,	O	O	0	0
11	such	O	O	0	0
12	as	O	O	0	0
13	robotics	O	O	0	0
14	,	O	O	0	0
15	augmented	O	O	0	0
16	reality	O	O	0	0
17	,	O	O	0	0
18	robotics	O	O	0	0
19	process	O	O	0	0
20	automation	O	O	0	0
21	,	O	O	0	0
22	IoT	S-ORG	O	0	24
23	and	O	O	0	0
24	DHL	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
25	's	O	O	0	0
26	proprietary	O	O	0	0
27	end-to-end	O	O	0	0
28	visibility	O	O	0	0
29	solution	O	O	0	0
30	–	O	O	0	0
31	MySupplyChain	O	O	0	0
32	-	O	O	0	0
33	,	O	O	0	0
34	will	O	O	0	0
35	vary	O	O	0	0
36	by	O	O	0	0
37	customer	O	O	0	0
38	needs	O	O	0	0
39	,	O	O	0	0
40	based	O	O	0	0
41	on	O	O	0	0
42	the	O	O	0	0
43	outcomes	O	O	0	0
44	of	O	O	0	0
45	research	O	O	0	0
46	and	O	O	0	0
47	pilot	O	O	0	0
48	programmes	O	O	0	0
49	.	O	O	0	0

1	In	O	O	0	0
2	certain	O	O	0	0
3	cases	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	technologies	O	S-TERM	1	13
6	have	O	O	0	0
7	produced	O	O	0	0
8	productivity	O	O	0	0
9	gains	O	O	0	0
10	upwards	O	O	0	0
11	of	O	O	0	0
12	25	B-PERCENT	O	0	0
13	%	E-PERCENT	O	1	20
14	and	O	O	0	0
15	throughput	O	O	0	0
16	capacity	O	O	0	0
17	gains	O	O	0	0
18	of	O	O	0	0
19	30	B-PERCENT	O	0	0
20	%	E-PERCENT	O	0	0
21	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	availability	O	O	0	0
3	of	O	O	0	0
4	these	O	O	0	0
5	technologies	O	S-TERM	1	10
6	is	O	O	0	0
7	expected	O	O	0	0
8	to	O	O	0	0
9	help	O	O	0	0
10	customers	O	S-TERM	0	0
11	remove	O	O	0	0
12	capacity	O	O	0	0
13	constraints	O	O	0	0
14	,	O	O	0	0
15	and	O	O	0	0
16	maximize	O	O	0	0
17	service	O	O	0	0
18	to	O	O	0	0
19	their	O	O	0	0
20	customers	O	S-TERM	0	0
21	.	O	O	0	0

1	DHL	B-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
2	Supply	I-ORG	O	0	0
3	Chain	I-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
4	North	I-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
5	America	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
6	chief	O	O	0	0
7	executive	O	O	0	0
8	Scott	B-PERSON	O	0	0
9	Sureddin	E-PERSON	O	0	0
10	said	O	O	0	0
11	:	O	O	0	0
12	"	O	O	0	0
13	This	O	O	0	0
14	investment	O	O	0	0
15	is	O	O	0	0
16	about	O	O	0	0
17	a	O	O	0	0
18	holistic	O	O	0	0
19	view	O	O	0	0
20	of	O	O	0	0
21	emerging	O	O	0	0
22	technologies	O	S-TERM	1	26
23	that	O	O	0	0
24	enables	O	O	0	0
25	our	O	O	0	0
26	customers	O	S-TERM	0	0
27	to	O	O	0	0
28	achieve	O	O	0	0
29	their	O	O	0	0
30	growth	O	O	0	0
31	and	O	O	0	0
32	profitability	O	O	0	0
33	goals	O	O	0	0
34	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	Our	O	O	0	0
3	customers	O	S-TERM	0	0
4	'	O	O	0	0
5	needs	O	O	0	0
6	are	O	O	0	0
7	not	O	O	0	0
8	homogenous	O	O	0	0
9	as	O	O	0	0
10	each	O	O	0	0
11	business	O	O	0	0
12	and	O	O	0	0
13	segment	O	O	0	0
14	has	O	O	0	0
15	unique	O	O	0	0
16	challenges	O	O	0	0
17	and	O	O	0	0
18	levels	O	O	0	0
19	of	O	O	0	0
20	maturity	O	O	0	0
21	.	O	O	0	0

1	Therefore	O	O	0	0
2	,	O	O	0	0
3	it	O	O	0	0
4	is	O	O	0	0
5	important	O	O	0	0
6	that	O	O	0	0
7	our	O	O	0	0
8	customers	O	S-TERM	0	0
9	can	O	O	0	0
10	benefit	O	O	0	0
11	from	O	O	0	0
12	our	O	O	0	0
13	experiences	O	O	0	0
14	and	O	O	0	0
15	expertise	O	O	0	0
16	with	O	O	0	0
17	a	O	O	0	0
18	variety	O	O	0	0
19	of	O	O	0	0
20	emerging	O	O	0	0
21	technologies	O	S-TERM	0	0
22	.	O	O	0	0
23	"	O	O	0	0

1	According	O	O	0	0
2	to	O	O	0	0
3	a	O	O	0	0
4	recent	O	O	0	0
5	DHL	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
6	report	O	O	0	0
7	,	O	O	0	0
8	the	O	O	0	0
9	exponential	O	O	0	0
10	growth	O	O	0	0
11	of	O	O	0	0
12	e-commerce	O	O	0	0
13	and	O	O	0	0
14	its	O	O	0	0
15	implications	O	O	0	0
16	on	O	O	0	0
17	service	O	O	0	0
18	was	O	O	0	0
19	identified	O	O	0	0
20	by	O	O	0	0
21	65	B-PERCENT	O	0	0
22	%	E-PERCENT	O	0	0
23	percent	E-PERCENT	O	0	0
24	of	O	O	0	0
25	responding	O	O	0	0
26	companies	O	O	0	0
27	as	O	O	0	0
28	having	O	O	0	0
29	a	O	O	0	0
30	significant	O	O	0	0
31	impact	O	O	0	0
32	on	O	O	0	0
33	their	O	O	0	0
34	supply	O	B-TERM	0	0
35	chain	O	E-TERM	0	0
36	.	O	O	0	0

1	In	O	O	0	0
2	alignment	O	O	0	0
3	with	O	O	0	0
4	this	O	O	0	0
5	trend	O	O	0	0
6	,	O	O	0	0
7	DHL	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	12
8	is	O	O	0	0
9	already	O	O	0	0
10	leveraging	O	O	0	0
11	emerging	O	O	0	0
12	technologies	O	S-TERM	1	15
13	at	O	O	0	0
14	approximately	B-CARDINAL	O	0	0
15	85	E-CARDINAL	O	1	18
16	of	O	O	0	0
17	its	O	O	0	0
18	430	S-CARDINAL	O	1	20
19	North	B-NORP	B-TERM	0	0
20	American	E-NORP	E-TERM	0	0
21	facilitie	O	O	0	0
22	,	O	O	0	0
23	"	O	O	0	0
24	the	O	O	0	0
25	company	O	O	0	0
26	said	O	O	0	0
27	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	While	O	O	0	0
3	many	O	O	0	0
4	technologies	O	S-TERM	0	0
5	are	O	O	0	0
6	already	O	O	0	0
7	in	O	O	0	0
8	active	O	O	0	0
9	deployment	O	O	0	0
10	,	O	O	0	0
11	collaborative	O	O	0	0
12	piece-picking	O	O	0	0
13	robots	O	O	0	0
14	,	O	O	0	0
15	artificial	O	O	0	0
16	intelligence	O	O	0	0
17	applications	O	O	0	0
18	and	O	O	0	0
19	self-driving	O	O	0	0
20	vehicles	O	O	0	0
21	stand	O	O	0	0
22	to	O	O	0	0
23	have	O	O	0	0
24	the	O	O	0	0
25	most	O	O	0	0
26	promise	O	O	0	0
27	today	S-DATE	O	0	0
28	,	O	O	0	0
29	"	O	O	0	0
30	added	O	O	0	0
31	Sureddin	S-PERSON	O	0	0
32	.	O	O	0	0

1	Tim	B-PERSON	O	0	0
2	Sprosty	E-PERSON	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	senior	O	O	0	0
5	vice	O	O	0	0
6	President	O	O	0	0
7	of	O	O	0	0
8	Human	B-ORG	O	0	0
9	Resources	E-ORG	O	1	13
10	at	O	O	0	0
11	DHL	B-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
12	Supply	I-ORG	O	0	0
13	Chain	E-ORG	S-TERM	1	19
14	,	O	O	0	0
15	said	O	O	0	0
16	:	O	O	0	0
17	"	O	O	0	0
18	These	O	O	0	0
19	technologies	O	S-TERM	0	0
20	enhance	O	O	0	0
21	the	O	O	0	0
22	value	O	O	0	0
23	of	O	O	0	0
24	our	O	O	0	0
25	people	O	O	0	0
26	;	O	O	0	0
27	they	O	O	0	0
28	do	O	O	0	0
29	n't	O	O	0	0
30	replace	O	O	0	0
31	them	O	O	0	0
32	.	O	O	0	0

1	Our	O	O	0	0
2	team	O	O	0	0
3	will	O	O	0	0
4	be	O	O	0	0
5	equipped	O	O	0	0
6	with	O	O	0	0
7	the	O	O	0	0
8	most	O	O	0	0
9	advanced	O	O	0	0
10	technologies	O	S-TERM	0	0
11	,	O	O	0	0
12	trained	O	O	0	0
13	on	O	O	0	0
14	emerging	O	O	0	0
15	ones	O	O	0	0
16	and	O	O	0	0
17	retained	O	O	0	0
18	through	O	O	0	0
19	a	O	O	0	0
20	culture	O	O	0	0
21	of	O	O	0	0
22	innovation	O	O	0	0
23	,	O	O	0	0
24	collaboration	O	O	0	0
25	and	O	O	0	0
26	recognition	O	O	0	0
27	.	O	O	0	0

1	We	O	O	0	0
2	believe	O	O	0	0
3	this	O	O	0	0
4	approach	O	O	0	0
5	is	O	O	0	0
6	a	O	O	0	0
7	winning	O	O	0	0
8	strategy	O	O	0	0
9	not	O	O	0	0
10	just	O	O	0	0
11	for	O	O	0	0
12	our	O	O	0	0
13	business	O	O	0	0
14	but	O	O	0	0
15	for	O	O	0	0
16	our	O	O	0	0
17	customers	O	S-TERM	0	0
18	'	O	O	0	0
19	businesses	O	O	0	0
20	as	O	O	0	0
21	well	O	O	0	0
22	.	O	O	0	0
23	"	O	O	0	0

1	Earlier	B-DATE	O	0	0
2	this	I-DATE	O	0	0
3	year	E-DATE	O	0	0
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	DHL	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	12
6	broke	O	O	0	0
7	ground	O	O	0	0
8	on	O	O	0	0
9	its	O	O	0	0
10	Americas	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
11	Innovation	I-FAC	I-TERM	0	0
12	Center	E-FAC	E-TERM	1	17
13	that	O	O	0	0
14	will	O	O	0	0
15	exhibit	O	O	0	0
16	the	O	O	0	0
17	technologies	O	S-TERM	0	0
18	and	O	O	0	0
19	innovations	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	business	O	O	0	0
22	is	O	O	0	0
23	already	O	O	0	0
24	implementing	O	O	0	0
25	across	O	O	0	0
26	the	O	O	0	0
27	region	O	O	0	0
28	.	O	O	0	0

1	Finnair	B-PERSON	B-TERM	0	0
2	Cargo	E-PERSON	E-TERM	0	0
3	launches	O	O	0	0
4	an	O	O	0	0
5	eye	O	O	0	0
6	in	O	O	0	0
7	the	O	O	0	0
8	sky	O	O	0	0
9	–	O	O	0	0
10	and	O	O	0	0
11	on	O	O	0	0
12	the	O	O	0	0
13	ground	O	O	0	0

1	Finnair	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	6
3	has	O	O	0	0
4	introduced	O	O	0	0
5	Cargo	B-PRODUCT	B-TERM	0	0
6	Eye	E-PRODUCT	E-TERM	0	0
7	,	O	O	0	0
8	an	O	O	0	0
9	airfreight	O	O	0	0
10	monitoring	O	O	0	0
11	tool	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	and	O	O	0	0
14	invited	O	O	0	0
15	other	O	O	0	0
16	innovators	O	O	0	0
17	to	O	O	0	0
18	pitch	O	O	0	0
19	for	O	O	0	0
20	solutions	O	O	0	0
21	to	O	O	0	0
22	the	O	O	0	0
23	air	O	B-TERM	0	0
24	cargo	O	I-TERM	0	0
25	industry	O	E-TERM	0	0
26	's	O	O	0	0
27	remaining	O	O	0	0
28	"	O	O	0	0
29	unsolved	O	O	0	0
30	challenges	O	O	0	0
31	"	O	O	0	0
32	.	O	O	0	0

1	Finnair	S-ORG	O	1	6
2	says	O	O	0	0
3	that	O	O	0	0
4	its	O	O	0	0
5	Cargo	B-PRODUCT	B-TERM	0	0
6	Eye	E-PRODUCT	I-TERM	0	0
7	solution	O	E-TERM	0	0
8	integrates	O	O	0	0
9	multiple	O	O	0	0
10	data	O	O	0	0
11	sources	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	transaction	O	O	0	0
14	data	O	O	0	0
15	and	O	O	0	0
16	sensors	O	O	0	0
17	to	O	O	0	0
18	help	O	O	0	0
19	its	O	O	0	0
20	newly	O	O	0	0
21	formed	O	O	0	0
22	Cargo	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
23	Control	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
24	Center	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	30
25	to	O	O	0	0
26	monitor	O	O	0	0
27	and	O	O	0	0
28	steer	O	O	0	0
29	cargo	O	B-TERM	0	0
30	flows	O	E-TERM	0	0
31	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	carrier	O	O	0	0
3	adds	O	O	0	0
4	that	O	O	0	0
5	its	O	O	0	0
6	Cargo	B-PRODUCT	B-TERM	0	0
7	Eye	E-PRODUCT	I-TERM	0	0
8	solution	O	E-TERM	0	0
9	provides	O	O	0	0
10	end-to-end	O	O	0	0
11	visibility	O	O	0	0
12	and	O	O	0	0
13	will	O	O	0	0
14	ultimately	O	O	0	0
15	lead	O	O	0	0
16	to	O	O	0	0
17	more	O	O	0	0
18	comprehensive	O	O	0	0
19	and	O	O	0	0
20	transparent	O	O	0	0
21	real-time	O	O	0	0
22	information	O	O	0	0
23	for	O	O	0	0
24	customers	O	O	0	0
25	,	O	O	0	0
26	helping	O	O	0	0
27	them	O	O	0	0
28	to	O	O	0	0
29	,	O	O	0	0
30	identify	O	O	0	0
31	exceptions	O	O	0	0
32	that	O	O	0	0
33	require	O	O	0	0
34	action	O	O	0	0
35	to	O	O	0	0
36	be	O	O	0	0
37	taken	O	O	0	0
38	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	Cargo	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
3	Eye	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
4	is	O	O	0	0
5	a	O	O	0	0
6	new	O	O	0	0
7	operations	O	O	0	0
8	monitoring	O	O	0	0
9	and	O	O	0	0
10	tracking	O	O	0	0
11	platform	O	O	0	0
12	that	O	O	0	0
13	presents	O	O	0	0
14	live	O	O	0	0
15	,	O	O	0	0
16	relevant	O	O	0	0
17	and	O	O	0	0
18	contextual	O	O	0	0
19	data	O	O	0	0
20	in	O	O	0	0
21	a	O	O	0	0
22	simple	O	O	0	0
23	,	O	O	0	0
24	graphical	O	O	0	0
25	view	O	O	0	0
26	,	O	O	0	0
27	"	O	O	0	0
28	explained	O	O	0	0
29	Kari	B-PERSON	B-TERM	0	0
30	Saarikoski	E-PERSON	E-TERM	0	0
31	,	O	O	0	0
32	Digital	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
33	Transformation	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
34	Lead	I-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
35	for	I-ORG	O	0	0
36	Finnair	I-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
37	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
38	.	O	O	0	0

1	Cargo	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Eye	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	12
3	collects	O	O	0	0
4	live	O	O	0	0
5	data	O	O	0	0
6	from	O	O	0	0
7	across	O	O	0	0
8	all	O	O	0	0
9	of	O	O	0	0
10	Finnair	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
11	Cargo	I-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
12	's	E-ORG	O	0	0
13	information	O	O	0	0
14	and	O	O	0	0
15	tracking	O	O	0	0
16	systems	O	O	0	0
17	–	O	O	0	0
18	the	O	O	0	0
19	global	O	O	0	0
20	position	O	O	0	0
21	of	O	O	0	0
22	aircraft	O	O	0	0
23	,	O	O	0	0
24	flight	O	O	0	0
25	information	O	O	0	0
26	,	O	O	0	0
27	the	O	O	0	0
28	geographic	O	O	0	0
29	location	O	O	0	0
30	of	O	O	0	0
31	all	O	O	0	0
32	cargo	O	B-TERM	0	0
33	ground	O	I-TERM	0	0
34	traffic	O	E-TERM	0	0
35	and	O	O	0	0
36	key	O	O	0	0
37	data	O	O	0	0
38	from	O	O	0	0
39	the	O	O	0	0
40	SkyChain	O	O	0	0
41	–	O	O	0	0
42	and	O	O	0	0
43	renders	O	O	0	0
44	it	O	O	0	0
45	onto	O	O	0	0
46	a	O	O	0	0
47	large	O	O	0	0
48	screen	O	O	0	0
49	in	O	O	0	0
50	Google	B-ORG	O	0	0
51	Maps	E-ORG	O	0	0
52	format	O	O	0	0
53	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	We	O	O	0	0
3	see	O	O	0	0
4	Cargo	B-WORK_OF_ART	B-TERM	0	0
5	Eye	E-WORK_OF_ART	E-TERM	0	0
6	as	O	O	0	0
7	an	O	O	0	0
8	indispensable	O	O	0	0
9	management	O	O	0	0
10	tool	O	O	0	0
11	,	O	O	0	0
12	"	O	O	0	0
13	continued	O	O	0	0
14	Saarikoski	S-PERSON	O	0	0
15	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	For	O	O	0	0
3	example	O	O	0	0
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	the	B-ORG	O	0	0
6	CCC	I-ORG	O	0	0
7	(	I-ORG	O	0	0
8	Cargo	I-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
9	Control	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
10	Center	I-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
11	)	E-ORG	O	1	14
12	in	O	O	0	0
13	the	O	O	0	0
14	COOL	S-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
15	cargo	O	I-TERM	0	0
16	terminal	O	E-TERM	0	0
17	can	O	O	0	0
18	look	O	O	0	0
19	at	O	O	0	0
20	one	O	O	0	0
21	screen	O	O	0	0
22	and	O	O	0	0
23	see	O	O	0	0
24	where	O	O	0	0
25	every	O	O	0	0
26	truck	O	O	0	0
27	and	O	O	0	0
28	plane	O	O	0	0
29	is	O	O	0	0
30	carrying	O	O	0	0
31	seafood	O	O	0	0
32	or	O	O	0	0
33	pharmaceuticals	O	O	0	0
34	,	O	O	0	0
35	get	O	O	0	0
36	updated	O	O	0	0
37	on	O	O	0	0
38	its	O	O	0	0
39	arrival	O	O	0	0
40	and	O	O	0	0
41	connecting	O	O	0	0
42	transport	O	O	0	0
43	,	O	O	0	0
44	monitor	O	O	0	0
45	its	O	O	0	0
46	contents	O	O	0	0
47	and	O	O	0	0
48	temperature	O	O	0	0
49	,	O	O	0	0
50	and	O	O	0	0
51	be	O	O	0	0
52	prepared	O	O	0	0
53	to	O	O	0	0
54	shift	O	O	0	0
55	ground	O	O	0	0
56	resources	O	O	0	0
57	to	O	O	0	0
58	where	O	O	0	0
59	they	O	O	0	0
60	are	O	O	0	0
61	needed	O	O	0	0
62	most	O	O	0	0
63	in	O	O	0	0
64	anticipation	O	O	0	0
65	of	O	O	0	0
66	delivery	O	O	0	0
67	.	O	O	0	0
68	"	O	O	0	0

1	Cargo	B-PRODUCT	B-TERM	0	0
2	Eye	E-PRODUCT	E-TERM	1	6
3	was	O	O	0	0
4	presented	O	O	0	0
5	in	O	O	0	0
6	Helsinki	S-GPE	O	1	9
7	at	O	O	0	0
8	the	O	O	0	0
9	Slush	S-GPE	O	0	0
10	event	O	O	0	0
11	for	O	O	0	0
12	start-ups	O	O	0	0
13	across	O	O	0	0
14	all	O	O	0	0
15	industries	O	O	0	0
16	.	O	O	0	0

1	Finnair	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Cargo	I-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
3	's	E-ORG	O	0	0
4	managing	O	O	0	0
5	director	O	O	0	0
6	,	O	O	0	0
7	Janne	B-PERSON	O	0	0
8	Tarvainen	E-PERSON	O	0	0
9	,	O	O	0	0
10	observed	O	O	0	0
11	:	O	O	0	0
12	"	O	O	0	0
13	We	O	O	0	0
14	are	O	O	0	0
15	happy	O	O	0	0
16	to	O	O	0	0
17	present	O	O	0	0
18	Cargo	B-PRODUCT	B-TERM	0	0
19	Eye	E-PRODUCT	E-TERM	1	21
20	at	O	O	0	0
21	Slush	S-GPE	O	0	0
22	,	O	O	0	0
23	and	O	O	0	0
24	invite	O	O	0	0
25	start-ups	O	O	0	0
26	to	O	O	0	0
27	innovate	O	O	0	0
28	with	O	O	0	0
29	us	O	O	0	0
30	for	O	O	0	0
31	improved	O	O	0	0
32	productivity	O	O	0	0
33	and	O	O	0	0
34	establishing	O	O	0	0
35	fully	O	O	0	0
36	transparent	O	O	0	0
37	E2E	O	O	0	0
38	value	O	O	0	0
39	chains	O	O	0	0
40	for	O	O	0	0
41	proactive	O	O	0	0
42	cargo	O	O	0	0
43	network	O	O	0	0
44	steering	O	O	0	0
45	.	O	O	0	0
46	"	O	O	0	0

1	Swissport	S-GPE	S-TERM	1	6
2	lays	O	O	0	0
3	foundations	O	O	0	0
4	for	O	O	0	0
5	Frankfurt	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
6	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	0	0
7	hub	O	O	0	0

1	Fraport	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	6
2	and	O	O	0	0
3	Swissport	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
4	Cargo	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
5	Services	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
6	Deutschland	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	15
7	have	O	O	0	0
8	laid	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	foundation	O	O	0	0
11	stone	O	O	0	0
12	for	O	O	0	0
13	the	O	O	0	0
14	cargo	O	B-TERM	0	0
15	handler	O	E-TERM	1	21
16	's	O	O	0	0
17	new	O	O	0	0
18	facility	O	O	0	0
19	at	O	O	0	0
20	Frankfurt	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
21	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	0	0
22	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	new	O	O	0	0
3	building	O	O	0	0
4	in	O	O	0	0
5	CargoCity	B-GPE	B-TERM	0	0
6	South	E-GPE	E-TERM	1	9
7	will	O	O	0	0
8	expand	O	O	0	0
9	Swissport	S-GPE	S-TERM	1	16
10	's	O	O	0	0
11	handling	O	O	0	0
12	capacity	O	O	0	0
13	by	O	O	0	0
14	almost	B-PERCENT	O	0	0
15	50	I-PERCENT	O	0	0
16	%	E-PERCENT	O	0	0
17	and	O	O	0	0
18	meet	O	O	0	0
19	requirements	O	O	0	0
20	for	O	O	0	0
21	state-of-the-art	O	O	0	0
22	airfreight	O	O	0	0
23	handling	O	O	0	0
24	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	cargo	O	O	0	0
3	centre	O	O	0	0
4	will	O	O	0	0
5	be	O	O	0	0
6	fitted	O	O	0	0
7	out	O	O	0	0
8	in	O	O	0	0
9	accordance	O	O	0	0
10	with	O	O	0	0
11	strict	O	O	0	0
12	IATA	S-ORG	O	1	18
13	criteria	O	O	0	0
14	and	O	O	0	0
15	will	O	O	0	0
16	be	O	O	0	0
17	CEIV	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
18	Pharma	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
19	certified	O	O	0	0
20	after	O	O	0	0
21	going	O	O	0	0
22	into	O	O	0	0
23	operation	O	O	0	0
24	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	roof	O	O	0	0
3	will	O	O	0	0
4	have	O	O	0	0
5	the	O	O	0	0
6	first	S-ORDINAL	O	1	12
7	large-scale	O	O	0	0
8	photovoltaic	O	O	0	0
9	system	O	O	0	0
10	at	O	O	0	0
11	Frankfurt	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
12	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	1	18
13	,	O	O	0	0
14	generating	O	O	0	0
15	1.5	B-QUANTITY	O	0	0
16	million	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
17	kilowatt	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
18	hours	E-QUANTITY	O	0	0
19	of	O	O	0	0
20	electricity	O	O	0	0
21	a	O	O	0	0
22	year	O	O	0	0
23	.	O	O	0	0

1	Felix	B-PERSON	O	0	0
2	Kreutel	E-PERSON	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	senior	O	O	0	0
5	vice	O	O	0	0
6	president	O	O	0	0
7	of	O	O	0	0
8	real	O	O	0	0
9	estate	O	O	0	0
10	and	O	O	0	0
11	properties	O	O	0	0
12	at	O	O	0	0
13	Fraport	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	19
14	says	O	O	0	0
15	:	O	O	0	0
16	"	O	O	0	0
17	Fraport	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
18	operates	O	O	0	0
19	Europe	S-LOC	S-TERM	1	26
20	's	O	O	0	0
21	largest	O	O	0	0
22	cargo	O	O	0	0
23	hub	O	O	0	0
24	at	O	O	0	0
25	Frankfurt	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
26	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	0	0
27	.	O	O	0	0

1	We	O	O	0	0
2	intend	O	O	0	0
3	to	O	O	0	0
4	write	O	O	0	0
5	another	O	O	0	0
6	chapter	O	O	0	0
7	in	O	O	0	0
8	this	O	O	0	0
9	success	O	O	0	0
10	story	O	O	0	0
11	together	O	O	0	0
12	with	O	O	0	0
13	our	O	O	0	0
14	long-standing	O	O	0	0
15	customer	O	O	0	0
16	Swissport	S-PERSON	S-TERM	0	0
17	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	building	O	O	0	0
3	will	O	O	0	0
4	handle	O	O	0	0
5	up	B-QUANTITY	O	0	0
6	to	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
7	200,000	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
8	tonnes	E-QUANTITY	O	1	18
9	of	O	O	0	0
10	airfreight	O	O	0	0
11	a	O	O	0	0
12	year	O	O	0	0
13	,	O	O	0	0
14	with	O	O	0	0
15	Willy	B-PERSON	O	0	0
16	Ruf	E-PERSON	O	0	0
17	,	O	O	0	0
18	Swissport	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	23
19	's	O	O	0	0
20	senior	O	B-TERM	0	0
21	vice	O	I-TERM	0	0
22	president	O	I-TERM	0	0
23	Central	S-ORG	E-TERM	0	26
24	and	O	O	0	0
25	Eastern	B-LOC	B-TERM	0	0
26	Europe	E-LOC	E-TERM	0	0
27	commenting	O	O	0	0
28	:	O	O	0	0
29	"	O	O	0	0
30	We	O	O	0	0
31	are	O	O	0	0
32	looking	O	O	0	0
33	forward	O	O	0	0
34	to	O	O	0	0
35	offering	O	O	0	0
36	our	O	O	0	0
37	customers	O	O	0	0
38	individual	O	O	0	0
39	air	O	O	0	0
40	cargo	O	O	0	0
41	services	O	O	0	0
42	at	O	O	0	0
43	one	O	O	0	0
44	of	O	O	0	0
45	Europe	S-LOC	S-TERM	0	0
46	's	O	O	0	0
47	most	O	O	0	0
48	modern	O	O	0	0
49	and	O	O	0	0
50	sustainable	O	O	0	0
51	airfreight	O	O	0	0
52	facilities	O	O	0	0
53	starting	O	O	0	0
54	in	O	O	0	0
55	the	B-DATE	O	0	0
56	autumn	I-DATE	O	0	0
57	of	I-DATE	O	0	0
58	2020	E-DATE	O	0	0
59	.	O	O	0	0

1	Frankfurt	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
2	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	0	0
3	thus	O	O	0	0
4	remains	O	O	0	0
5	one	O	O	0	0
6	of	O	O	0	0
7	the	O	O	0	0
8	most	O	O	0	0
9	important	O	O	0	0
10	airfreight	O	O	0	0
11	locations	O	O	0	0
12	in	O	O	0	0
13	our	O	O	0	0
14	global	O	O	0	0
15	Swissport	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
16	network	O	O	0	0
17	.	O	O	0	0
18	"	O	O	0	0

1	DHL	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	3
2	and	O	O	0	0
3	Gavi	S-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
4	form	O	I-TERM	0	0
5	vaccine	O	I-TERM	0	0
6	delivery	O	I-TERM	0	0
7	alliance	O	E-TERM	0	0

1	Deutsche	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Post	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
3	DHL	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
4	Group	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	7
5	(	O	O	0	0
6	DP-DHLG	B-ORG	O	0	0
7	)	E-ORG	O	1	12
8	is	O	O	0	0
9	teaming	O	O	0	0
10	up	O	O	0	0
11	with	O	O	0	0
12	Gavi	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	16
13	,	O	O	0	0
14	the	B-ORG	O	0	0
15	Vaccine	I-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
16	Alliance	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	26
17	,	O	O	0	0
18	in	O	O	0	0
19	a	O	O	0	0
20	global	O	O	0	0
21	partnership	O	O	0	0
22	to	O	O	0	0
23	improve	O	O	0	0
24	vaccine	O	B-TERM	0	0
25	supply	O	I-TERM	0	0
26	chains	O	E-TERM	0	0
27	.	O	O	0	0

1	Over	O	O	0	0
2	the	B-DATE	O	0	0
3	next	I-DATE	O	0	0
4	three	I-DATE	O	0	0
5	years	E-DATE	O	0	0
6	,	O	O	0	0
7	the	O	O	0	0
8	Germany-based	S-GPE	B-TERM	0	0
9	global	O	I-TERM	0	0
10	logistics	O	I-TERM	0	0
11	giant	O	E-TERM	0	0
12	will	O	O	0	0
13	provide	O	O	0	0
14	Gavi-supported	O	B-TERM	0	0
15	countries	O	E-TERM	0	0
16	with	O	O	0	0
17	efficient	O	O	0	0
18	supply	O	O	0	0
19	chain	O	O	0	0
20	solutions	O	O	0	0
21	to	O	O	0	0
22	improve	O	O	0	0
23	health	O	O	0	0
24	care	O	O	0	0
25	delivery	O	O	0	0
26	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	With	O	O	0	0
3	vaccine	O	O	0	0
4	volumes	O	O	0	0
5	continuing	O	O	0	0
6	to	O	O	0	0
7	increase	O	O	0	0
8	and	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	persistence	O	O	0	0
11	of	O	O	0	0
12	often	O	O	0	0
13	weak	O	O	0	0
14	or	O	O	0	0
15	broken	O	O	0	0
16	health	O	O	0	0
17	systems	O	O	0	0
18	,	O	O	0	0
19	there	O	O	0	0
20	is	O	O	0	0
21	a	O	O	0	0
22	critical	O	O	0	0
23	need	O	O	0	0
24	for	O	O	0	0
25	improvements	O	O	0	0
26	in	O	O	0	0
27	immunisation	O	B-TERM	0	0
28	supply	O	I-TERM	0	0
29	chain	O	I-TERM	0	0
30	infrastructure	O	E-TERM	0	0
31	.	O	O	0	0
32	"	O	O	0	0

1	This	O	O	0	0
2	is	O	O	0	0
3	not	O	O	0	0
4	Gavi	S-PERSON	S-TERM	0	0
5	's	O	O	0	0
6	first	S-ORDINAL	O	0	0
7	such	O	O	0	0
8	alliance	O	O	0	0
9	.	O	O	0	0

1	While	O	O	0	0
2	the	O	O	0	0
3	service	O	O	0	0
4	is	O	O	0	0
5	focused	O	O	0	0
6	initially	O	O	0	0
7	on	O	O	0	0
8	the	O	O	0	0
9	transfer	O	O	0	0
10	of	O	O	0	0
11	blood	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	a	O	O	0	0
14	partnership	O	O	0	0
15	between	O	O	0	0
16	US-based	O	O	0	0
17	express	O	O	0	0
18	firm	O	O	0	0
19	UPS	S-ORG	O	0	21
20	,	O	O	0	0
21	Gavi	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	23
22	and	O	O	0	0
23	Californian	S-NORP	O	1	25
24	firm	O	O	0	0
25	Zipline	S-ORG	O	0	0
26	will	O	O	0	0
27	help	O	O	0	0
28	expand	O	O	0	0
29	it	O	O	0	0
30	to	O	O	0	0
31	other	O	O	0	0
32	types	O	O	0	0
33	of	O	O	0	0
34	medicines	O	O	0	0
35	and	O	O	0	0
36	vaccines	O	O	0	0
37	.	O	O	0	0

1	In	O	O	0	0
2	this	O	O	0	0
3	new	O	O	0	0
4	alliance	O	O	0	0
5	,	O	O	0	0
6	DP-DHLG	S-ORG	O	0	8
7	and	O	O	0	0
8	Gavi	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
9	aim	O	O	0	0
10	to	O	O	0	0
11	increase	O	O	0	0
12	immunisation	O	O	0	0
13	coverage	O	O	0	0
14	,	O	O	0	0
15	reduce	O	O	0	0
16	vaccine	O	O	0	0
17	wastage	O	O	0	0
18	and	O	O	0	0
19	better	O	O	0	0
20	ensure	O	O	0	0
21	vaccine	O	O	0	0
22	availability	O	O	0	0
23	and	O	O	0	0
24	potency	O	O	0	0
25	and	O	O	0	0
26	will	O	O	0	0
27	ultimately	O	O	0	0
28	help	O	O	0	0
29	reduce	O	O	0	0
30	child	O	O	0	0
31	mortality	O	O	0	0
32	.	O	O	0	0

1	Kenya	S-GPE	O	1	3
2	is	O	O	0	0
3	one	S-CARDINAL	O	1	6
4	of	O	O	0	0
5	the	O	O	0	0
6	first	S-ORDINAL	O	0	0
7	countries	O	O	0	0
8	to	O	O	0	0
9	benefit	O	O	0	0
10	from	O	O	0	0
11	the	O	O	0	0
12	new	O	O	0	0
13	partnership	O	O	0	0
14	,	O	O	0	0
15	announcing	O	O	0	0
16	an	O	O	0	0
17	initiative	O	O	0	0
18	with	O	O	0	0
19	DHL	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	25
20	,	O	O	0	0
21	the	O	O	0	0
22	logistics	O	O	0	0
23	unit	O	O	0	0
24	of	O	O	0	0
25	DP-DHLG	S-ORG	O	0	0
26	.	O	O	0	0

1	Together	O	O	0	0
2	Gavi	S-PERSON	S-TERM	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	DHL	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	10
5	and	O	O	0	0
6	the	B-ORG	O	0	0
7	Kenyan	I-ORG	O	0	0
8	Ministry	I-ORG	O	0	0
9	of	I-ORG	O	0	0
10	Health	E-ORG	O	0	0
11	will	O	O	0	0
12	test	O	O	0	0
13	a	O	O	0	0
14	dedicated	O	O	0	0
15	transportation	O	O	0	0
16	management	O	O	0	0
17	solution	O	O	0	0
18	for	O	O	0	0
19	the	O	O	0	0
20	efficient	O	O	0	0
21	distribution	O	O	0	0
22	of	O	O	0	0
23	vaccines	O	O	0	0
24	throughout	O	O	0	0
25	the	O	O	0	0
26	East	B-NORP	O	0	0
27	African	E-NORP	O	0	0
28	country	O	O	0	0
29	.	O	O	0	0

1	Incorporating	O	O	0	0
2	a	O	O	0	0
3	control	O	O	0	0
4	tower	O	O	0	0
5	called	O	O	0	0
6	a	B-ORG	O	0	0
7	Transport	I-ORG	O	0	0
8	Support	I-ORG	O	0	0
9	Hub	E-ORG	O	0	0
10	,	O	O	0	0
11	to	O	O	0	0
12	better	O	O	0	0
13	manage	O	O	0	0
14	and	O	O	0	0
15	coordinate	O	O	0	0
16	third-party	O	O	0	0
17	transport	O	O	0	0
18	carriers	O	O	0	0
19	and	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	use	O	O	0	0
22	of	O	O	0	0
23	DHL	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
24	's	O	O	0	0
25	own	O	O	0	0
26	global	O	O	0	0
27	transportation	O	O	0	0
28	network	O	O	0	0
29	,	O	O	0	0
30	the	O	O	0	0
31	solution	O	O	0	0
32	aims	O	O	0	0
33	to	O	O	0	0
34	improve	O	O	0	0
35	the	O	O	0	0
36	speed	O	O	0	0
37	and	O	O	0	0
38	reliability	O	O	0	0
39	of	O	O	0	0
40	vaccine	O	O	0	0
41	deliveries	O	O	0	0
42	to	O	O	0	0
43	hospitals	O	O	0	0
44	,	O	O	0	0
45	clinics	O	O	0	0
46	and	O	O	0	0
47	medical	O	O	0	0
48	professionals	O	O	0	0
49	in	O	O	0	0
50	the	O	O	0	0
51	country	O	O	0	0
52	.	O	O	0	0

1	Frank	B-PERSON	O	0	0
2	Appel	E-PERSON	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	chief	O	O	0	0
5	executive	O	O	0	0
6	of	O	O	0	0
7	Deutsche	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
8	Post	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
9	DHL	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
10	Group	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	10
11	,	O	O	0	0
12	said	O	O	0	0
13	:	O	O	0	0
14	"	O	O	0	0
15	This	O	O	0	0
16	enhanced	O	O	0	0
17	relationship	O	O	0	0
18	will	O	O	0	0
19	allow	O	O	0	0
20	Deutsche	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
21	Post	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
22	DHL	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
23	Group	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
24	to	O	O	0	0
25	contribute	O	O	0	0
26	its	O	O	0	0
27	world	O	O	0	0
28	class	O	O	0	0
29	supply	O	O	0	0
30	chain	O	O	0	0
31	expertise	O	O	0	0
32	and	O	O	0	0
33	network	O	O	0	0
34	towards	O	O	0	0
35	making	O	O	0	0
36	a	O	O	0	0
37	real	O	O	0	0
38	difference	O	O	0	0
39	to	O	O	0	0
40	vaccine	O	O	0	0
41	distribution	O	O	0	0
42	in	O	O	0	0
43	the	O	O	0	0
44	developing	O	O	0	0
45	world	O	O	0	0
46	–	O	O	0	0
47	and	O	O	0	0
48	,	O	O	0	0
49	with	O	O	0	0
50	this	O	O	0	0
51	,	O	O	0	0
52	to	O	O	0	0
53	improve	O	O	0	0
54	lives	O	O	0	0
55	.	O	O	0	0
56	"	O	O	0	0

1	Dr	O	O	0	0
2	Seth	B-PERSON	O	0	0
3	Berkley	E-PERSON	O	0	0
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	chief	O	O	0	0
6	executive	O	O	0	0
7	of	O	O	0	0
8	Gavi	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	16
9	,	O	O	0	0
10	said	O	O	0	0
11	:	O	O	0	0
12	"	O	O	0	0
13	Robust	O	B-TERM	0	0
14	vaccine	O	I-TERM	0	0
15	supply	O	I-TERM	0	0
16	chains	O	E-TERM	0	0
17	are	O	O	0	0
18	a	O	O	0	0
19	vital	O	O	0	0
20	part	O	O	0	0
21	of	O	O	0	0
22	building	O	O	0	0
23	strong	O	O	0	0
24	health	O	O	0	0
25	systems	O	O	0	0
26	,	O	O	0	0
27	so	O	O	0	0
28	that	O	O	0	0
29	children	O	O	0	0
30	,	O	O	0	0
31	parents	O	O	0	0
32	,	O	O	0	0
33	and	O	O	0	0
34	communities	O	O	0	0
35	can	O	O	0	0
36	be	O	O	0	0
37	reached	O	O	0	0
38	wherever	O	O	0	0
39	they	O	O	0	0
40	live	O	O	0	0
41	with	O	O	0	0
42	life-saving	O	O	0	0
43	vaccines	O	O	0	0
44	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	DHL	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	13
3	's	O	O	0	0
4	expertise	O	O	0	0
5	in	O	O	0	0
6	healthcare	O	O	0	0
7	delivery	O	O	0	0
8	and	O	O	0	0
9	its	O	O	0	0
10	footprint	O	O	0	0
11	in	O	O	0	0
12	sub-Saharan	B-LOC	O	0	0
13	Africa	E-LOC	O	0	0
14	will	O	O	0	0
15	help	O	O	0	0
16	the	O	O	0	0
17	partnership	O	O	0	0
18	develop	O	O	0	0
19	and	O	O	0	0
20	test	O	O	0	0
21	new	O	O	0	0
22	innovative	O	O	0	0
23	solutions	O	O	0	0
24	aimed	O	O	0	0
25	at	O	O	0	0
26	increasing	O	O	0	0
27	the	O	O	0	0
28	health	O	O	0	0
29	impact	O	O	0	0
30	in	O	O	0	0
31	Gavi-supported	S-NORP	B-TERM	0	0
32	countries	O	E-TERM	0	0
33	.	O	O	0	0
34	"	O	O	0	0

1	This	O	O	0	0
2	project	O	O	0	0
3	aligns	O	O	0	0
4	directly	O	O	0	0
5	with	O	O	0	0
6	Gavi	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
7	's	O	O	0	0
8	private	O	O	0	0
9	sector	O	O	0	0
10	engagement	O	O	0	0
11	strategy	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	which	O	O	0	0
14	seeks	O	O	0	0
15	to	O	O	0	0
16	build	O	O	0	0
17	a	O	O	0	0
18	cluster	O	O	0	0
19	of	O	O	0	0
20	a	O	O	0	0
21	private	O	O	0	0
22	sector	O	O	0	0
23	partners	O	O	0	0
24	to	O	O	0	0
25	address	O	O	0	0
26	critical	O	O	0	0
27	bottlenecks	O	O	0	0
28	to	O	O	0	0
29	immunisation	O	O	0	0
30	coverage	O	O	0	0
31	and	O	O	0	0
32	equity	O	O	0	0
33	in	O	O	0	0
34	Gavi-supported	S-NORP	B-TERM	0	0
35	countries	O	E-TERM	0	0
36	.	O	O	0	0

1	Liege	S-ORG	O	1	3
2	selects	O	O	0	0
3	Nallian	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	6
4	for	O	O	0	0
5	Air	B-PRODUCT	B-TERM	0	0
6	Cargo	E-PRODUCT	I-TERM	0	0
7	open	O	I-TERM	0	0
8	data	O	E-TERM	0	0
9	sharing	O	O	0	0
10	platform	O	S-TERM	0	0

1	Liege	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
2	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	1	7
3	is	O	O	0	0
4	to	O	O	0	0
5	employ	O	O	0	0
6	the	O	O	0	0
7	Nallian	S-PRODUCT	S-TERM	1	10
8	for	O	O	0	0
9	Air	B-PRODUCT	B-TERM	0	0
10	Cargo	E-PRODUCT	I-TERM	1	15
11	suite	O	E-TERM	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	a	O	O	0	0
14	data-sharing	O	O	0	0
15	platform	O	S-TERM	1	22
16	topped	O	O	0	0
17	by	O	O	0	0
18	a	O	O	0	0
19	set	O	O	0	0
20	of	O	O	0	0
21	collaborative	O	B-TERM	0	0
22	applications	O	E-TERM	0	0
23	.	O	O	0	0

1	It	O	O	0	0
2	will	O	O	0	0
3	empower	O	O	0	0
4	Liege	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
5	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	0	0
6	and	O	O	0	0
7	its	O	O	0	0
8	cargo	O	O	0	0
9	stakeholders	O	O	0	0
10	to	O	O	0	0
11	operate	O	O	0	0
12	in	O	O	0	0
13	an	O	O	0	0
14	integrated	O	O	0	0
15	way	O	O	0	0
16	that	O	O	0	0
17	generates	O	O	0	0
18	business	O	O	0	0
19	benefits	O	O	0	0
20	.	O	O	0	0

1	A	O	O	0	0
2	data	O	O	0	0
3	lake	O	O	0	0
4	will	O	O	0	0
5	allow	O	O	0	0
6	the	O	O	0	0
7	airport	O	S-TERM	0	0
8	to	O	O	0	0
9	further	O	O	0	0
10	maximize	O	O	0	0
11	the	O	O	0	0
12	value	O	O	0	0
13	of	O	O	0	0
14	this	O	O	0	0
15	shared	O	O	0	0
16	data	O	O	0	0
17	,	O	O	0	0
18	enabling	O	O	0	0
19	in-depth	O	O	0	0
20	analysis	O	O	0	0
21	that	O	O	0	0
22	helps	O	O	0	0
23	them	O	O	0	0
24	to	O	O	0	0
25	better	O	O	0	0
26	understand	O	O	0	0
27	their	O	O	0	0
28	cargo	O	B-TERM	0	0
29	streams	O	E-TERM	0	0
30	and	O	O	0	0
31	make	O	O	0	0
32	informed	O	O	0	0
33	decisions	O	O	0	0
34	.	O	O	0	0

1	With	O	O	0	0
2	an	O	O	0	0
3	annual	O	O	0	0
4	volume	O	O	0	0
5	of	O	O	0	0
6	more	B-QUANTITY	O	0	0
7	than	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
8	700.000	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
9	tonnes	E-QUANTITY	O	0	12
10	,	O	O	0	0
11	Liege	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
12	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	1	17
13	is	O	O	0	0
14	launching	O	O	0	0
15	a	O	O	0	0
16	cloud-based	O	O	0	0
17	platform	O	S-TERM	0	0
18	that	O	O	0	0
19	enables	O	O	0	0
20	its	O	O	0	0
21	stakeholders	O	O	0	0
22	to	O	O	0	0
23	operate	O	O	0	0
24	in	O	O	0	0
25	a	O	O	0	0
26	more	O	O	0	0
27	collaborative	O	O	0	0
28	,	O	O	0	0
29	integrated	O	O	0	0
30	way	O	O	0	0
31	.	O	O	0	0

1	Using	O	O	0	0
2	Nallian	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	7
3	's	O	O	0	0
4	open	O	O	0	0
5	data	O	O	0	0
6	sharing	O	O	0	0
7	platform	O	S-TERM	0	0
8	,	O	O	0	0
9	information	O	O	0	0
10	that	O	O	0	0
11	is	O	O	0	0
12	uploaded	O	O	0	0
13	once	O	O	0	0
14	can	O	O	0	0
15	be	O	O	0	0
16	shared	O	O	0	0
17	in	O	O	0	0
18	a	O	O	0	0
19	secured	O	O	0	0
20	,	O	O	0	0
21	controlled	O	O	0	0
22	way	O	O	0	0
23	with	O	O	0	0
24	other	O	O	0	0
25	parties	O	O	0	0
26	.	O	O	0	0

1	A	O	O	0	0
2	set	O	O	0	0
3	of	O	O	0	0
4	collaborative	O	B-TERM	0	0
5	applications	O	E-TERM	0	0
6	enables	O	O	0	0
7	to	O	O	0	0
8	capture	O	O	0	0
9	and	O	O	0	0
10	share	O	O	0	0
11	this	O	O	0	0
12	single	O	O	0	0
13	version	O	O	0	0
14	of	O	O	0	0
15	the	O	O	0	0
16	truth	O	O	0	0
17	in	O	O	0	0
18	a	O	O	0	0
19	wide	O	O	0	0
20	range	O	O	0	0
21	of	O	O	0	0
22	processes	O	O	0	0
23	.	O	O	0	0

1	Liege	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
2	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	1	7
3	is	O	O	0	0
4	starting	O	O	0	0
5	off	O	O	0	0
6	with	O	O	0	0
7	6	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
8	applications	O	O	0	0
9	:	O	O	0	0
10	slot	O	O	0	0
11	booking	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	export	O	O	0	0
14	VAT	O	O	0	0
15	recovery	O	O	0	0
16	,	O	O	0	0
17	freight	O	O	0	0
18	consolidation	O	O	0	0
19	,	O	O	0	0
20	e-commerce	O	O	0	0
21	declaration	O	O	0	0
22	,	O	O	0	0
23	cargo	O	O	0	0
24	performance	O	O	0	0
25	monitoring	O	O	0	0
26	,	O	O	0	0
27	and	O	O	0	0
28	track	O	O	0	0
29	&	O	O	0	0
30	trace	O	O	0	0
31	.	O	O	0	0

1	A	O	O	0	0
2	data	O	O	0	0
3	lake	O	O	0	0
4	will	O	O	0	0
5	be	O	O	0	0
6	fueled	O	O	0	0
7	with	O	O	0	0
8	information	O	O	0	0
9	from	O	O	0	0
10	these	O	O	0	0
11	applications	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	allowing	O	O	0	0
14	the	O	O	0	0
15	airport	O	S-TERM	0	0
16	to	O	O	0	0
17	,	O	O	0	0
18	amongst	O	O	0	0
19	others	O	O	0	0
20	,	O	O	0	0
21	analyze	O	O	0	0
22	freight	O	O	0	0
23	routes	O	O	0	0
24	in	O	O	0	0
25	much	O	O	0	0
26	more	O	O	0	0
27	detail	O	O	0	0
28	,	O	O	0	0
29	using	O	O	0	0
30	a	O	O	0	0
31	set	O	O	0	0
32	of	O	O	0	0
33	parameters	O	O	0	0
34	such	O	O	0	0
35	as	O	O	0	0
36	freight	O	O	0	0
37	origin	O	O	0	0
38	or	O	O	0	0
39	final	O	O	0	0
40	destination	O	O	0	0
41	,	O	O	0	0
42	commodities	O	O	0	0
43	,	O	O	0	0
44	airline	O	O	0	0
45	,	O	O	0	0
46	transport	O	O	0	0
47	mode	O	O	0	0
48	etc	O	O	0	0
49	.	O	O	0	0

1	Gaining	O	O	0	0
2	better	O	O	0	0
3	insights	O	O	0	0
4	in	O	O	0	0
5	its	O	O	0	0
6	cargo	O	B-TERM	0	0
7	streams	O	E-TERM	1	11
8	will	O	O	0	0
9	allow	O	O	0	0
10	the	O	O	0	0
11	airport	O	S-TERM	0	0
12	to	O	O	0	0
13	make	O	O	0	0
14	strategic	O	O	0	0
15	decisions	O	O	0	0
16	based	O	O	0	0
17	on	O	O	0	0
18	real-world	O	O	0	0
19	information	O	O	0	0
20	.	O	O	0	0

1	Liege	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Airport	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
3	vp	O	O	0	0
4	air	O	O	0	0
5	services	O	O	0	0
6	Franz	B-PERSON	O	0	0
7	Heuckeroth	E-PERSON	O	0	0
8	Van	B-PERSON	O	0	0
9	Hessen	E-PERSON	O	0	0
10	says	O	O	0	0
11	:	O	O	0	0
12	"	O	O	0	0
13	Nallian	S-GPE	S-TERM	1	22
14	's	O	O	0	0
15	unique	O	O	0	0
16	approach	O	O	0	0
17	of	O	O	0	0
18	an	O	O	0	0
19	open	O	O	0	0
20	data	O	O	0	0
21	sharing	O	O	0	0
22	platform	O	S-TERM	1	25
23	empowering	O	O	0	0
24	collaborative	O	B-TERM	0	0
25	applications	O	E-TERM	0	0
26	gives	O	O	0	0
27	our	O	O	0	0
28	business	O	O	0	0
29	the	O	O	0	0
30	agility	O	O	0	0
31	it	O	O	0	0
32	needs	O	O	0	0
33	to	O	O	0	0
34	remain	O	O	0	0
35	ahead	O	O	0	0
36	of	O	O	0	0
37	the	O	O	0	0
38	game	O	O	0	0
39	,	O	O	0	0
40	today	S-DATE	O	0	0
41	and	O	O	0	0
42	tomorrow	S-DATE	O	0	0
43	.	O	O	0	0

1	We	O	O	0	0
2	have	O	O	0	0
3	been	O	O	0	0
4	impressed	O	O	0	0
5	by	O	O	0	0
6	the	O	O	0	0
7	proven	O	O	0	0
8	performance	O	O	0	0
9	of	O	O	0	0
10	the	O	O	0	0
11	platform	O	S-TERM	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	and	O	O	0	0
14	are	O	O	0	0
15	convinced	O	O	0	0
16	it	O	O	0	0
17	will	O	O	0	0
18	generate	O	O	0	0
19	significant	O	O	0	0
20	value	O	O	0	0
21	for	O	O	0	0
22	the	O	O	0	0
23	airport	O	S-TERM	0	0
24	and	O	O	0	0
25	our	O	O	0	0
26	stakeholders	O	O	0	0
27	.	O	O	0	0
28	"	O	O	0	0

1	Nallian	S-ORG	B-TERM	1	9
2	CEO	O	I-TERM	0	0
3	Jean	B-PERSON	I-TERM	0	0
4	Verheyen	E-PERSON	E-TERM	0	0
5	says	O	O	0	0
6	:	O	O	0	0
7	"	O	O	0	0
8	Liege	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
9	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	1	17
10	is	O	O	0	0
11	a	O	O	0	0
12	pioneer	O	O	0	0
13	in	O	O	0	0
14	the	O	O	0	0
15	air	O	B-TERM	0	0
16	cargo	O	I-TERM	0	0
17	industry	O	E-TERM	0	0
18	and	O	O	0	0
19	we	O	O	0	0
20	are	O	O	0	0
21	proud	O	O	0	0
22	to	O	O	0	0
23	support	O	O	0	0
24	them	O	O	0	0
25	in	O	O	0	0
26	their	O	O	0	0
27	ambition	O	O	0	0
28	to	O	O	0	0
29	take	O	O	0	0
30	their	O	O	0	0
31	business	O	O	0	0
32	and	O	O	0	0
33	the	O	O	0	0
34	air	O	O	0	0
35	cargo	O	O	0	0
36	sector	O	O	0	0
37	to	O	O	0	0
38	the	O	O	0	0
39	next	O	O	0	0
40	level	O	O	0	0
41	.	O	O	0	0

1	Our	O	O	0	0
2	Nallian	B-PRODUCT	S-TERM	0	0
3	for	I-PRODUCT	O	0	0
4	Air	I-PRODUCT	B-TERM	0	0
5	Cargo	I-PRODUCT	I-TERM	0	0
6	Suite	E-PRODUCT	E-TERM	1	5
7	has	O	O	0	0
8	been	O	O	0	0
9	developed	O	O	0	0
10	for	O	O	0	0
11	and	O	O	0	0
12	by	O	O	0	0
13	Air	B-ORG	O	0	0
14	Cargo	E-ORG	O	0	0
15	leaders	O	O	0	0
16	like	O	O	0	0
17	them	O	O	0	0
18	,	O	O	0	0
19	so	O	O	0	0
20	we	O	O	0	0
21	are	O	O	0	0
22	pleased	O	O	0	0
23	to	O	O	0	0
24	be	O	O	0	0
25	able	O	O	0	0
26	to	O	O	0	0
27	support	O	O	0	0
28	their	O	O	0	0
29	long-term	O	O	0	0
30	vision	O	O	0	0
31	with	O	O	0	0
32	a	O	O	0	0
33	platform	O	S-TERM	0	0
34	that	O	O	0	0
35	is	O	O	0	0
36	tuned	O	O	0	0
37	to	O	O	0	0
38	their	O	O	0	0
39	reality	O	O	0	0
40	.	O	O	0	0
41	"	O	O	0	0

1	American	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Airlines	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
3	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	8
4	opens	O	O	0	0
5	new	O	O	0	0
6	,	O	O	0	0
7	expanded	O	O	0	0
8	London	S-GPE	B-TERM	0	0
9	pharma	O	I-TERM	0	0
10	room	O	E-TERM	0	0

1	As	O	O	0	0
2	part	O	O	0	0
3	of	O	O	0	0
4	American	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
5	's	O	O	0	0
6	commitment	O	O	0	0
7	to	O	O	0	0
8	support	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	expansion	O	O	0	0
11	of	O	O	0	0
12	its	O	O	0	0
13	healthcare	O	O	0	0
14	and	O	O	0	0
15	pharmaceutical	O	O	0	0
16	services	O	O	0	0
17	,	O	O	0	0
18	American	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
19	Airlines	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
20	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	32
21	has	O	O	0	0
22	announced	O	O	0	0
23	the	O	O	0	0
24	opening	O	O	0	0
25	of	O	O	0	0
26	a	O	O	0	0
27	new	O	B-TERM	0	0
28	Controlled	B-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
29	Room	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
30	Temperature	I-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
31	(	I-ORG	O	0	0
32	CRT	E-ORG	O	1	37
33	)	O	O	0	0
34	facility	O	O	0	0
35	at	O	O	0	0
36	its	O	O	0	0
37	London	S-GPE	B-TERM	1	38
38	Heathrow	S-GPE	E-TERM	1	40
39	(	O	O	0	0
40	LHR	S-GPE	S-TERM	1	43
41	)	O	O	0	0
42	cargo	O	B-TERM	0	0
43	center	O	E-TERM	0	0
44	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	new	O	B-TERM	0	0
3	room	O	E-TERM	1	7
4	is	O	O	0	0
5	1,700	B-QUANTITY	O	0	0
6	square	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
7	feet	E-QUANTITY	O	1	12
8	(	O	O	0	0
9	160	B-QUANTITY	O	0	0
10	square	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
11	meters	I-QUANTITY	O	0	0
12	)	E-QUANTITY	O	1	18
13	and	O	O	0	0
14	can	O	O	0	0
15	accommodate	O	O	0	0
16	up	O	O	0	0
17	to	O	O	0	0
18	16	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
19	times	O	O	0	0
20	more	O	O	0	0
21	standard	O	O	0	0
22	euro	O	O	0	0
23	skid	O	O	0	0
24	pallets	O	O	0	0
25	at	O	O	0	0
26	one	O	O	0	0
27	time	O	O	0	0
28	than	O	O	0	0
29	the	O	O	0	0
30	previous	O	O	0	0
31	room	O	O	0	0
32	.	O	O	0	0

1	Thus	O	O	0	0
2	it	O	O	0	0
3	is	O	O	0	0
4	providing	O	O	0	0
5	airline	O	O	0	0
6	customers	O	O	0	0
7	with	O	O	0	0
8	greater	O	O	0	0
9	capacity	O	O	0	0
10	when	O	O	0	0
11	it	O	O	0	0
12	comes	O	O	0	0
13	to	O	O	0	0
14	moving	O	O	0	0
15	temperature-sensitive	O	O	0	0
16	healthcare	O	O	0	0
17	freight	O	O	0	0
18	to	O	O	0	0
19	and	O	O	0	0
20	from	O	O	0	0
21	LHR	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
22	.	O	O	0	0

1	Both	O	O	0	0
2	inbound	O	O	0	0
3	and	O	O	0	0
4	outbound	O	O	0	0
5	logistics	O	O	0	0
6	companies	O	O	0	0
7	supporting	O	O	0	0
8	American	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	10
9	's	O	O	0	0
10	ExpediteTC	S-ORG	O	0	0
11	service	O	O	0	0
12	will	O	O	0	0
13	utilize	O	O	0	0
14	the	O	O	0	0
15	new	O	B-TERM	0	0
16	CRT	O	I-TERM	0	0
17	room	O	E-TERM	0	0
18	.	O	O	0	0

1	Euro	B-ORG	O	0	0
2	Scan	E-ORG	O	0	0
3	software	O	O	0	0
4	is	O	O	0	0
5	used	O	O	0	0
6	to	O	O	0	0
7	monitor	O	O	0	0
8	precise	O	O	0	0
9	temperatures	O	O	0	0
10	within	O	O	0	0
11	the	O	O	0	0
12	facility	O	O	0	0
13	,	O	O	0	0
14	which	O	O	0	0
15	will	O	O	0	0
16	provide	O	O	0	0
17	real-time	O	O	0	0
18	information	O	O	0	0
19	to	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	American	S-NORP	S-TERM	0	0
22	operations	O	O	0	0
23	team	O	O	0	0
24	,	O	O	0	0
25	and	O	O	0	0
26	will	O	O	0	0
27	be	O	O	0	0
28	used	O	O	0	0
29	for	O	O	0	0
30	reporting	O	O	0	0
31	purposes	O	O	0	0
32	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	newly	O	O	0	0
3	enlarged	O	O	0	0
4	CRT	O	B-TERM	0	0
5	room	O	E-TERM	0	0
6	will	O	O	0	0
7	be	O	O	0	0
8	of	O	O	0	0
9	significant	O	O	0	0
10	value	O	O	0	0
11	to	O	O	0	0
12	customers	O	O	0	0
13	moving	O	O	0	0
14	specialist	O	O	0	0
15	pharma	O	O	0	0
16	traffic	O	O	0	0
17	between	O	O	0	0
18	Europe	S-LOC	O	1	21
19	and	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	US	S-GPE	O	0	0
22	.	O	O	0	0

1	As	O	O	0	0
2	the	O	O	0	0
3	second	S-ORDINAL	O	1	7
4	largest	O	O	0	0
5	carrier	O	O	0	0
6	from	O	O	0	0
7	LHR	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	31
8	across	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	Atlantic	S-LOC	O	0	12
11	,	O	O	0	0
12	American	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	43
13	offers	O	O	0	0
14	up	B-CARDINAL	O	0	0
15	to	I-CARDINAL	O	0	0
16	20	E-CARDINAL	O	1	22
17	daily	S-DATE	O	0	0
18	departures	O	O	0	0
19	to	O	O	0	0
20	the	B-GPE	O	0	0
21	United	I-GPE	O	0	0
22	States	E-GPE	O	1	25
23	,	O	O	0	0
24	including	O	O	0	0
25	two	S-CARDINAL	O	1	7
26	daily	S-DATE	O	0	0
27	flights	O	O	0	0
28	between	O	O	0	0
29	LHR	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
30	and	O	O	0	0
31	Philadelphia	S-GPE	O	1	33
32	(	O	O	0	0
33	PHL	S-GPE	O	1	12
34	)	O	O	0	0
35	,	O	O	0	0
36	home	O	O	0	0
37	to	O	O	0	0
38	American	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
39	's	O	O	0	0
40	industry	O	O	0	0
41	leading	O	O	0	0
42	25,000	B-QUANTITY	O	0	0
43	square-foot	E-QUANTITY	O	0	0
44	pharmaceutical	O	O	0	0
45	facility	O	O	0	0
46	.	O	O	0	0

1	Lufthansa	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	7
3	processes	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	world	O	O	0	0
6	's	O	O	0	0
7	first	S-ORDINAL	O	1	10
8	electronic	O	O	0	0
9	dangerous	O	B-TERM	0	0
10	goods	O	I-TERM	0	0
11	declaration	O	E-TERM	0	0

1	Lufthansa	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	8
3	has	O	O	0	0
4	handled	O	O	0	0
5	the	O	O	0	0
6	world	O	O	0	0
7	's	O	O	0	0
8	first	S-ORDINAL	O	1	12
9	electronic	O	O	0	0
10	Dangerous	B-PRODUCT	B-TERM	0	0
11	Goods	I-PRODUCT	I-TERM	0	0
12	Declaration	E-PRODUCT	E-TERM	1	14
13	(	O	O	0	0
14	eDGD	S-PRODUCT	O	1	18
15	)	O	O	0	0
16	shipment	O	O	0	0
17	using	O	O	0	0
18	Dakosy	S-ORG	O	1	20
19	's	O	O	0	0
20	INFr8	S-PRODUCT	B-TERM	0	0
21	shipping	O	I-TERM	0	0
22	portal	O	E-TERM	0	0
23	.	O	O	0	0

1	A	O	O	0	0
2	shipment	O	O	0	0
3	from	O	O	0	0
4	healthcare	O	O	0	0
5	company	O	O	0	0
6	Abbott	S-ORG	O	1	9
7	based	O	O	0	0
8	in	O	O	0	0
9	Wiesbaden	S-GPE	O	1	18
10	was	O	O	0	0
11	flown	O	O	0	0
12	on	O	O	0	0
13	board	O	B-TERM	0	0
14	cargo	O	I-TERM	0	0
15	flight	O	I-TERM	0	0
16	LH8222	O	E-TERM	0	0
17	from	O	O	0	0
18	Frankfurt	S-GPE	O	1	21
19	to	O	O	0	0
20	Mexico	B-GPE	O	0	0
21	City	E-GPE	O	0	0
22	last	B-DATE	O	0	0
23	Thursday	E-DATE	O	0	0
24	.	O	O	0	0

1	Lufthansa	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	6
2	said	O	O	0	0
3	that	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	dangerous	O	B-TERM	0	0
6	goods	O	I-TERM	0	0
7	process	O	E-TERM	0	0
8	has	O	O	0	0
9	traditionally	O	O	0	0
10	been	O	O	0	0
11	paper-based	O	O	0	0
12	due	O	O	0	0
13	to	O	O	0	0
14	the	O	O	0	0
15	lack	O	O	0	0
16	of	O	O	0	0
17	digital	O	O	0	0
18	standards	O	O	0	0
19	.	O	O	0	0

1	Dangerous	O	B-TERM	0	0
2	Goods	O	I-TERM	0	0
3	Declarations	O	E-TERM	0	0
4	on	O	O	0	0
5	paper	O	O	0	0
6	from	O	O	0	0
7	shippers	O	O	0	0
8	arrive	O	O	0	0
9	at	O	O	0	0
10	the	O	O	0	0
11	airport	O	O	0	0
12	with	O	O	0	0
13	the	O	O	0	0
14	respective	O	O	0	0
15	goods	O	O	0	0
16	and	O	O	0	0
17	airlines	O	O	0	0
18	can	O	O	0	0
19	begin	O	O	0	0
20	checking	O	O	0	0
21	the	O	O	0	0
22	documentation	O	O	0	0
23	only	O	O	0	0
24	after	O	O	0	0
25	handover	O	O	0	0
26	.	O	O	0	0

1	It	O	O	0	0
2	will	O	O	0	0
3	also	O	O	0	0
4	mean	O	O	0	0
5	faster	O	O	0	0
6	processes	O	O	0	0
7	and	O	O	0	0
8	better	O	O	0	0
9	use	O	O	0	0
10	of	O	O	0	0
11	resources	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	Lufthansa	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
14	said	O	O	0	0
15	.	O	O	0	0

1	Lufthansa	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	6
3	worked	O	O	0	0
4	closely	O	O	0	0
5	with	O	O	0	0
6	IATA	S-ORG	O	1	6
7	to	O	O	0	0
8	establish	O	O	0	0
9	a	O	O	0	0
10	global	O	O	0	0
11	eDGD	O	O	0	0
12	standard	O	O	0	0
13	as	O	O	0	0
14	part	O	O	0	0
15	of	O	O	0	0
16	IATA	S-ORG	O	0	0
17	's	O	O	0	0
18	e-freight	O	O	0	0
19	initiative	O	O	0	0
20	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	A	O	O	0	0
3	completely	O	O	0	0
4	new	O	O	0	0
5	approach	O	O	0	0
6	has	O	O	0	0
7	been	O	O	0	0
8	developed	O	O	0	0
9	and	O	O	0	0
10	evaluated	O	O	0	0
11	through	O	O	0	0
12	close	O	O	0	0
13	collaboration	O	O	0	0
14	all	O	O	0	0
15	along	O	O	0	0
16	the	O	O	0	0
17	transport	O	O	0	0
18	chain	O	O	0	0
19	with	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	Infr8	S-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
22	eDGD	O	I-TERM	0	0
23	platform	O	E-TERM	0	0
24	,	O	O	0	0
25	"	O	O	0	0
26	the	O	O	0	0
27	airline	O	O	0	0
28	said	O	O	0	0
29	.	O	O	0	0

1	Lufthansa	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Cargo	I-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
3	's	E-ORG	O	1	14
4	IT	O	O	0	0
5	systems	O	O	0	0
6	and	O	O	0	0
7	processes	O	O	0	0
8	can	O	O	0	0
9	now	O	O	0	0
10	deal	O	O	0	0
11	with	O	O	0	0
12	paperless	O	B-TERM	0	0
13	dangerous	O	I-TERM	0	0
14	goods	O	I-TERM	1	21
15	shipments	O	E-TERM	0	0
16	,	O	O	0	0
17	making	O	O	0	0
18	the	O	O	0	0
19	airline	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	first	S-ORDINAL	O	1	30
22	and	O	O	0	0
23	so	O	O	0	0
24	far	O	O	0	0
25	only	O	O	0	0
26	airline	O	O	0	0
27	to	O	O	0	0
28	support	O	O	0	0
29	the	O	O	0	0
30	eDGD	S-ORG	O	0	0
31	standard	O	O	0	0
32	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	We	O	O	0	0
3	are	O	O	0	0
4	pleased	O	O	0	0
5	that	O	O	0	0
6	the	O	O	0	0
7	eDGD	S-ORG	O	1	15
8	has	O	O	0	0
9	celebrated	O	O	0	0
10	its	O	O	0	0
11	global	O	O	0	0
12	launch	O	O	0	0
13	with	O	O	0	0
14	Lufthansa	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
15	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
16	.	O	O	0	0

1	There	O	O	0	0
2	is	O	O	0	0
3	still	O	O	0	0
4	so	O	O	0	0
5	much	O	O	0	0
6	more	O	O	0	0
7	for	O	O	0	0
8	us	O	O	0	0
9	to	O	O	0	0
10	achieve	O	O	0	0
11	here	O	O	0	0
12	together	O	O	0	0
13	with	O	O	0	0
14	shippers	O	O	0	0
15	,	O	O	0	0
16	forwarders	O	O	0	0
17	and	O	O	0	0
18	airports	O	O	0	0
19	,	O	O	0	0
20	"	O	O	0	0
21	said	O	O	0	0
22	Sören	B-PERSON	O	0	0
23	Stark	E-PERSON	O	0	0
24	,	O	O	0	0
25	board	O	O	0	0
26	member	O	O	0	0
27	operations	O	O	0	0
28	and	O	O	0	0
29	chief	O	O	0	0
30	operating	O	O	0	0
31	officer	O	O	0	0
32	of	O	O	0	0
33	Lufthansa	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
34	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
35	.	O	O	0	0

1	Hand	O	O	0	0
2	in	O	O	0	0
3	hand	O	O	0	0
4	with	O	O	0	0
5	this	O	O	0	0
6	,	O	O	0	0
7	the	O	O	0	0
8	pilot	O	O	0	0
9	phase	O	O	0	0
10	of	O	O	0	0
11	the	O	O	0	0
12	INFr8	S-PRODUCT	B-TERM	0	0
13	shipping	O	I-TERM	0	0
14	portal	O	E-TERM	0	0
15	has	O	O	0	0
16	been	O	O	0	0
17	successfully	O	O	0	0
18	launched	O	O	0	0
19	.	O	O	0	0

1	All	O	O	0	0
2	pilot	O	O	0	0
3	partners	O	O	0	0
4	are	O	O	0	0
5	digitally	O	O	0	0
6	connected	O	O	0	0
7	to	O	O	0	0
8	the	O	O	0	0
9	platform	O	O	0	0
10	and	O	O	0	0
11	can	O	O	0	0
12	use	O	O	0	0
13	it	O	O	0	0
14	to	O	O	0	0
15	process	O	O	0	0
16	transport	O	O	0	0
17	documents	O	O	0	0
18	–	O	O	0	0
19	including	O	O	0	0
20	the	B-LAW	O	0	0
21	Dangerous	I-LAW	B-TERM	0	0
22	Goods	I-LAW	I-TERM	0	0
23	Declaration	I-LAW	E-TERM	0	0
24	(	I-LAW	O	0	0
25	DGD	I-LAW	O	0	0
26	)	E-LAW	O	0	0
27	required	O	O	0	0
28	by	O	O	0	0
29	law	O	O	0	0
30	.	O	O	0	0

1	Besides	O	O	0	0
2	Lufthansa	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
3	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	forwarder	O	O	0	0
6	Panalpina	S-PERSON	O	0	0
7	has	O	O	0	0
8	also	O	O	0	0
9	been	O	O	0	0
10	a	O	O	0	0
11	key	O	O	0	0
12	partner	O	O	0	0
13	to	O	O	0	0
14	Dakosy	S-ORG	O	0	0
15	.	O	O	0	0

1	Frankfurt	B-FAC	O	0	0
2	Airport	E-FAC	O	1	9
3	plays	O	O	0	0
4	a	O	O	0	0
5	major	O	O	0	0
6	role	O	O	0	0
7	in	O	O	0	0
8	dangerous	O	B-TERM	0	0
9	goods	O	E-TERM	0	0
10	handling	O	O	0	0
11	for	O	O	0	0
12	both	O	O	0	0
13	companies	O	O	0	0
14	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	Thanks	O	O	0	0
3	to	O	O	0	0
4	this	O	O	0	0
5	worldwide	O	O	0	0
6	innovation	O	O	0	0
7	,	O	O	0	0
8	the	O	O	0	0
9	INFr8	S-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
10	platform	O	E-TERM	0	0
11	integrates	O	O	0	0
12	the	O	O	0	0
13	shipper	O	O	0	0
14	into	O	O	0	0
15	the	O	O	0	0
16	electronic	O	O	0	0
17	information	O	O	0	0
18	chain	O	O	0	0
19	of	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	air	O	O	0	0
22	cargo	O	O	0	0
23	process	O	O	0	0
24	for	O	O	0	0
25	the	O	O	0	0
26	first	S-ORDINAL	O	0	0
27	time	O	O	0	0
28	.	O	O	0	0
