1	AirBridgeCargo	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Airlines	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	8
3	inks	O	O	0	0
4	leasing	O	O	0	0
5	agreement	O	O	0	0
6	with	O	O	0	0
7	Sonoco	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
8	ThermoSafe	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	We	O	O	0	0
3	have	O	O	0	0
4	been	O	O	0	0
5	consistently	O	O	0	0
6	developing	O	O	0	0
7	and	O	O	0	0
8	upgrading	O	O	0	0
9	our	O	O	0	0
10	'	O	O	0	0
11	abc	O	S-TERM	0	0
12	pharma	O	O	0	0
13	'	O	O	0	0
14	product	O	O	0	0
15	,	O	O	0	0
16	offering	O	O	0	0
17	our	O	O	0	0
18	customers	O	O	0	0
19	dedicated	O	O	0	0
20	airlift	O	O	0	0
21	for	O	O	0	0
22	both	O	O	0	0
23	passive	O	O	0	0
24	and	O	O	0	0
25	active	O	O	0	0
26	ways	O	O	0	0
27	of	O	O	0	0
28	transportation	O	O	0	0
29	.	O	O	0	0

1	This	O	O	0	0
2	is	O	O	0	0
3	a	O	O	0	0
4	quantum	O	O	0	0
5	leap	O	O	0	0
6	for	O	O	0	0
7	our	O	O	0	0
8	dedicated	O	O	0	0
9	product	O	O	0	0
10	,	O	O	0	0
11	and	O	O	0	0
12	we	O	O	0	0
13	expect	O	O	0	0
14	it	O	O	0	0
15	to	O	O	0	0
16	ramp	O	O	0	0
17	up	O	O	0	0
18	our	O	O	0	0
19	volumes	O	O	0	0
20	,	O	O	0	0
21	as	O	O	0	0
22	well	O	O	0	0
23	as	O	O	0	0
24	to	O	O	0	0
25	gain	O	O	0	0
26	interest	O	O	0	0
27	in	O	O	0	0
28	our	O	O	0	0
29	services	O	O	0	0
30	from	O	O	0	0
31	new	O	O	0	0
32	customers	O	O	0	0
33	,	O	O	0	0
34	"	O	O	0	0
35	highlighted	O	O	0	0
36	Fedor	B-PERSON	O	0	0
37	Novikov	E-PERSON	O	0	0
38	,	O	O	0	0
39	Deputy	O	O	0	0
40	director	O	O	0	0
41	,	O	O	0	0
42	Products	B-ORG	O	0	0
43	of	I-ORG	O	0	0
44	AirBridgeCargo	I-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
45	Airlines	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
46	.	O	O	0	0

1	Christopher	B-PERSON	O	0	0
2	Day	E-PERSON	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	director	O	O	0	0
5	of	O	O	0	0
6	Business	B-ORG	O	0	0
7	Development	I-ORG	O	0	0
8	&	I-ORG	O	0	0
9	Innovation	E-ORG	O	1	12
10	at	O	O	0	0
11	Sonoco	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
12	ThermoSafe	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
13	said	O	O	0	0
14	:	O	O	0	0
15	"	O	O	0	0
16	As	O	O	0	0
17	always	O	O	0	0
18	,	O	O	0	0
19	our	O	O	0	0
20	focus	O	O	0	0
21	is	O	O	0	0
22	to	O	O	0	0
23	make	O	O	0	0
24	it	O	O	0	0
25	as	O	O	0	0
26	easy	O	O	0	0
27	as	O	O	0	0
28	possible	O	O	0	0
29	for	O	O	0	0
30	pharmaceutical	O	O	0	0
31	shippers	O	O	0	0
32	and	O	O	0	0
33	forwarders	O	O	0	0
34	to	O	O	0	0
35	directly	O	O	0	0
36	lease	O	O	0	0
37	PharmaPort	B-MISC	S-TERM	0	0
38	360s	E-MISC	O	0	0
39	from	O	O	0	0
40	the	O	O	0	0
41	leading	O	O	0	0
42	airlines	O	O	0	0
43	around	O	O	0	0
44	the	O	O	0	0
45	globe	O	O	0	0
46	,	O	O	0	0
47	and	O	O	0	0
48	we	O	O	0	0
49	are	O	O	0	0
50	delighted	O	O	0	0
51	to	O	O	0	0
52	partner	O	O	0	0
53	with	O	O	0	0
54	AirBridgeCargo	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
55	Airlines	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
56	to	O	O	0	0
57	do	O	O	0	0
58	so	O	O	0	0
59	.	O	O	0	0
60	"	O	O	0	0

1	For	O	O	0	0
2	the	B-DATE	O	0	0
3	first	I-DATE	O	0	0
4	three	I-DATE	O	0	0
5	months	I-DATE	O	0	0
6	of	I-DATE	O	0	0
7	2019	E-DATE	O	0	0
8	,	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	abc	O	S-TERM	1	20
11	pharma	O	O	0	0
12	team	O	O	0	0
13	managed	O	O	0	0
14	to	O	O	0	0
15	achieve	O	O	0	0
16	a	O	O	0	0
17	more	B-MISC	O	0	0
18	than	I-MISC	O	0	0
19	15	I-MISC	O	0	0
20	percent	E-MISC	O	0	0
21	upsurge	O	O	0	0
22	of	O	O	0	0
23	volumes	O	O	0	0
24	for	O	O	0	0
25	temperature-sensitive	O	O	0	0
26	pharmaceutical	O	O	0	0
27	and	O	O	0	0
28	other	O	O	0	0
29	medical	O	O	0	0
30	products	O	O	0	0
31	.	O	O	0	0

1	DHL	S-ORG	O	0	3
2	and	O	O	0	0
3	United	S-ORG	O	1	10
4	expand	O	O	0	0
5	services	O	O	0	0
6	into	O	O	0	0
7	pharma	O	B-TERM	0	0
8	hub	O	E-TERM	0	0
9	San	B-GPE	O	0	0
10	Juan	E-GPE	S-TERM	0	0

1	United	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Airlines	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	9
3	and	O	O	0	0
4	DHL	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
5	Global	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
6	Forwarding	I-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
7	(	I-ORG	O	0	0
8	DGF	I-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
9	)	E-ORG	O	1	15
10	have	O	O	0	0
11	announced	O	O	0	0
12	growth	O	O	0	0
13	and	O	O	0	0
14	expansion	O	B-TERM	0	0
15	initiatives	O	E-TERM	1	19
16	to	O	O	0	0
17	serve	O	O	0	0
18	San	B-GPE	B-TERM	0	0
19	Juan	E-GPE	E-TERM	1	24
20	,	O	O	0	0
21	the	O	O	0	0
22	burgeoning	O	O	0	0
23	life	O	B-TERM	0	0
24	sciences	O	E-TERM	0	27
25	and	O	O	0	0
26	pharmaceuticals	O	B-TERM	0	0
27	hub	O	E-TERM	0	30
28	in	O	O	0	0
29	Puerto	B-GPE	B-TERM	0	0
30	Rico	E-GPE	E-TERM	0	0
31	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	two	S-CARDINAL	O	1	13
3	companies	O	O	0	0
4	are	O	O	0	0
5	working	O	O	0	0
6	together	O	O	0	0
7	to	O	O	0	0
8	increase	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	number	O	O	0	0
11	of	O	O	0	0
12	widebody	O	B-TERM	0	0
13	flights	O	E-TERM	1	16
14	serving	O	O	0	0
15	San	B-MISC	B-TERM	0	0
16	Juan	E-MISC	E-TERM	0	0
17	and	O	O	0	0
18	to	O	O	0	0
19	offer	O	O	0	0
20	expanded	O	O	0	0
21	cold	O	O	0	0
22	chain	O	O	0	0
23	storage	O	O	0	0
24	solutions	O	O	0	0
25	for	O	O	0	0
26	temperature-controlled	O	O	0	0
27	chambers	O	O	0	0
28	operating	O	O	0	0
29	at	O	O	0	0
30	15	S-CARDINAL	O	1	32
31	to	O	O	0	0
32	25	S-CARDINAL	O	1	36
33	°	O	O	0	0
34	C	O	O	0	0
35	(	O	O	0	0
36	59	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
37	to	O	O	0	0
38	77	O	O	0	0
39	°	O	O	0	0
40	F	O	O	0	0
41	)	O	O	0	0
42	.	O	O	0	0

1	United	S-ORG	O	0	0
2	,	O	O	0	0
3	partly	O	O	0	0
4	to	O	O	0	0
5	serve	O	O	0	0
6	increased	O	O	0	0
7	demand	O	O	0	0
8	for	O	O	0	0
9	temperature-controlled	O	O	0	0
10	shipments	O	O	0	0
11	,	O	O	0	0
12	will	O	O	0	0
13	from	O	O	0	0
14	mid-December	S-DATE	O	0	0
15	increase	O	O	0	0
16	its	O	O	0	0
17	current	O	O	0	0
18	one	S-CARDINAL	O	1	19
19	Boeing	S-ORG	O	1	20
20	777	S-MISC	O	1	25
21	flight	O	O	0	0
22	per	O	O	0	0
23	week	O	O	0	0
24	to	O	O	0	0
25	six	S-CARDINAL	O	0	29
26	between	O	O	0	0
27	San	B-GPE	B-TERM	0	0
28	Juan	I-GPE	E-TERM	0	0
29	's	E-GPE	O	1	33
30	Luis	B-FAC	O	0	0
31	Munoz	I-FAC	O	0	0
32	Marin	I-FAC	O	0	0
33	airport	E-FAC	O	1	39
34	and	O	O	0	0
35	the	O	O	0	0
36	airline	O	O	0	0
37	's	O	O	0	0
38	New	B-GPE	O	0	0
39	York/Newark	E-GPE	O	0	0
40	hub	O	O	0	0
41	.	O	O	0	0

1	According	O	O	0	0
2	to	O	O	0	0
3	the	B-ORG	O	0	0
4	Puerto	I-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
5	Rico	I-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
6	Industrial	I-ORG	O	0	0
7	Development	I-ORG	O	0	0
8	Co	I-ORG	O	0	0
9	(	I-ORG	O	0	0
10	PRIDCO	I-ORG	O	0	0
11	)	E-ORG	O	1	16
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	the	O	O	0	0
14	island	O	O	0	0
15	has	O	O	0	0
16	49	S-CARDINAL	O	1	21
17	US	B-ORG	O	0	0
18	Food	I-ORG	O	0	0
19	and	I-ORG	O	0	0
20	Drug	I-ORG	O	0	0
21	Administration	E-ORG	O	1	27
22	FDA-approved	O	O	0	0
23	pharmaceutical	O	O	0	0
24	plants	O	O	0	0
25	,	O	O	0	0
26	while	O	O	0	0
27	twelve	S-CARDINAL	O	1	31
28	of	O	O	0	0
29	the	O	O	0	0
30	top	O	O	0	0
31	20	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
32	global	O	O	0	0
33	pharmaceutical	O	O	0	0
34	companies	O	O	0	0
35	have	O	O	0	0
36	a	O	O	0	0
37	presence	O	O	0	0
38	there	O	O	0	0
39	.	O	O	0	0

1	It	O	O	0	0
2	also	O	O	0	0
3	is	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	fifth	S-MISC	O	0	0
6	largest	O	O	0	0
7	pharmaceutical	O	O	0	0
8	manufacturing	O	O	0	0
9	territory	O	O	0	0
10	in	O	O	0	0
11	the	O	O	0	0
12	world	O	O	0	0
13	and	O	O	0	0
14	has	O	O	0	0
15	recently	O	O	0	0
16	attracted	O	O	0	0
17	extra	O	O	0	0
18	cargo	O	O	0	0
19	services	O	O	0	0
20	from	O	O	0	0
21	Cargolux	S-ORG	O	0	23
22	,	O	O	0	0
23	CAL	S-ORG	O	0	26
24	,	O	O	0	0
25	American	B-ORG	O	0	0
26	Airlines	E-ORG	O	0	28
27	and	O	O	0	0
28	IAG	S-ORG	O	0	0
29	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	Building	O	O	0	0
3	strong	O	O	0	0
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	collaborative	O	O	0	0
6	relationships	O	O	0	0
7	with	O	O	0	0
8	United	B-ORG	O	0	0
9	Cargo	E-ORG	O	0	0
10	customers	O	O	0	0
11	allows	O	O	0	0
12	us	O	O	0	0
13	to	O	O	0	0
14	share	O	O	0	0
15	innovative	O	O	0	0
16	ideas	O	O	0	0
17	and	O	O	0	0
18	opportunities	O	O	0	0
19	to	O	O	0	0
20	ensure	O	O	0	0
21	we	O	O	0	0
22	meet	O	O	0	0
23	the	O	O	0	0
24	needs	O	O	0	0
25	of	O	O	0	0
26	the	O	O	0	0
27	global	O	O	0	0
28	health	O	O	0	0
29	care	O	O	0	0
30	community	O	O	0	0
31	,	O	O	0	0
32	"	O	O	0	0
33	said	O	O	0	0
34	Jim	B-PERSON	O	0	0
35	Bellinder	E-PERSON	O	0	0
36	,	O	O	0	0
37	United	B-ORG	O	0	0
38	Cargo	I-ORG	O	0	0
39	's	E-ORG	O	0	44
40	vice	O	O	0	0
41	president	O	O	0	0
42	of	O	O	0	0
43	sales	O	O	0	0
44	Americas	S-MISC	O	0	0
45	.	O	O	0	0

1	Brussels	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
2	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	0	6
3	and	O	O	0	0
4	MVD	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
5	Free	I-FAC	I-TERM	0	0
6	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	0	0
7	sign	O	O	0	0
8	MoU	O	O	0	0
9	for	O	O	0	0
10	pharma	O	O	0	0

1	Brussels	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
2	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	0	4
3	and	O	O	0	0
4	Montevideo	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	8
5	's	O	O	0	0
6	MVD	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
7	Free	I-FAC	I-TERM	0	0
8	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	0	0
9	have	O	O	0	0
10	signed	O	O	0	0
11	a	O	O	0	0
12	memorandum	O	O	0	0
13	of	O	O	0	0
14	understanding	O	O	0	0
15	to	O	O	0	0
16	continue	O	O	0	0
17	sharing	O	O	0	0
18	know-how	O	O	0	0
19	and	O	O	0	0
20	best	O	B-TERM	0	0
21	practices	O	E-TERM	1	25
22	to	O	O	0	0
23	develop	O	O	0	0
24	new	O	B-TERM	0	0
25	pharma	O	E-TERM	1	29
26	certified	O	O	0	0
27	lanes	O	O	0	0
28	between	O	O	0	0
29	Europe	S-MISC	O	0	32
30	and	O	O	0	0
31	Latin	B-MISC	B-TERM	0	0
32	America	E-MISC	E-TERM	0	0
33	.	O	O	0	0

1	A	O	O	0	0
2	joint	O	B-TERM	0	0
3	statement	O	E-TERM	0	5
4	from	O	O	0	0
5	Uruguay	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	9
6	's	O	O	0	0
7	MVD	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
8	Free	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
9	Airport	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	13
10	and	O	O	0	0
11	Brussels	B-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
12	Airport	I-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
13	Company	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
14	said	O	O	0	0
15	that	O	O	0	0
16	they	O	O	0	0
17	both	O	O	0	0
18	"	O	O	0	0
19	see	O	O	0	0
20	eye-to-eye	O	O	0	0
21	with	O	O	0	0
22	regards	O	O	0	0
23	to	O	O	0	0
24	the	O	O	0	0
25	challenges	O	O	0	0
26	that	O	O	0	0
27	global	O	O	0	0
28	pharma	O	O	0	0
29	distribution	O	O	0	0
30	is	O	O	0	0
31	facing	O	O	0	0
32	"	O	O	0	0
33	.	O	O	0	0

1	They	O	O	0	0
2	have	O	O	0	0
3	worked	O	O	0	0
4	on	O	O	0	0
5	several	O	O	0	0
6	initiatives	O	O	0	0
7	including	O	O	0	0
8	the	O	O	0	0
9	launching	O	O	0	0
10	of	O	O	0	0
11	a	O	O	0	0
12	GDP	O	O	0	0
13	compliant	O	O	0	0
14	route	O	O	0	0
15	between	O	O	0	0
16	Brussels	S-GPE	O	0	18
17	and	O	O	0	0
18	Montevideo	S-GPE	S-TERM	1	24
19	to	O	O	0	0
20	facilitate	O	O	0	0
21	regional	O	O	0	0
22	distribution	O	O	0	0
23	to	O	O	0	0
24	Brazil	S-GPE	O	0	26
25	,	O	O	0	0
26	Argentina	S-GPE	O	1	32
27	and	O	O	0	0
28	the	O	O	0	0
29	rest	O	O	0	0
30	of	O	O	0	0
31	South	B-MISC	B-TERM	0	0
32	America	E-MISC	E-TERM	1	34
33	via	O	O	0	0
34	Uruguay	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
35	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	We	O	O	0	0
3	've	O	O	0	0
4	felt	O	O	0	0
5	identified	O	O	0	0
6	with	O	O	0	0
7	what	O	O	0	0
8	Brussels	B-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
9	Airport	I-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
10	Company	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
11	has	O	O	0	0
12	been	O	O	0	0
13	doing	O	O	0	0
14	for	O	O	0	0
15	quite	O	O	0	0
16	some	O	O	0	0
17	time	O	O	0	0
18	"	O	O	0	0
19	Saidd	B-PERSON	O	0	0
20	Bruno	I-PERSON	O	0	0
21	Guella	E-PERSON	O	0	0
22	,	O	O	0	0
23	managing	O	O	0	0
24	director	O	O	0	0
25	at	O	O	0	0
26	MVD	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
27	Free	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
28	Airport	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
29	,	O	O	0	0
30	adding	O	O	0	0
31	:	O	O	0	0
32	"	O	O	0	0
33	The	O	O	0	0
34	way	O	O	0	0
35	they	O	O	0	0
36	've	O	O	0	0
37	positioned	O	O	0	0
38	themselves	O	O	0	0
39	as	O	O	0	0
40	a	O	O	0	0
41	pharma	O	O	0	0
42	gateway	O	O	0	0
43	with	O	O	0	0
44	state-of-the-art	O	O	0	0
45	infrastructure	O	O	0	0
46	,	O	O	0	0
47	pharma-oriented	O	O	0	0
48	processes	O	O	0	0
49	and	O	O	0	0
50	internal	O	O	0	0
51	quality	O	O	0	0
52	standards	O	O	0	0
53	up	O	O	0	0
54	to	O	O	0	0
55	par	O	O	0	0
56	with	O	O	0	0
57	the	O	O	0	0
58	most	O	O	0	0
59	demanding	O	O	0	0
60	has	O	O	0	0
61	definitely	O	O	0	0
62	helped	O	O	0	0
63	shape	O	O	0	0
64	our	O	O	0	0
65	mission	O	O	0	0
66	and	O	O	0	0
67	vision	O	O	0	0
68	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	We	O	O	0	0
3	are	O	O	0	0
4	happy	O	O	0	0
5	to	O	O	0	0
6	be	O	O	0	0
7	in	O	O	0	0
8	continuous	O	O	0	0
9	collaboration	O	O	0	0
10	with	O	O	0	0
11	Brussels	B-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
12	Airport	I-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
13	Company	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
14	and	O	O	0	0
15	very	O	O	0	0
16	excited	O	O	0	0
17	for	O	O	0	0
18	what	O	O	0	0
19	is	O	O	0	0
20	to	O	O	0	0
21	come	O	O	0	0
22	.	O	O	0	0
23	"	O	O	0	0

1	Nathan	B-PERSON	O	0	0
2	De	I-PERSON	O	0	0
3	Valck	E-PERSON	O	0	0
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	cargo	O	O	0	0
6	development	O	O	0	0
7	manager	O	O	0	0
8	at	O	O	0	0
9	Brussels	B-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
10	Airport	I-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
11	Company	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	said	O	O	0	0
14	:	O	O	0	0
15	"	O	O	0	0
16	It	O	O	0	0
17	is	O	O	0	0
18	great	O	O	0	0
19	to	O	O	0	0
20	see	O	O	0	0
21	companies	O	O	0	0
22	such	O	O	0	0
23	as	O	O	0	0
24	MVD	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
25	Free	I-FAC	I-TERM	0	0
26	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	0	0
27	who	O	O	0	0
28	operate	O	O	0	0
29	in	O	O	0	0
30	very	O	O	0	0
31	challenging	O	O	0	0
32	regional	O	O	0	0
33	contexts	O	O	0	0
34	strive	O	O	0	0
35	for	O	O	0	0
36	greatness	O	O	0	0
37	and	O	O	0	0
38	help	O	O	0	0
39	pave	O	O	0	0
40	the	O	O	0	0
41	way	O	O	0	0
42	for	O	O	0	0
43	a	O	O	0	0
44	safer	O	O	0	0
45	,	O	O	0	0
46	reliable	O	O	0	0
47	and	O	O	0	0
48	standardized	O	O	0	0
49	pharma	O	O	0	0
50	distribution	O	O	0	0
51	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	When	O	O	0	0
3	we	O	O	0	0
4	first	S-MISC	O	0	0
5	started	O	O	0	0
6	exchanging	O	O	0	0
7	ideas	O	O	0	0
8	and	O	O	0	0
9	information	O	O	0	0
10	we	O	O	0	0
11	were	O	O	0	0
12	very	O	O	0	0
13	pleasantly	O	O	0	0
14	surprised	O	O	0	0
15	to	O	O	0	0
16	learn	O	O	0	0
17	we	O	O	0	0
18	were	O	O	0	0
19	speaking	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	same	O	O	0	0
22	language	O	O	0	0
23	and	O	O	0	0
24	that	O	O	0	0
25	a	O	O	0	0
26	lot	O	O	0	0
27	could	O	O	0	0
28	be	O	O	0	0
29	accomplished	O	O	0	0
30	together	O	O	0	0
31	and	O	O	0	0
32	also	O	O	0	0
33	being	O	O	0	0
34	part	O	O	0	0
35	of	O	O	0	0
36	Pharma	S-ORG	O	0	0
37	.	O	O	0	0
38	Aero	O	O	0	0
39	as	O	O	0	0
40	well	O	O	0	0
41	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	Today	S-DATE	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	we	O	O	0	0
5	are	O	O	0	0
6	very	O	O	0	0
7	satisfied	O	O	0	0
8	with	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	road	O	O	0	0
11	we	O	O	0	0
12	've	O	O	0	0
13	travelled	O	O	0	0
14	and	O	O	0	0
15	looking	O	O	0	0
16	forward	O	O	0	0
17	to	O	O	0	0
18	all	O	O	0	0
19	that	O	O	0	0
20	is	O	O	0	0
21	yet	O	O	0	0
22	to	O	O	0	0
23	come	O	O	0	0
24	"	O	O	0	0
25	mentioned	O	O	0	0
26	.	O	O	0	0

1	MVD	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Free	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
3	Airport	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	10
4	is	O	O	0	0
5	a	O	O	0	0
6	business	O	O	0	0
7	unit	O	O	0	0
8	of	O	O	0	0
9	Corporación	B-ORG	O	0	0
10	America	E-ORG	O	0	0
11	,	O	O	0	0
12	the	O	O	0	0
13	largest	O	O	0	0
14	airport	O	O	0	0
15	operator	O	O	0	0
16	in	O	O	0	0
17	the	O	O	0	0
18	world	O	O	0	0
19	with	O	O	0	0
20	a	O	O	0	0
21	network	O	O	0	0
22	of	O	O	0	0
23	over	B-CARDINAL	O	0	0
24	50	E-CARDINAL	O	1	30
25	airports	O	O	0	0
26	and	O	O	0	0
27	cargo	O	O	0	0
28	terminals	O	O	0	0
29	across	O	O	0	0
30	three	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
31	continents	O	O	0	0
32	.	O	O	0	0

1	It	O	O	0	0
2	is	O	O	0	0
3	a	O	O	0	0
4	multimodal	O	O	0	0
5	distribution	O	O	0	0
6	centre	O	O	0	0
7	specialised	O	O	0	0
8	in	O	O	0	0
9	temperature-controlled	O	O	0	0
10	supply	O	O	0	0
11	chain	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	operating	O	O	0	0
14	as	O	O	0	0
15	the	O	O	0	0
16	first	S-MISC	O	1	23
17	and	O	O	0	0
18	only	O	O	0	0
19	free	O	O	0	0
20	airport	O	O	0	0
21	in	O	O	0	0
22	South	B-MISC	B-TERM	0	0
23	America	E-MISC	E-TERM	0	0
24	.	O	O	0	0

1	TIACA	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	4
2	backs	O	O	0	0
3	new	O	B-TERM	0	0
4	initiative	O	E-TERM	0	0
5	encouraging	O	O	0	0
6	leaders	O	O	0	0
7	of	O	O	0	0
8	the	O	O	0	0
9	future	O	O	0	0

1	The	B-ORG	O	0	0
2	International	I-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
3	Air	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
4	Cargo	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
5	Association	I-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
6	(	I-ORG	O	0	0
7	TIACA	I-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
8	)	E-ORG	O	1	13
9	has	O	O	0	0
10	backed	O	O	0	0
11	a	O	O	0	0
12	new	O	B-TERM	0	0
13	initiative	O	E-TERM	1	18
14	encouraging	O	O	0	0
15	new	O	B-TERM	0	0
16	air	O	I-TERM	0	0
17	cargo	O	I-TERM	0	0
18	leaders	O	E-TERM	1	27
19	of	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	future	O	O	0	0
22	and	O	O	0	0
23	collaboration	O	O	0	0
24	in	O	O	0	0
25	the	O	O	0	0
26	supply	O	B-TERM	0	0
27	chain	O	E-TERM	0	0
28	.	O	O	0	0

1	Staff	O	O	0	0
2	from	O	O	0	0
3	companies	O	O	0	0
4	including	O	O	0	0
5	Air	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
6	France	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
7	KLM	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
8	Martinair	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
9	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	14
10	,	O	O	0	0
11	Jan	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
12	De	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
13	Rijk	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
14	Logistics	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	17
15	,	O	O	0	0
16	Tosoh	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
17	Corporation	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	21
18	,	O	O	0	0
19	Valeant	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
20	Pharmaceuticals	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
21	International	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	23
22	,	O	O	0	0
23	Agility	S-ORG	O	1	26
24	,	O	O	0	0
25	and	O	O	0	0
26	Swissport	S-ORG	O	0	0
27	visited	O	O	0	0
28	each	O	O	0	0
29	other	O	O	0	0
30	's	O	O	0	0
31	sites	O	O	0	0
32	to	O	O	0	0
33	gain	O	O	0	0
34	a	O	O	0	0
35	better	O	O	0	0
36	understanding	O	O	0	0
37	of	O	O	0	0
38	processes	O	O	0	0
39	and	O	O	0	0
40	explore	O	O	0	0
41	new	O	O	0	0
42	ways	O	O	0	0
43	of	O	O	0	0
44	collaborating	O	O	0	0
45	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	initiative	O	O	0	0
3	was	O	O	0	0
4	launched	O	O	0	0
5	by	O	O	0	0
6	TIACA	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	14
7	,	O	O	0	0
8	with	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	help	O	O	0	0
11	of	O	O	0	0
12	Air	B-ORG	O	0	0
13	Cargo	I-ORG	O	0	0
14	Netherlands	E-ORG	O	1	20
15	,	O	O	0	0
16	as	O	O	0	0
17	part	O	O	0	0
18	of	O	O	0	0
19	the	O	O	0	0
20	Association	S-ORG	O	0	0
21	's	O	O	0	0
22	commitment	O	O	0	0
23	to	O	O	0	0
24	training	O	O	0	0
25	and	O	O	0	0
26	supporting	O	O	0	0
27	the	O	O	0	0
28	next	O	O	0	0
29	generation	O	O	0	0
30	of	O	O	0	0
31	air	O	O	0	0
32	cargo	O	O	0	0
33	leaders	O	O	0	0
34	.	O	O	0	0

1	TIACA	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	8
2	vice	O	O	0	0
3	chairman	O	O	0	0
4	and	O	O	0	0
5	Jan	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
6	de	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
7	Rijk	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
8	Logistics	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
9	chief	O	O	0	0
10	executive	O	O	0	0
11	officer	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	Sebastiaan	B-PERSON	O	0	0
14	Scholte	E-PERSON	O	0	0
15	says	O	O	0	0
16	:	O	O	0	0
17	"	O	O	0	0
18	This	O	O	0	0
19	initiative	O	O	0	0
20	will	O	O	0	0
21	hopefully	O	O	0	0
22	be	O	O	0	0
23	the	O	O	0	0
24	start	O	O	0	0
25	of	O	O	0	0
26	many	O	O	0	0
27	more	O	O	0	0
28	to	O	O	0	0
29	follow	O	O	0	0
30	,	O	O	0	0
31	where	O	O	0	0
32	we	O	O	0	0
33	can	O	O	0	0
34	develop	O	O	0	0
35	young	O	O	0	0
36	talent	O	O	0	0
37	to	O	O	0	0
38	be	O	O	0	0
39	the	O	O	0	0
40	leaders	O	O	0	0
41	of	O	O	0	0
42	tomorrow	S-DATE	O	0	0
43	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	It	O	O	0	0
3	is	O	O	0	0
4	a	O	O	0	0
5	unique	O	O	0	0
6	program	O	O	0	0
7	as	O	O	0	0
8	it	O	O	0	0
9	involves	O	O	0	0
10	a	O	O	0	0
11	vertical	O	O	0	0
12	integration	O	O	0	0
13	of	O	O	0	0
14	the	O	O	0	0
15	supply	O	B-TERM	0	0
16	chain	O	E-TERM	0	0
17	with	O	O	0	0
18	complete	O	O	0	0
19	openness	O	O	0	0
20	and	O	O	0	0
21	transparency	O	O	0	0
22	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	It	O	O	0	0
3	is	O	O	0	0
4	more	O	O	0	0
5	and	O	O	0	0
6	more	O	O	0	0
7	difficult	O	O	0	0
8	to	O	O	0	0
9	discover	O	O	0	0
10	and	O	O	0	0
11	develop	O	O	0	0
12	talent	O	O	0	0
13	,	O	O	0	0
14	especially	O	O	0	0
15	in	O	O	0	0
16	small	O	O	0	0
17	and	O	O	0	0
18	medium	O	O	0	0
19	sized	O	O	0	0
20	companies	O	O	0	0
21	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	Ideally	O	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	we	O	O	0	0
5	would	O	O	0	0
6	like	O	O	0	0
7	to	O	O	0	0
8	see	O	O	0	0
9	this	O	O	0	0
10	develop	O	O	0	0
11	into	O	O	0	0
12	an	O	O	0	0
13	internship	O	O	0	0
14	scheme	O	O	0	0
15	,	O	O	0	0
16	so	O	O	0	0
17	we	O	O	0	0
18	not	O	O	0	0
19	only	O	O	0	0
20	prepare	O	O	0	0
21	our	O	O	0	0
22	future	O	O	0	0
23	talent	O	O	0	0
24	,	O	O	0	0
25	but	O	O	0	0
26	also	O	O	0	0
27	improve	O	O	0	0
28	cooperation	O	O	0	0
29	in	O	O	0	0
30	the	O	O	0	0
31	supply	O	B-TERM	0	0
32	chain	O	E-TERM	0	0
33	.	O	O	0	0
34	"	O	O	0	0

1	TIACA	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	6
2	's	O	O	0	0
3	Education	B-ORG	O	0	0
4	and	I-ORG	O	0	0
5	Research	I-ORG	O	0	0
6	Committee	E-ORG	O	0	0
7	members	O	O	0	0
8	will	O	O	0	0
9	be	O	O	0	0
10	discussing	O	O	0	0
11	next	O	O	0	0
12	steps	O	O	0	0
13	for	O	O	0	0
14	the	O	O	0	0
15	scheme	O	O	0	0
16	at	O	O	0	0
17	their	O	O	0	0
18	board	O	O	0	0
19	meeting	O	O	0	0
20	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	We	O	O	0	0
3	have	O	O	0	0
4	gained	O	O	0	0
5	understanding	O	O	0	0
6	for	O	O	0	0
7	each	O	O	0	0
8	of	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	partners	O	O	0	0
11	'	O	O	0	0
12	activities	O	O	0	0
13	in	O	O	0	0
14	the	O	O	0	0
15	air	O	B-TERM	0	0
16	cargo	O	E-TERM	0	0
17	supply	O	O	0	0
18	chain	O	S-TERM	1	25
19	,	O	O	0	0
20	"	O	O	0	0
21	says	O	O	0	0
22	Jan	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
23	de	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
24	Rijk	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
25	Logistics	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
26	sales	O	O	0	0
27	manager	O	O	0	0
28	,	O	O	0	0
29	Jeroen	B-PERSON	O	0	0
30	Leemans	E-PERSON	O	0	0
31	,	O	O	0	0
32	who	O	O	0	0
33	participated	O	O	0	0
34	in	O	O	0	0
35	the	O	O	0	0
36	initiative	O	O	0	0
37	last	B-DATE	O	0	0
38	week	E-DATE	O	0	0
39	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	What	O	O	0	0
3	we	O	O	0	0
4	have	O	O	0	0
5	found	O	O	0	0
6	is	O	O	0	0
7	that	O	O	0	0
8	by	O	O	0	0
9	working	O	O	0	0
10	closely	O	O	0	0
11	together	O	O	0	0
12	there	O	O	0	0
13	is	O	O	0	0
14	a	O	O	0	0
15	lot	O	O	0	0
16	to	O	O	0	0
17	gain	O	O	0	0
18	every	O	O	0	0
19	step	O	O	0	0
20	of	O	O	0	0
21	the	O	O	0	0
22	way	O	O	0	0
23	.	O	O	0	0

1	Currently	O	O	0	0
2	we	O	O	0	0
3	optimise	O	O	0	0
4	our	O	O	0	0
5	own	O	O	0	0
6	processes	O	O	0	0
7	and	O	O	0	0
8	we	O	O	0	0
9	do	O	O	0	0
10	a	O	O	0	0
11	good	O	O	0	0
12	job	O	O	0	0
13	,	O	O	0	0
14	but	O	O	0	0
15	issues	O	O	0	0
16	arise	O	O	0	0
17	around	O	O	0	0
18	the	O	O	0	0
19	transfer	O	O	0	0
20	of	O	O	0	0
21	information	O	O	0	0
22	as	O	O	0	0
23	well	O	O	0	0
24	as	O	O	0	0
25	the	O	O	0	0
26	physical	O	O	0	0
27	hand-over	O	O	0	0
28	process	O	O	0	0
29	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	For	O	O	0	0
3	the	O	O	0	0
4	air	O	B-TERM	0	0
5	cargo	O	E-TERM	0	0
6	supply	O	O	0	0
7	chain	O	S-TERM	0	0
8	to	O	O	0	0
9	grow	O	O	0	0
10	,	O	O	0	0
11	we	O	O	0	0
12	need	O	O	0	0
13	to	O	O	0	0
14	understand	O	O	0	0
15	how	O	O	0	0
16	to	O	O	0	0
17	work	O	O	0	0
18	better	O	O	0	0
19	together	O	O	0	0
20	with	O	O	0	0
21	our	O	O	0	0
22	partners	O	O	0	0
23	,	O	O	0	0
24	"	O	O	0	0
25	he	O	O	0	0
26	adds	O	O	0	0
27	.	O	O	0	0

1	TIACA	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	8
2	has	O	O	0	0
3	developed	O	O	0	0
4	a	B-ORG	O	0	0
5	Professional	I-ORG	O	0	0
6	Development	I-ORG	O	0	0
7	Workshop	I-ORG	O	0	0
8	Program	E-ORG	O	0	0
9	aimed	O	O	0	0
10	at	O	O	0	0
11	growing	O	O	0	0
12	management	O	O	0	0
13	skills	O	O	0	0
14	for	O	O	0	0
15	air	O	O	0	0
16	cargo	O	O	0	0
17	professionals	O	O	0	0
18	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	next	O	O	0	0
3	workshop	O	O	0	0
4	takes	O	O	0	0
5	place	O	O	0	0
6	in	O	O	0	0
7	Anchorage	S-GPE	O	0	9
8	,	O	O	0	0
9	Alaska	S-GPE	O	0	0
10	,	O	O	0	0
11	from	O	O	0	0
12	August	B-DATE	O	0	0
13	29	I-DATE	O	0	0
14	to	I-DATE	O	0	0
15	1	I-DATE	O	0	0
16	September	I-DATE	O	0	0
17	,	I-DATE	O	0	0
18	2017	E-DATE	O	0	0
19	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	program	O	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	designed	O	O	0	0
5	by	O	O	0	0
6	Strategic	B-ORG	O	0	0
7	Aviation	I-ORG	O	0	0
8	Solutions	I-ORG	O	0	0
9	International	E-ORG	O	0	11
10	(	O	O	0	0
11	SASI	S-ORG	O	0	0
12	)	O	O	0	0
13	,	O	O	0	0
14	gives	O	O	0	0
15	participants	O	O	0	0
16	an	O	O	0	0
17	appreciation	O	O	0	0
18	of	O	O	0	0
19	the	O	O	0	0
20	entire	O	O	0	0
21	air	O	B-TERM	0	0
22	cargo	O	E-TERM	0	0
23	supply	O	O	0	0
24	chain	O	S-TERM	0	0
25	and	O	O	0	0
26	the	O	O	0	0
27	component	O	O	0	0
28	sectors	O	O	0	0
29	by	O	O	0	0
30	encouraging	O	O	0	0
31	discussion	O	O	0	0
32	and	O	O	0	0
33	the	O	O	0	0
34	sharing	O	O	0	0
35	of	O	O	0	0
36	perspectives	O	O	0	0
37	,	O	O	0	0
38	as	O	O	0	0
39	well	O	O	0	0
40	as	O	O	0	0
41	providing	O	O	0	0
42	practical	O	O	0	0
43	advice	O	O	0	0
44	and	O	O	0	0
45	insight	O	O	0	0
46	.	O	O	0	0

1	BRUcloud	O	S-TERM	0	0
2	app	O	O	1	6
3	smooths	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	export	O	B-TERM	0	0
6	flow	O	E-TERM	1	8
7	at	O	O	0	0
8	Brussels	S-GPE	O	0	0

1	Freight	O	B-TERM	0	0
2	forwarders	O	E-TERM	0	0
3	within	O	O	0	0
4	Brussels	S-GPE	B-TERM	1	7
5	airport	O	E-TERM	0	0
6	's	O	O	0	0
7	BRUcargo	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
8	community	O	O	0	0
9	are	O	O	0	0
10	saving	O	O	0	0
11	air	O	O	0	0
12	waybill	O	O	0	0
13	(	O	O	0	0
14	AWB	O	S-TERM	0	0
15	)	O	O	0	0
16	processing	O	O	0	0
17	time	O	O	0	0
18	by	O	O	0	0
19	accessing	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	new	O	O	0	0
22	Customs	B-ORG	O	0	0
23	Export	I-ORG	O	0	0
24	Application	E-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
25	which	O	O	0	0
26	went	O	O	0	0
27	live	O	O	0	0
28	on	O	O	0	0
29	July	B-DATE	O	0	0
30	1	E-DATE	O	0	0
31	.	O	O	0	0

1	This	O	O	0	0
2	latest	O	O	0	0
3	application	O	S-TERM	0	0
4	is	O	O	0	0
5	one	S-CARDINAL	O	1	11
6	of	O	O	0	0
7	several	O	O	0	0
8	made	O	O	0	0
9	possible	O	O	0	0
10	by	O	O	0	0
11	BRUcloud	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	19
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	the	O	O	0	0
14	open	O	O	0	0
15	community	O	O	0	0
16	platform	O	O	0	0
17	at	O	O	0	0
18	the	O	O	0	0
19	Belgian	S-MISC	O	1	23
20	hub	O	O	0	0
21	based	O	O	0	0
22	on	O	O	0	0
23	Nallian	S-ORG	O	1	30
24	's	O	O	0	0
25	data-sharing	O	O	0	0
26	technology	O	O	0	0
27	and	O	O	0	0
28	initiated	O	O	0	0
29	by	O	O	0	0
30	Brussels	S-GPE	O	0	0
31	'	O	O	0	0
32	cargo	O	O	0	0
33	department	O	O	0	0
34	three	B-DATE	O	0	0
35	years	I-DATE	O	0	0
36	ago	E-DATE	O	0	0
37	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	app	O	S-TERM	0	0
3	combines	O	O	0	0
4	manifest	O	O	0	0
5	data	O	O	0	0
6	,	O	O	0	0
7	which	O	O	0	0
8	has	O	O	0	0
9	been	O	O	0	0
10	made	O	O	0	0
11	available	O	O	0	0
12	in	O	O	0	0
13	the	O	O	0	0
14	BRUcloud	S-MISC	S-TERM	0	0
15	since	O	O	0	0
16	2016	S-DATE	O	0	0
17	,	O	O	0	0
18	with	O	O	0	0
19	newly	O	O	0	0
20	added	O	O	0	0
21	data	O	O	0	0
22	from	O	O	0	0
23	the	O	O	0	0
24	forwarders	O	O	0	0
25	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	app	O	S-TERM	1	8
3	matches	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	collected	O	O	0	0
6	data	O	O	0	0
7	at	O	O	0	0
8	AWB	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
9	level	O	O	0	0
10	and	O	O	0	0
11	reports	O	O	0	0
12	a	O	O	0	0
13	complete	O	O	0	0
14	set	O	O	0	0
15	of	O	O	0	0
16	information	O	O	0	0
17	automatically	O	O	0	0
18	to	O	O	0	0
19	customs	O	O	0	0
20	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	It	O	O	0	0
3	is	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	first	S-MISC	O	0	0
6	result	O	O	0	0
7	whereby	O	O	0	0
8	information	O	O	0	0
9	from	O	O	0	0
10	different	O	O	0	0
11	sources	O	O	0	0
12	can	O	O	0	0
13	be	O	O	0	0
14	linked	O	O	0	0
15	to	O	O	0	0
16	one	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
17	new	O	O	0	0
18	solution	O	O	0	0
19	,	O	O	0	0
20	without	O	O	0	0
21	much	O	O	0	0
22	effort	O	O	0	0
23	,	O	O	0	0
24	but	O	O	0	0
25	with	O	O	0	0
26	great	O	O	0	0
27	impact	O	O	0	0
28	on	O	O	0	0
29	the	O	O	0	0
30	day-to-day	O	O	0	0
31	operation	O	O	0	0
32	of	O	O	0	0
33	the	O	O	0	0
34	companies	O	O	0	0
35	participating	O	O	0	0
36	,	O	O	0	0
37	"	O	O	0	0
38	said	O	O	0	0
39	Steven	B-PERSON	O	0	0
40	Polmans	E-PERSON	O	0	0
41	,	O	O	0	0
42	head	O	O	0	0
43	of	O	O	0	0
44	cargo	O	O	0	0
45	and	O	O	0	0
46	logistics	O	O	0	0
47	at	O	O	0	0
48	Brussels	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
49	Airport	I-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
50	Co	E-ORG	O	0	0
51	,	O	O	0	0
52	adding	O	O	0	0
53	:	O	O	0	0
54	"	O	O	0	0
55	This	O	O	0	0
56	is	O	O	0	0
57	one	O	O	0	0
58	of	O	O	0	0
59	the	O	O	0	0
60	several	O	O	0	0
61	benefits	O	O	0	0
62	we	O	O	0	0
63	aimed	O	O	0	0
64	for	O	O	0	0
65	when	O	O	0	0
66	developing	O	O	0	0
67	our	O	O	0	0
68	community	O	O	0	0
69	platform	O	O	0	0
70	.	O	O	0	0
71	"	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	cargo	O	O	0	0
3	arm	O	O	0	0
4	of	O	O	0	0
5	Brussels	S-GPE	B-TERM	0	0
6	airport	O	E-TERM	0	0
7	said	O	O	0	0
8	that	O	O	0	0
9	forwarders	O	O	0	0
10	who	O	O	0	0
11	opt	O	O	0	0
12	to	O	O	0	0
13	connect	O	O	0	0
14	to	O	O	0	0
15	the	O	O	0	0
16	app	O	S-TERM	0	0
17	can	O	O	0	0
18	"	O	O	0	0
19	drastically	O	O	0	0
20	improve	O	O	0	0
21	their	O	O	0	0
22	efficiency	O	O	0	0
23	by	O	O	0	0
24	avoiding	O	O	0	0
25	having	O	O	0	0
26	to	O	O	0	0
27	wait	O	O	0	0
28	in	O	O	0	0
29	lines	O	O	0	0
30	at	O	O	0	0
31	the	O	O	0	0
32	Customs	S-ORG	O	0	0
33	offices	O	O	0	0
34	for	O	O	0	0
35	the	O	O	0	0
36	stamping	O	O	0	0
37	of	O	O	0	0
38	AWBs	O	S-TERM	0	0
39	,	O	O	0	0
40	avoiding	O	O	0	0
41	having	O	O	0	0
42	to	O	O	0	0
43	create	O	O	0	0
44	Excel	S-MISC	O	0	0
45	list	O	O	0	0
46	reports	O	O	0	0
47	and	O	O	0	0
48	having	O	O	0	0
49	to	O	O	0	0
50	collect	O	O	0	0
51	alternative	O	O	0	0
52	evidence	O	O	0	0
53	manually	O	O	0	0
54	,	O	O	0	0
55	thus	O	O	0	0
56	eliminating	O	O	0	0
57	paper-based	O	O	0	0
58	procedures	O	O	0	0
59	and	O	O	0	0
60	the	O	O	0	0
61	resulting	O	O	0	0
62	errors	O	S-TERM	0	0
63	"	O	O	0	0
64	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	Customs	S-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
3	authorities	O	E-TERM	0	0
4	now	O	O	0	0
5	also	O	O	0	0
6	give	O	O	0	0
7	clearance	O	O	0	0
8	priority	O	O	0	0
9	to	O	O	0	0
10	forwarders	O	O	0	0
11	'	O	O	0	0
12	shipments	O	O	0	0
13	handled	O	O	0	0
14	via	O	O	0	0
15	the	O	O	0	0
16	app	O	S-TERM	0	0
17	,	O	O	0	0
18	saving	O	O	0	0
19	time	O	O	0	0
20	compared	O	O	0	0
21	with	O	O	0	0
22	the	O	O	0	0
23	previous	O	O	0	0
24	manual	O	O	0	0
25	process	O	O	0	0
26	for	O	O	0	0
27	verifying	O	O	0	0
28	documents	O	O	0	0
29	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	initiative	O	O	0	0
3	to	O	O	0	0
4	develop	O	O	0	0
5	the	O	O	0	0
6	"	O	O	0	0
7	quick-win	O	O	0	0
8	app	O	S-TERM	1	13
9	"	O	O	0	0
10	came	O	O	0	0
11	from	O	O	0	0
12	the	O	O	0	0
13	Customs	S-ORG	O	1	17
14	working	O	O	0	0
15	group	O	O	0	0
16	,	O	O	0	0
17	one	S-CARDINAL	O	1	27
18	of	O	O	0	0
19	several	O	O	0	0
20	organised	O	O	0	0
21	by	O	O	0	0
22	Air	B-ORG	O	0	0
23	Cargo	I-ORG	O	0	0
24	Belgium	I-ORG	O	0	0
25	(	I-ORG	O	0	0
26	ACB	I-ORG	O	0	0
27	)	E-ORG	O	0	0
28	,	O	O	0	0
29	the	O	O	0	0
30	air	O	O	0	0
31	cargo	O	O	0	0
32	community	O	O	0	0
33	representation	O	O	0	0
34	group	O	O	0	0
35	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	This	O	O	0	0
3	app	O	S-TERM	1	10
4	is	O	O	0	0
5	a	O	O	0	0
6	win	O	O	0	0
7	for	O	O	0	0
8	both	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	Customs	S-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
11	authorities	O	E-TERM	0	0
12	and	O	O	0	0
13	the	O	O	0	0
14	forwarders	O	O	0	0
15	.	O	O	0	0

1	A	O	O	0	0
2	fine	O	O	0	0
3	example	O	O	0	0
4	of	O	O	0	0
5	the	O	O	0	0
6	fruitful	O	O	0	0
7	cooperation	O	O	0	0
8	between	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	stakeholders	O	O	0	0
11	at	O	O	0	0
12	BRUcargo	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	19
13	"	O	O	0	0
14	said	O	O	0	0
15	a	O	O	0	0
16	spokesperson	O	O	0	0
17	for	O	O	0	0
18	BDP	B-ORG	O	0	0
19	International	E-ORG	O	1	20
20	one	S-CARDINAL	O	1	23
21	of	O	O	0	0
22	the	O	O	0	0
23	six	S-CARDINAL	O	1	28
24	companies	O	O	0	0
25	already	O	O	0	0
26	using	O	O	0	0
27	the	O	O	0	0
28	app	O	S-TERM	0	0
29	on	O	O	0	0
30	a	O	O	0	0
31	daily	O	O	0	0
32	basis	O	O	0	0
33	.	O	O	0	0

1	David	B-PERSON	O	0	0
2	Bellon	E-PERSON	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	director	O	O	0	0
5	of	O	O	0	0
6	airfreight	O	O	0	0
7	at	O	O	0	0
8	DHL	B-ORG	O	0	0
9	Global	I-ORG	O	0	0
10	Forwarding	I-ORG	O	0	0
11	Belgium	E-ORG	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	said	O	O	0	0
14	:	O	O	0	0
15	"	O	O	0	0
16	It	O	O	0	0
17	was	O	O	0	0
18	great	O	O	0	0
19	to	O	O	0	0
20	see	O	O	0	0
21	the	O	O	0	0
22	collaborative	O	O	0	0
23	approach	O	S-TERM	0	0
24	in	O	O	0	0
25	the	O	O	0	0
26	community	O	O	0	0
27	resulted	O	O	0	0
28	in	O	O	0	0
29	an	O	O	0	0
30	application	O	S-TERM	0	0
31	that	O	O	0	0
32	addressed	O	O	0	0
33	the	O	O	0	0
34	urgent	O	O	0	0
35	needs	O	O	0	0
36	of	O	O	0	0
37	the	O	O	0	0
38	entire	O	O	0	0
39	forwarding	O	O	0	0
40	community	O	O	0	0
41	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	Together	O	O	0	0
3	with	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	other	O	O	0	0
6	members	O	O	0	0
7	of	O	O	0	0
8	BAFI	S-ORG	O	0	12
9	,	O	O	0	0
10	DHL	B-ORG	O	0	0
11	Global	I-ORG	O	0	0
12	Forwarding	E-ORG	O	0	0
13	was	O	O	0	0
14	happy	O	O	0	0
15	to	O	O	0	0
16	provide	O	O	0	0
17	support	O	O	0	0
18	in	O	O	0	0
19	developing	O	O	0	0
20	it	O	O	0	0
21	.	O	O	0	0
22	"	O	O	0	0

1	More	B-CARDINAL	O	0	0
2	than	I-CARDINAL	O	0	0
3	25	E-CARDINAL	O	0	0
4	companies	O	O	0	0
5	have	O	O	0	0
6	already	O	O	0	0
7	confirmed	O	O	0	0
8	that	O	O	0	0
9	they	O	O	0	0
10	will	O	O	0	0
11	roll	O	O	0	0
12	out	O	O	0	0
13	the	O	O	0	0
14	app	O	S-TERM	1	22
15	in	O	O	0	0
16	the	B-DATE	O	0	0
17	coming	I-DATE	O	0	0
18	weeks	E-DATE	O	0	0
19	,	O	O	0	0
20	covering	O	O	0	0
21	90	B-MISC	O	0	0
22	%	E-MISC	O	1	28
23	of	O	O	0	0
24	the	O	O	0	0
25	volumes	O	O	0	0
26	handled	O	O	0	0
27	at	O	O	0	0
28	BRUcargo	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
29	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	This	O	O	0	0
3	collaboratively	O	O	0	0
4	created	O	O	0	0
5	app	O	S-TERM	0	0
6	results	O	O	0	0
7	in	O	O	0	0
8	a	O	O	0	0
9	lower	O	O	0	0
10	administrative	O	O	0	0
11	burden	O	O	0	0
12	for	O	O	0	0
13	all	O	O	0	0
14	the	O	O	0	0
15	parties	O	O	0	0
16	.	O	O	0	0

1	Digitization	O	O	0	0
2	within	O	O	0	0
3	BRUcargo	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	10
4	will	O	O	0	0
5	further	O	O	0	0
6	lower	O	O	0	0
7	the	O	O	0	0
8	chances	O	O	0	0
9	of	O	O	0	0
10	errors	O	S-TERM	0	0
11	and	O	O	0	0
12	will	O	O	0	0
13	help	O	O	0	0
14	to	O	O	0	0
15	drastically	O	O	0	0
16	decrease	O	O	0	0
17	lead	O	O	0	0
18	times	O	O	0	0
19	,	O	O	0	0
20	"	O	O	0	0
21	said	O	O	0	0
22	Bart	B-PERSON	O	0	0
23	Vleugels	E-PERSON	O	0	0
24	,	O	O	0	0
25	advisory	O	O	0	0
26	general	O	O	0	0
27	at	O	O	0	0
28	Federal	B-ORG	O	0	0
29	Public	I-ORG	O	0	0
30	Service	I-ORG	O	0	0
31	of	I-ORG	O	0	0
32	Finance	E-ORG	O	0	37
33	,	O	O	0	0
34	Customs	B-ORG	O	0	0
35	and	I-ORG	O	0	0
36	Excise	I-ORG	O	0	0
37	Duties	E-ORG	O	0	0
38	.	O	O	0	0

1	Later	B-DATE	O	0	0
2	this	I-DATE	O	0	0
3	year	E-DATE	O	0	0
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	the	O	O	0	0
6	BRUcargo	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
7	slot	O	O	0	0
8	application	O	S-TERM	0	0
9	will	O	O	0	0
10	be	O	O	0	0
11	introduced	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	reducing	O	O	0	0
14	waiting	O	O	0	0
15	times	O	O	0	0
16	at	O	O	0	0
17	the	O	O	0	0
18	handlers	O	O	0	0
19	'	O	O	0	0
20	premises	O	O	0	0
21	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	The	O	O	0	0
3	application	O	S-TERM	0	0
4	is	O	O	0	0
5	undergoing	O	O	0	0
6	final	O	O	0	0
7	testing	O	O	0	0
8	with	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	partners	O	O	0	0
11	in	O	O	0	0
12	our	O	O	0	0
13	project	O	O	0	0
14	group	O	O	0	0
15	and	O	O	0	0
16	the	O	O	0	0
17	results	O	O	0	0
18	are	O	O	0	0
19	meeting	O	O	0	0
20	our	O	O	0	0
21	expectations	O	O	0	0
22	"	O	O	0	0
23	,	O	O	0	0
24	said	O	O	0	0
25	Sara	B-PERSON	O	0	0
26	Van	I-PERSON	O	0	0
27	Gelder	E-PERSON	O	0	0
28	,	O	O	0	0
29	leading	O	O	0	0
30	the	O	O	0	0
31	BRUcloud	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	34
32	project	O	O	0	0
33	at	O	O	0	0
34	BRUcargo	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
35	.	O	O	0	0

1	She	O	O	0	0
2	added	O	O	0	0
3	:	O	O	0	0
4	"	O	O	0	0
5	We	O	O	0	0
6	are	O	O	0	0
7	excited	O	O	0	0
8	and	O	O	0	0
9	look	O	O	0	0
10	forward	O	O	0	0
11	going	O	O	0	0
12	live	O	O	0	0
13	with	O	O	0	0
14	additional	O	O	0	0
15	partners	O	O	0	0
16	in	O	O	0	0
17	the	B-DATE	O	0	0
18	last	I-DATE	O	0	0
19	quarter	I-DATE	O	0	0
20	of	I-DATE	O	0	0
21	this	I-DATE	O	0	0
22	year	E-DATE	O	0	0
23	.	O	O	0	0
24	"	O	O	0	0

1	Read	O	O	0	0
2	more	O	O	0	0
3	cargo	O	O	0	0
4	airport	O	O	0	0
5	news	O	O	0	0

1	DHL	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	5
2	opens	O	O	0	0
3	urban	O	B-TERM	0	0
4	logistics	O	I-TERM	0	0
5	center	O	E-TERM	0	7
6	in	O	O	0	0
7	Singapore	S-GPE	O	0	0

1	To	O	O	0	0
2	prepare	O	O	0	0
3	for	O	O	0	0
4	an	O	O	0	0
5	expected	O	O	0	0
6	increase	O	O	0	0
7	in	O	O	0	0
8	pharmaceutical	O	O	0	0
9	and	O	O	0	0
10	high-tech	O	B-TERM	0	0
11	air	O	I-TERM	0	0
12	cargo	O	I-TERM	0	0
13	traffic	O	E-TERM	1	17
14	in	O	O	0	0
15	the	O	O	0	0
16	Southeast	B-MISC	B-TERM	0	0
17	Asian	E-MISC	I-TERM	0	22
18	region	O	E-TERM	0	0
19	,	O	O	0	0
20	DHL	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
21	Supply	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
22	Chain	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	28
23	has	O	O	0	0
24	opened	O	O	0	0
25	a	O	O	0	0
26	new	O	B-TERM	0	0
27	logistics	O	I-TERM	0	0
28	center	O	E-TERM	0	30
29	in	O	O	0	0
30	Singapore	S-GPE	O	0	0
31	that	O	O	0	0
32	the	O	O	0	0
33	company	O	O	0	0
34	said	O	O	0	0
35	will	O	O	0	0
36	improve	O	O	0	0
37	the	O	O	0	0
38	efficiency	O	O	0	0
39	of	O	O	0	0
40	its	O	O	0	0
41	current	O	B-TERM	0	0
42	operations	O	E-TERM	0	45
43	by	O	O	0	0
44	20	B-MISC	O	0	0
45	percent	E-MISC	O	0	0
46	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	design	O	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	DHL	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	15
5	said	O	O	0	0
6	,	O	O	0	0
7	will	O	O	0	0
8	be	O	O	0	0
9	considered	O	O	0	0
10	a	O	O	0	0
11	model	O	O	0	0
12	for	O	O	0	0
13	its	O	O	0	0
14	future	O	B-TERM	0	0
15	expansions	O	E-TERM	1	20
16	in	O	O	0	0
17	densely	O	O	0	0
18	settled	O	O	0	0
19	urban	O	B-TERM	0	0
20	areas	O	E-TERM	0	0
21	.	O	O	0	0

1	Called	O	O	0	0
2	the	B-ORG	O	0	0
3	Advanced	I-ORG	O	0	0
4	Regional	I-ORG	O	0	0
5	Center	I-ORG	O	0	0
6	(	I-ORG	O	0	0
7	ARC	I-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
8	)	E-ORG	O	1	13
9	,	O	O	0	0
10	the	O	O	0	0
11	new	O	O	0	0
12	90,000-square-foot	O	O	0	0
13	Singapore	S-GPE	O	0	0
14	facility	O	O	0	0
15	features	O	O	0	0
16	advanced	O	O	0	0
17	robotics	O	O	0	0
18	and	O	O	0	0
19	increased	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	warehousing	O	O	0	0
22	footprint	O	O	0	0
23	on	O	O	0	0
24	the	O	O	0	0
25	island	O	O	0	0
26	nation	O	O	0	0
27	by	O	O	0	0
28	40	B-MISC	O	0	0
29	percent	E-MISC	O	0	0
30	.	O	O	0	0

1	DHL	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	4
2	will	O	O	0	0
3	use	O	O	0	0
4	130	S-CARDINAL	O	1	15
5	robotic	O	O	0	0
6	shuttles	O	O	0	0
7	to	O	O	0	0
8	retrieve	O	O	0	0
9	and	O	O	0	0
10	store	O	O	0	0
11	products	O	O	0	0
12	from	O	O	0	0
13	up	B-CARDINAL	O	0	0
14	to	I-CARDINAL	O	0	0
15	72,000	E-CARDINAL	O	1	19
16	locations	O	O	0	0
17	arranged	O	O	0	0
18	in	O	O	0	0
19	26	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
20	levels	O	O	0	0
21	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	We	O	O	0	0
3	see	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	Asian	S-MISC	O	0	0
6	region	O	O	0	0
7	as	O	O	0	0
8	a	O	O	0	0
9	swift	O	O	0	0
10	adopter	O	O	0	0
11	of	O	O	0	0
12	technologies	O	O	0	0
13	for	O	O	0	0
14	enhanced	O	O	0	0
15	productivity	O	O	0	0
16	and	O	O	0	0
17	efficiency	O	O	0	0
18	,	O	O	0	0
19	"	O	O	0	0
20	said	O	O	0	0
21	Frank	B-PERSON	O	0	0
22	Appel	E-PERSON	O	0	0
23	,	O	O	0	0
24	CEO	O	O	0	0
25	of	O	O	0	0
26	Deutsche	B-ORG	O	0	0
27	Post	I-ORG	O	0	0
28	DHL	I-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
29	Group	E-ORG	O	0	0
30	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	By	O	O	0	0
3	2020	S-DATE	O	0	0
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	Asia	S-MISC	O	1	9
6	will	O	O	0	0
7	constitute	O	O	0	0
8	30	B-MISC	O	0	0
9	percent	E-MISC	O	0	0
10	of	O	O	0	0
11	our	O	O	0	0
12	total	O	O	0	0
13	revenue	O	O	0	0
14	.	O	O	0	0
15	"	O	O	0	0

1	Facilities	O	O	0	0
2	like	O	O	0	0
3	the	O	O	0	0
4	ARC	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	11
5	,	O	O	0	0
6	he	O	O	0	0
7	added	O	O	0	0
8	,	O	O	0	0
9	will	O	O	0	0
10	help	O	O	0	0
11	DHL	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
12	reduce	O	O	0	0
13	complexity	O	O	0	0
14	,	O	O	0	0
15	while	O	O	0	0
16	it	O	O	0	0
17	improves	O	O	0	0
18	accuracy	O	O	0	0
19	and	O	O	0	0
20	productivity	O	O	0	0
21	.	O	O	0	0

1	In	O	O	0	0
2	addition	O	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	ARC	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
6	includes	O	O	0	0
7	"	O	O	0	0
8	clean	O	O	0	0
9	rooms	O	O	0	0
10	"	O	O	0	0
11	for	O	O	0	0
12	the	O	O	0	0
13	storage	O	O	0	0
14	and	O	O	0	0
15	handling	O	O	0	0
16	of	O	O	0	0
17	life	O	O	0	0
18	sciences	O	O	0	0
19	and	O	O	0	0
20	healthcare-related	O	O	0	0
21	shipments	O	O	0	0
22	.	O	O	0	0

1	There	O	O	0	0
2	will	O	O	0	0
3	also	O	O	0	0
4	be	O	O	0	0
5	specialized	O	O	0	0
6	infrastructure	O	O	0	0
7	for	O	O	0	0
8	aerospace	O	O	0	0
9	operations	O	O	0	0
10	and	O	O	0	0
11	customizable	O	O	0	0
12	storage	O	O	0	0
13	options	O	O	0	0
14	for	O	O	0	0
15	various	O	O	0	0
16	high-tech	O	O	0	0
17	customers	O	O	0	0
18	.	O	O	0	0

1	DHL	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	11
2	's	O	O	0	0
3	move	O	O	0	0
4	comes	O	O	0	0
5	a	B-DATE	O	0	0
6	few	I-DATE	O	0	0
7	months	E-DATE	O	0	0
8	after	O	O	0	0
9	Kuehne	B-ORG	O	0	0
10	+	I-ORG	O	0	0
11	Nagel	E-ORG	O	1	21
12	opened	O	O	0	0
13	its	O	O	0	0
14	own	O	O	0	0
15	pharma-friendly	O	O	0	0
16	facility	O	O	0	0
17	in	O	O	0	0
18	January	S-DATE	O	0	0
19	–	O	O	0	0
20	a	O	O	0	0
21	164,000-square-foot	S-CARDINAL	O	1	26
22	logistics	O	O	0	0
23	hub	O	O	0	0
24	in	O	O	0	0
25	west	O	O	0	0
26	Singapore	S-GPE	O	0	0
27	,	O	O	0	0
28	located	O	O	0	0
29	near	O	O	0	0
30	the	O	O	0	0
31	country	O	O	0	0
32	's	O	O	0	0
33	pharmaceutical	O	O	0	0
34	and	O	O	0	0
35	healthcare	O	O	0	0
36	centers	O	O	0	0
37	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	new	O	O	0	0
3	facility	O	O	0	0
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	K+N	S-ORG	O	0	0
6	said	O	O	0	0
7	,	O	O	0	0
8	will	O	O	0	0
9	be	O	O	0	0
10	large	O	O	0	0
11	enough	O	O	0	0
12	to	O	O	0	0
13	serve	O	O	0	0
14	its	O	O	0	0
15	clients	O	O	0	0
16	across	O	O	0	0
17	the	O	O	0	0
18	ASEAN	S-ORG	O	0	0
19	countries	O	O	0	0
20	.	O	O	0	0

1	TIACA	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	5
2	and	O	O	0	0
3	Air	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
4	Cargo	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
5	Belgium	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	7
6	launch	O	O	0	0
7	masterclass	O	S-TERM	0	0
8	on	O	O	0	0
9	digitisation	O	O	0	0
10	and	O	O	0	0
11	data	O	O	0	0
12	sharing	O	O	0	0

1	TIACA	S-ORG	O	1	8
2	has	O	O	0	0
3	teamed	O	O	0	0
4	up	O	O	0	0
5	with	O	O	0	0
6	Air	B-ORG	O	0	0
7	Cargo	I-ORG	O	0	0
8	Belgium	E-ORG	O	1	12
9	,	O	O	0	0
10	the	O	O	0	0
11	community	O	O	0	0
12	organisation	O	O	1	15
13	at	O	O	0	0
14	Brussels	B-FAC	O	0	0
15	Airport	E-FAC	O	1	19
16	to	O	O	0	0
17	hold	O	O	0	0
18	a	O	O	0	0
19	masterclass	O	O	1	28
20	next	B-DATE	O	0	0
21	month	E-DATE	O	0	0
22	exploring	O	O	0	0
23	how	O	O	0	0
24	the	O	O	0	0
25	air	O	O	0	0
26	cargo	O	O	0	0
27	supply	O	O	0	0
28	chain	O	O	1	32
29	can	O	O	0	0
30	leverage	O	O	0	0
31	digital	O	O	0	0
32	transformation	O	O	0	0
33	and	O	O	0	0
34	data	O	O	0	0
35	sharing	O	O	0	0
36	as	O	O	0	0
37	enablers	O	O	0	0
38	for	O	O	0	0
39	growth	O	O	0	0
40	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	B-MISC	O	0	0
2	'	I-MISC	B-TERM	0	0
3	Connected	I-MISC	I-TERM	0	0
4	Air	I-MISC	I-TERM	0	0
5	Cargo	I-MISC	I-TERM	0	0
6	Masterclass	I-MISC	E-TERM	0	0
7	'	E-MISC	O	1	11
8	will	O	O	0	0
9	feature	O	O	0	0
10	important	O	O	0	0
11	debates	O	O	0	0
12	including	O	O	0	0
13	building	O	O	0	0
14	a	O	O	0	0
15	connected	O	O	0	0
16	air	O	O	0	0
17	cargo	O	O	0	0
18	community	O	O	0	0
19	,	O	O	0	0
20	using	O	O	0	0
21	technology	O	O	0	0
22	as	O	O	0	0
23	an	O	O	0	0
24	enabler	O	O	0	0
25	,	O	O	0	0
26	and	O	O	0	0
27	digital	O	O	0	0
28	transformation	O	O	1	37
29	best	O	O	0	0
30	practice	O	O	0	0
31	,	O	O	0	0
32	when	O	O	0	0
33	it	O	O	0	0
34	takes	O	O	0	0
35	place	O	O	0	0
36	at	O	O	0	0
37	BRUcargo	S-GPE	O	0	41
38	's	O	O	0	0
39	Air	B-ORG	O	0	0
40	Cargo	I-ORG	O	0	0
41	Academy	E-ORG	O	0	43
42	in	O	O	0	0
43	Brussels	S-GPE	O	0	45
44	,	O	O	0	0
45	Belgium	S-GPE	O	0	0
46	,	O	O	0	0
47	from	O	O	0	0
48	January	B-DATE	O	0	0
49	30	I-DATE	O	0	0
50	to	I-DATE	O	0	0
51	31	E-DATE	O	0	0
52	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	Masterclass	S-MISC	O	1	12
3	will	O	O	0	0
4	also	O	O	0	0
5	include	O	O	0	0
6	a	O	O	0	0
7	seminar	O	O	0	0
8	on	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	story	O	O	0	0
11	of	O	O	0	0
12	BRUcloud	S-ORG	O	0	0
13	,	O	O	0	0
14	an	O	O	0	0
15	open	O	O	0	0
16	data	O	O	0	0
17	sharing	O	O	0	0
18	platform	O	O	0	0
19	that	O	O	0	0
20	enables	O	O	0	0
21	the	O	O	0	0
22	different	O	O	0	0
23	stakeholders	O	O	0	0
24	to	O	O	0	0
25	work	O	O	0	0
26	more	O	O	0	0
27	"	O	O	0	0
28	integrated	O	O	0	0
29	"	O	O	0	0
30	and	O	O	0	0
31	act	O	O	0	0
32	as	O	O	0	0
33	a	O	O	0	0
34	network	O	O	0	0
35	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	We	O	O	0	0
3	are	O	O	0	0
4	living	O	O	0	0
5	in	O	O	0	0
6	a	O	O	0	0
7	period	O	O	0	0
8	of	O	O	0	0
9	great	O	O	0	0
10	change	O	O	0	0
11	for	O	O	0	0
12	the	O	O	0	0
13	airfreight	O	O	0	0
14	industry	O	O	0	0
15	,	O	O	0	0
16	and	O	O	0	0
17	it	O	O	0	0
18	is	O	O	0	0
19	imperative	O	O	0	0
20	that	O	O	0	0
21	supply	O	O	0	0
22	chain	O	O	0	0
23	professionals	O	O	0	0
24	learn	O	O	0	0
25	how	O	O	0	0
26	to	O	O	0	0
27	take	O	O	0	0
28	advantage	O	O	0	0
29	of	O	O	0	0
30	emerging	O	O	0	0
31	technologies	O	O	0	0
32	and	O	O	0	0
33	trends	O	O	0	0
34	,	O	O	0	0
35	as	O	O	0	0
36	well	O	O	0	0
37	as	O	O	0	0
38	explore	O	O	0	0
39	new	O	O	0	0
40	ways	O	O	0	0
41	of	O	O	0	0
42	collaborating	O	O	0	0
43	,	O	O	0	0
44	"	O	O	0	0
45	said	O	O	0	0
46	Steven	B-PERSON	O	0	0
47	Polmans	E-PERSON	O	0	0
48	,	O	O	0	0
49	vice	O	O	0	0
50	chairman	O	O	0	0
51	,	O	O	0	0
52	TIACA	S-ORG	O	1	59
53	,	O	O	0	0
54	and	O	O	0	0
55	head	O	O	0	0
56	of	O	O	0	0
57	Cargo	B-ORG	O	0	0
58	and	I-ORG	O	0	0
59	Logistics	E-ORG	O	1	63
60	at	O	O	0	0
61	Brussels	B-ORG	O	0	0
62	Airport	I-ORG	O	0	0
63	Company	E-ORG	O	0	0
64	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	Attendees	O	O	0	0
3	have	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	option	O	O	0	0
6	of	O	O	0	0
7	attending	O	O	0	0
8	an	O	O	0	0
9	additional	O	O	0	0
10	session	O	O	0	0
11	,	O	O	0	0
12	'	O	O	0	0
13	From	O	O	0	0
14	theory	O	O	0	0
15	to	O	O	0	0
16	practice	O	O	0	0
17	,	O	O	0	0
18	getting	O	O	0	0
19	started	O	O	0	0
20	with	O	O	0	0
21	collaborative	O	O	0	0
22	apps	O	O	0	0
23	'	O	O	0	0
24	,	O	O	0	0
25	which	O	O	0	0
26	looks	O	O	0	0
27	at	O	O	0	0
28	how	O	O	0	0
29	to	O	O	0	0
30	put	O	O	0	0
31	theory	O	O	0	0
32	into	O	O	0	0
33	practice	O	O	0	0
34	and	O	O	0	0
35	even	O	O	0	0
36	includes	O	O	0	0
37	live	O	O	0	0
38	demonstrations	O	O	0	0
39	,	O	O	0	0
40	when	O	O	0	0
41	it	O	O	0	0
42	takes	O	O	0	0
43	place	O	O	0	0
44	on	O	O	0	0
45	February	B-DATE	O	0	0
46	1	E-DATE	O	0	0
47	.	O	O	0	0
48	"	O	O	0	0

1	Earlier	B-DATE	O	0	0
2	this	I-DATE	O	0	0
3	year	E-DATE	O	0	0
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	TIACA	S-ORG	O	1	13
6	teamed	O	O	0	0
7	up	O	O	0	0
8	with	O	O	0	0
9	UK-based	O	O	0	0
10	aviation	O	O	0	0
11	consultancy	O	O	0	0
12	TSA	B-ORG	O	0	0
13	Group	E-ORG	O	0	0
14	for	O	O	0	0
15	an	O	O	0	0
16	extensive	O	O	0	0
17	training	O	O	0	0
18	programme	O	O	0	0
19	for	O	O	0	0
20	air	O	O	0	0
21	cargo	O	O	0	0
22	professionals	O	O	0	0
23	,	O	O	0	0
24	including	O	O	0	0
25	the	O	O	0	0
26	development	O	O	0	0
27	of	O	O	0	0
28	several	O	O	0	0
29	new	O	O	0	0
30	courses	O	O	0	0
31	aimed	O	O	0	0
32	at	O	O	0	0
33	providing	O	O	0	0
34	participants	O	O	0	0
35	with	O	O	0	0
36	a	O	O	0	0
37	complete	O	O	0	0
38	overview	O	O	0	0
39	of	O	O	0	0
40	the	O	O	0	0
41	aviation	O	O	0	0
42	industry	O	O	0	0
43	.	O	O	0	0

1	IATA	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	3
2	and	O	O	0	0
3	UNCTAD	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
4	aim	O	O	0	0
5	to	O	O	0	0
6	boost	O	O	0	0
7	adoption	O	O	0	0
8	of	O	O	0	0
9	messaging	O	O	0	0
10	standards	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	integration	O	O	0	0
3	of	O	O	0	0
4	Cargo-XML	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	6
5	in	O	O	0	0
6	ASYCUDAWorld	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	9
7	–	O	O	0	0
8	the	O	O	0	0
9	UNCTAD	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	16
10	automated	O	O	0	0
11	customs	O	O	0	0
12	management	O	O	0	0
13	system	O	O	0	0
14	used	O	O	0	0
15	by	O	O	0	0
16	90	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
17	countries	O	O	0	0
18	for	O	O	0	0
19	customs	O	O	0	0
20	procedures	O	O	0	0
21	–	O	O	0	0
22	standardises	O	O	0	0
23	the	O	O	0	0
24	electronic	O	O	0	0
25	communications	O	O	0	0
26	between	O	O	0	0
27	airlines	O	O	0	0
28	and	O	O	0	0
29	customs	O	B-TERM	0	0
30	authorities	O	E-TERM	0	0
31	using	O	O	0	0
32	the	O	O	0	0
33	program	O	O	0	0
34	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	new	O	O	0	0
3	data	O	O	0	0
4	standard	O	O	0	0
5	reduces	O	O	0	0
6	message	O	O	0	0
7	duplication	O	O	0	0
8	and	O	O	0	0
9	simplifies	O	O	0	0
10	communication	O	O	0	0
11	across	O	O	0	0
12	the	O	O	0	0
13	supply	O	O	0	0
14	chain	O	O	0	0
15	facilitating	O	O	0	0
16	trade	O	O	0	0
17	growth	O	O	0	0
18	,	O	O	0	0
19	improving	O	O	0	0
20	cargo	O	O	0	0
21	security	O	O	0	0
22	,	O	O	0	0
23	modernising	O	O	0	0
24	customs	O	O	0	0
25	operations	O	O	0	0
26	and	O	O	0	0
27	fostering	O	O	0	0
28	participation	O	O	0	0
29	in	O	O	0	0
30	global	O	O	0	0
31	commerce	O	O	0	0
32	through	O	O	0	0
33	advance	O	O	0	0
34	electronic	O	O	0	0
35	data	O	O	0	0
36	submission	O	O	0	0
37	for	O	O	0	0
38	air	O	B-TERM	0	0
39	cargo	O	I-TERM	0	0
40	shipments	O	E-TERM	0	0
41	.	O	O	0	0

1	Cargo-XML	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	9
2	makes	O	O	0	0
3	it	O	O	0	0
4	easier	O	O	0	0
5	for	O	O	0	0
6	airlines	O	O	0	0
7	,	O	O	0	0
8	freight	O	B-TERM	0	0
9	forwarders	O	E-TERM	0	0
10	and	O	O	0	0
11	shippers	O	O	0	0
12	to	O	O	0	0
13	ensure	O	O	0	0
14	that	O	O	0	0
15	the	O	O	0	0
16	information	O	O	0	0
17	being	O	O	0	0
18	provided	O	O	0	0
19	to	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	customs	O	B-TERM	0	0
22	authorities	O	E-TERM	0	0
23	is	O	O	0	0
24	technically	O	O	0	0
25	correct	O	O	0	0
26	and	O	O	0	0
27	in	O	O	0	0
28	line	O	O	0	0
29	with	O	O	0	0
30	standards	O	O	0	0
31	of	O	O	0	0
32	industry	O	O	0	0
33	bodies	O	O	0	0
34	such	O	O	0	0
35	as	O	O	0	0
36	the	B-ORG	O	0	0
37	World	I-ORG	O	0	0
38	Customs	I-ORG	O	0	0
39	Organization	E-ORG	O	0	41
40	(	O	O	0	0
41	WCO	S-ORG	O	0	0
42	)	O	O	0	0
43	and	O	O	0	0
44	regulators	O	O	0	0
45	.	O	O	0	0

1	It	O	O	0	0
2	also	O	O	0	0
3	facilitates	O	O	0	0
4	custom	O	O	0	0
5	risk	O	O	0	0
6	assessments	O	O	0	0
7	for	O	O	0	0
8	air	O	B-TERM	0	0
9	cargo	O	I-TERM	0	0
10	shipments	O	E-TERM	0	0
11	and	O	O	0	0
12	improves	O	O	0	0
13	compliance	O	O	0	0
14	with	O	O	0	0
15	security	O	O	0	0
16	regulations	O	O	0	0
17	.	O	O	0	0

1	IATA	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
2	's	O	O	0	0
3	head	O	O	0	0
4	of	O	O	0	0
5	cargo	O	O	0	0
6	,	O	O	0	0
7	Glyn	B-PERSON	O	0	0
8	Hughes	E-PERSON	O	0	0
9	says	O	O	0	0
10	:	O	O	0	0
11	"	O	O	0	0
12	Having	O	O	0	0
13	a	O	O	0	0
14	standard	O	B-TERM	0	0
15	air	O	I-TERM	0	0
16	cargo	O	E-TERM	1	22
17	digital	O	O	0	0
18	messaging	O	O	0	0
19	system	O	O	0	0
20	between	O	O	0	0
21	customs	O	B-TERM	0	0
22	authorities	O	E-TERM	0	0
23	,	O	O	0	0
24	airlines	O	O	0	0
25	and	O	O	0	0
26	other	O	O	0	0
27	air	O	O	0	0
28	cargo	O	O	0	0
29	stakeholders	O	O	0	0
30	is	O	O	0	0
31	fundamental	O	O	0	0
32	to	O	O	0	0
33	enhancing	O	O	0	0
34	efficiency	O	O	0	0
35	,	O	O	0	0
36	driving	O	O	0	0
37	trade	O	O	0	0
38	growth	O	O	0	0
39	and	O	O	0	0
40	maximizing	O	O	0	0
41	safety	O	O	0	0
42	and	O	O	0	0
43	security	O	O	0	0
44	across	O	O	0	0
45	the	O	O	0	0
46	industry	O	O	0	0
47	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	IATA	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	7
3	's	O	O	0	0
4	successful	O	O	0	0
5	partnership	O	O	0	0
6	with	O	O	0	0
7	UNCTAD	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	13
8	means	O	O	0	0
9	that	O	O	0	0
10	airlines	O	O	0	0
11	,	O	O	0	0
12	freight	O	B-TERM	0	0
13	forwarders	O	E-TERM	1	21
14	,	O	O	0	0
15	shippers	O	O	0	0
16	and	O	O	0	0
17	border	O	O	0	0
18	agencies	O	O	0	0
19	in	O	O	0	0
20	over	O	O	0	0
21	90	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
22	countries	O	O	0	0
23	can	O	O	0	0
24	now	O	O	0	0
25	talk	O	O	0	0
26	the	O	O	0	0
27	same	O	O	0	0
28	digital	O	O	0	0
29	language	O	O	0	0
30	.	O	O	0	0

1	It	O	O	0	0
2	takes	O	O	0	0
3	the	O	O	0	0
4	industry	O	O	0	0
5	one	S-CARDINAL	O	1	17
6	step	O	O	0	0
7	closer	O	O	0	0
8	to	O	O	0	0
9	achieving	O	O	0	0
10	the	O	O	0	0
11	global	O	O	0	0
12	adoption	O	O	0	0
13	of	O	O	0	0
14	a	O	O	0	0
15	standard	O	B-TERM	0	0
16	air	O	I-TERM	0	0
17	cargo	O	E-TERM	0	0
18	messaging	O	O	0	0
19	system	O	O	0	0
20	.	O	O	0	0
21	"	O	O	0	0

1	UNCTAD	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
2	's	O	O	0	0
3	director	O	O	0	0
4	of	O	O	0	0
5	division	O	O	0	0
6	on	O	O	0	0
7	technology	O	O	0	0
8	and	O	O	0	0
9	logistics	O	O	0	0
10	,	O	O	0	0
11	Shamika	B-PERSON	O	0	0
12	Sirimanne	E-PERSON	O	0	0
13	adds	O	O	0	0
14	:	O	O	0	0
15	"	O	O	0	0
16	Considering	O	O	0	0
17	the	O	O	0	0
18	complexity	O	O	0	0
19	of	O	O	0	0
20	trade	O	O	0	0
21	flows	O	O	0	0
22	,	O	O	0	0
23	increasing	O	O	0	0
24	demands	O	O	0	0
25	on	O	O	0	0
26	advance	O	O	0	0
27	risk	O	O	0	0
28	assessments	O	O	0	0
29	and	O	O	0	0
30	operational	O	O	0	0
31	efficiency	O	O	0	0
32	,	O	O	0	0
33	electronic	O	O	0	0
34	data	O	O	0	0
35	interchange	O	O	0	0
36	is	O	O	0	0
37	an	O	O	0	0
38	integral	O	O	0	0
39	component	O	O	0	0
40	of	O	O	0	0
41	customs	O	O	0	0
42	modernisation	O	O	0	0
43	programs	O	O	0	0
44	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	We	O	O	0	0
3	're	O	O	0	0
4	delighted	O	O	0	0
5	to	O	O	0	0
6	support	O	O	0	0
7	IATA	B-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
8	Cargo-XML	E-ORG	S-TERM	1	12
9	standards	O	O	0	0
10	in	O	O	0	0
11	the	O	O	0	0
12	ASYCUDA	S-ORG	O	0	0
13	system	O	O	0	0
14	,	O	O	0	0
15	which	O	O	0	0
16	ultimately	O	O	0	0
17	will	O	O	0	0
18	help	O	O	0	0
19	trade	O	O	0	0
20	efficiency	O	O	0	0
21	,	O	O	0	0
22	improve	O	O	0	0
23	custom	O	O	0	0
24	clearance	O	O	0	0
25	and	O	O	0	0
26	enhance	O	O	0	0
27	security	O	O	0	0
28	through	O	O	0	0
29	risk	O	O	0	0
30	assessment	O	O	0	0
31	procedures	O	O	0	0
32	.	O	O	0	0
33	"	O	O	0	0

1	DB	B-ORG	O	0	0
2	Schenker	E-ORG	O	0	6
3	opens	O	O	0	0
4	solar-powered	O	B-TERM	0	0
5	logistics	O	I-TERM	0	0
6	center	O	E-TERM	0	8
7	in	O	O	0	0
8	Dubai	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0

1	DB	B-ORG	O	0	0
2	Schenker	E-ORG	O	1	9
3	has	O	O	0	0
4	opened	O	O	0	0
5	a	O	O	0	0
6	new	O	O	0	0
7	,	O	O	0	0
8	massive	O	B-TERM	0	0
9	logistics	O	E-TERM	0	12
10	and	O	O	0	0
11	distribution	O	B-TERM	0	0
12	center	O	E-TERM	1	16
13	,	O	O	0	0
14	named	O	O	0	0
15	DLC	B-MISC	O	0	0
16	II	E-MISC	O	1	19
17	,	O	O	0	0
18	in	O	O	0	0
19	Dubai	S-GPE	S-TERM	1	25
20	near	O	O	0	0
21	Dubai	S-GPE	B-TERM	0	0
22	World	I-FAC	I-TERM	0	0
23	Central	I-FAC	I-TERM	0	0
24	International	I-FAC	I-TERM	0	0
25	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	0	27
26	(	O	O	0	0
27	DWC	S-GPE	O	0	0
28	)	O	O	0	0
29	.	O	O	0	0

1	According	O	O	0	0
2	to	O	O	0	0
3	the	O	O	0	0
4	logistics	O	B-TERM	0	0
5	company	O	E-TERM	1	11
6	,	O	O	0	0
7	the	O	O	0	0
8	building	O	O	0	0
9	is	O	O	0	0
10	its	O	O	0	0
11	first	S-MISC	O	1	15
12	fully	O	O	0	0
13	solar-powered	O	B-TERM	0	0
14	logistics	O	I-TERM	0	0
15	center	O	E-TERM	0	17
16	in	O	O	0	0
17	Dubai	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
18	and	O	O	0	0
19	will	O	O	0	0
20	serve	O	O	0	0
21	as	O	O	0	0
22	a	O	O	0	0
23	base	O	O	0	0
24	for	O	O	0	0
25	the	O	O	0	0
26	company	O	O	0	0
27	's	O	O	0	0
28	long-term	O	B-TERM	0	0
29	plans	O	E-TERM	1	34
30	to	O	O	0	0
31	develop	O	O	0	0
32	a	O	O	0	0
33	logistics	O	B-TERM	0	0
34	hub	O	E-TERM	0	38
35	in	O	O	0	0
36	the	B-MISC	O	0	0
37	Middle	I-MISC	B-TERM	0	0
38	East	E-MISC	E-TERM	0	0
39	.	O	O	0	0

1	Located	O	O	0	0
2	in	O	O	0	0
3	the	O	O	0	0
4	Dubai	B-MISC	S-TERM	0	0
5	South	E-MISC	O	0	0
6	logistics	O	O	0	0
7	area	O	O	0	0
8	free	O	O	0	0
9	trade	O	O	0	0
10	zone	O	O	0	0
11	(	O	O	0	0
12	FTZ	O	O	0	0
13	)	O	O	0	0
14	,	O	O	0	0
15	the	O	O	0	0
16	temperature-controlled	O	B-TERM	0	0
17	logistics	O	I-TERM	0	0
18	facility	O	E-TERM	1	22
19	comprises	O	O	0	0
20	33,000	B-MISC	O	0	0
21	square	I-MISC	O	0	0
22	meters	E-MISC	O	1	28
23	total	O	O	0	0
24	,	O	O	0	0
25	with	O	O	0	0
26	3,000	B-MISC	O	0	0
27	square	I-MISC	O	0	0
28	meters	E-MISC	O	0	0
29	in	O	O	0	0
30	mezzanine	O	O	0	0
31	space	O	O	0	0
32	for	O	O	0	0
33	value-added	O	O	0	0
34	services	O	O	0	0
35	and	O	O	0	0
36	warehouse	O	O	0	0
37	space	O	O	0	0
38	for	O	O	0	0
39	90,000	S-CARDINAL	O	1	40
40	Euro	S-MISC	O	0	0
41	pallets	O	O	0	0
42	.	O	O	0	0

1	In	O	O	0	0
2	addition	O	O	0	0
3	to	O	O	0	0
4	various	O	O	0	0
5	value-added	O	O	0	0
6	and	O	O	0	0
7	distribution	O	O	0	0
8	services	O	O	0	0
9	,	O	O	0	0
10	the	O	O	0	0
11	facility	O	O	0	0
12	can	O	O	0	0
13	provide	O	O	0	0
14	storage	O	O	0	0
15	for	O	O	0	0
16	hazardous	O	O	0	0
17	material	O	O	0	0
18	in	O	O	0	0
19	transit	O	O	0	0
20	and	O	O	0	0
21	offers	O	O	0	0
22	direct	O	O	0	0
23	connections	O	O	0	0
24	to	O	O	0	0
25	local	O	O	0	0
26	cargo	O	O	0	0
27	hubs	O	O	0	0
28	DWC	S-ORG	O	0	32
29	and	O	O	0	0
30	Jebel	B-FAC	O	0	0
31	Ali	I-FAC	O	0	0
32	Port	E-FAC	O	0	0
33	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	facility	O	O	0	0
3	helps	O	O	0	0
4	fulfill	O	O	0	0
5	two	S-CARDINAL	O	1	9
6	of	O	O	0	0
7	DB	B-ORG	O	0	0
8	Schenker	I-ORG	O	0	0
9	's	E-ORG	O	0	0
10	larger	O	O	0	0
11	initiatives	O	O	0	0
12	targeted	O	O	0	0
13	at	O	O	0	0
14	supporting	O	O	0	0
15	environmental	O	O	0	0
16	sustainability	O	O	0	0
17	and	O	O	0	0
18	developing	O	O	0	0
19	a	O	O	0	0
20	Middle	B-MISC	B-TERM	0	0
21	Eastern	E-MISC	E-TERM	1	24
22	regional	O	O	0	0
23	logistics	O	B-TERM	0	0
24	hub	O	E-TERM	0	0
25	.	O	O	0	0

1	Fully	O	O	0	0
2	powered	O	O	0	0
3	by	O	O	0	0
4	solar	O	O	0	0
5	energy	O	O	0	0
6	,	O	O	0	0
7	DLC	B-MISC	O	0	0
8	II	E-MISC	O	1	20
9	is	O	O	0	0
10	part	O	O	0	0
11	of	O	O	0	0
12	a	O	O	0	0
13	series	O	O	0	0
14	of	O	O	0	0
15	"	O	O	0	0
16	Eco	B-MISC	O	0	0
17	Warehouses	I-MISC	O	0	0
18	"	I-MISC	O	0	0
19	DB	I-MISC	O	0	0
20	Schenker	E-MISC	O	0	0
21	is	O	O	0	0
22	constructing	O	O	0	0
23	worldwide	O	O	0	0
24	to	O	O	0	0
25	reduce	O	O	0	0
26	carbon	O	O	0	0
27	emissions	O	O	0	0
28	and	O	O	0	0
29	costs	O	O	0	0
30	.	O	O	0	0

1	Currently	O	O	0	0
2	,	O	O	0	0
3	the	O	O	0	0
4	company	O	O	0	0
5	hosts	O	O	0	0
6	five	S-CARDINAL	O	1	11
7	other	O	O	0	0
8	green	O	O	0	0
9	warehouses	O	O	0	0
10	in	O	O	0	0
11	Singapore	S-GPE	O	0	13
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	Helsinki	S-GPE	O	0	15
14	,	O	O	0	0
15	Klagenfurt	S-GPE	O	0	17
16	,	O	O	0	0
17	Tilburg	S-GPE	O	0	19
18	and	O	O	0	0
19	Dortmund	S-GPE	O	0	0
20	.	O	O	0	0

1	Additionally	O	O	0	0
2	,	O	O	0	0
3	DB	B-ORG	O	0	0
4	Schenker	E-ORG	O	0	0
5	is	O	O	0	0
6	working	O	O	0	0
7	to	O	O	0	0
8	convert	O	O	0	0
9	all	O	O	0	0
10	the	O	O	0	0
11	lighting	O	O	0	0
12	in	O	O	0	0
13	its	O	O	0	0
14	warehouses	O	O	0	0
15	to	O	O	0	0
16	LED	O	O	0	0
17	lighting	O	O	0	0
18	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	completed	O	O	0	0
3	construction	O	O	0	0
4	of	O	O	0	0
5	DLC	B-ORG	O	0	0
6	II	E-ORG	O	0	10
7	also	O	O	0	0
8	concludes	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	second	S-MISC	O	1	12
11	of	O	O	0	0
12	three	S-CARDINAL	O	1	18
13	development	O	O	0	0
14	phases	O	O	0	0
15	of	O	O	0	0
16	the	O	O	0	0
17	logistics	O	B-TERM	0	0
18	company	O	E-TERM	1	24
19	's	O	O	0	0
20	broader	O	O	0	0
21	expansion	O	O	0	0
22	plans	O	O	0	0
23	in	O	O	0	0
24	Dubai	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
25	.	O	O	0	0

1	Currently	O	O	0	0
2	,	O	O	0	0
3	the	O	O	0	0
4	facility	O	O	0	0
5	hosts	O	O	0	0
6	the	O	O	0	0
7	operations	O	O	0	0
8	of	O	O	0	0
9	one	S-CARDINAL	O	1	13
10	of	O	O	0	0
11	DB	B-ORG	O	0	0
12	Schenker	I-ORG	O	0	0
13	's	E-ORG	O	1	18
14	major	O	O	0	0
15	local	O	O	0	0
16	partners	O	O	0	0
17	,	O	O	0	0
18	Unilever	S-ORG	O	0	0
19	.	O	O	0	0

1	By	O	O	0	0
2	2021	S-DATE	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	DB	B-ORG	O	0	0
5	Schenker	E-ORG	O	1	15
6	plans	O	O	0	0
7	to	O	O	0	0
8	achieve	O	O	0	0
9	a	O	O	0	0
10	total	O	O	0	0
11	capacity	O	O	0	0
12	of	O	O	0	0
13	80,000	B-MISC	O	0	0
14	square	I-MISC	O	0	0
15	meters	E-MISC	O	0	0
16	in	O	O	0	0
17	logistics	O	O	0	0
18	space	O	O	0	0
19	in	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	city	O	O	0	0
22	.	O	O	0	0

1	Subscribe	O	O	0	0
2	to	O	O	0	0
3	the	O	O	0	0
4	Cargo	B-ORG	O	0	0
5	Airport	I-ORG	O	0	0
6	Growth	I-ORG	O	0	0
7	Summit	E-ORG	O	0	0
8	email	O	O	0	0
9	list	O	O	0	0
10	for	O	O	0	0
11	more	O	O	0	0
12	news	O	O	0	0
13	and	O	O	0	0
14	event	O	O	0	0
15	updates	O	O	0	0
16	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	B-MISC	O	0	0
2	Cargo	I-MISC	O	0	0
3	Airport	I-MISC	O	0	0
4	Growth	I-MISC	O	0	0
5	Summit	E-MISC	O	0	0
6	,	O	O	0	0
7	a	O	O	0	0
8	new	O	O	0	0
9	event	O	O	0	0
10	diving	O	O	0	0
11	into	O	O	0	0
12	the	O	O	0	0
13	strategies	O	O	0	0
14	airport	O	O	0	0
15	executives	O	O	0	0
16	need	O	O	0	0
17	to	O	O	0	0
18	improve	O	O	0	0
19	their	O	O	0	0
20	value	O	O	0	0
21	proposition	O	O	0	0
22	to	O	O	0	0
23	carriers	O	O	0	0
24	and	O	O	0	0
25	forwarders	O	O	0	0
26	,	O	O	0	0
27	will	O	O	0	0
28	take	O	O	0	0
29	place	O	O	0	0
30	June	B-DATE	O	0	0
31	3-4	E-DATE	O	0	0
32	at	O	O	0	0
33	the	O	O	0	0
34	Conrad	S-GPE	O	1	35
35	Miami	S-GPE	O	0	0
36	.	O	O	0	0

1	For	O	O	0	0
2	more	O	O	0	0
3	information	O	O	0	0
4	on	O	O	0	0
5	the	O	O	0	0
6	event	O	O	0	0
7	,	O	O	0	0
8	visit	O	O	0	0
9	www.CargoAirportGrowthSummit.com	O	O	0	0
10	.	O	O	0	0

1	IATA	S-ORG	O	0	0
2	names	O	O	0	0
3	innovation	O	B-TERM	0	0
4	award	O	I-TERM	0	0
5	finalists	O	E-TERM	0	0

1	IATA	S-ORG	O	1	5
2	has	O	O	0	0
3	announced	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	five	S-CARDINAL	O	1	13
6	finalists	O	O	0	0
7	for	O	O	0	0
8	its	O	O	0	0
9	2017	S-DATE	B-TERM	0	0
10	air	O	I-TERM	0	0
11	cargo	O	I-TERM	0	0
12	innovation	O	I-TERM	0	0
13	awards	O	E-TERM	0	0
14	,	O	O	0	0
15	whose	O	O	0	0
16	ideas	O	O	0	0
17	will	O	O	0	0
18	be	O	O	0	0
19	subject	O	O	0	0
20	to	O	O	0	0
21	a	O	O	0	0
22	vote	O	O	0	0
23	at	O	O	0	0
24	the	O	O	0	0
25	airline	O	B-TERM	0	0
26	association	O	E-TERM	0	30
27	's	O	O	0	0
28	World	B-MISC	B-TERM	0	0
29	Cargo	I-MISC	I-TERM	0	0
30	Symposium	E-MISC	E-TERM	0	33
31	in	O	O	0	0
32	Abu	B-GPE	O	0	0
33	Dhabi	E-GPE	O	0	0
34	next	B-DATE	O	0	0
35	month	E-DATE	O	0	0
36	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	final	O	O	0	0
3	five	S-CARDINAL	O	1	6
4	out	O	O	0	0
5	of	O	O	0	0
6	46	S-CARDINAL	O	1	7
7	entries	O	S-TERM	1	11
8	,	O	O	0	0
9	in	O	O	0	0
10	alphabetical	O	B-TERM	0	0
11	order	O	E-TERM	1	17
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	are	O	O	0	0
14	:	O	O	0	0
15	Astral	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
16	Aerial	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
17	Solutions	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	22
18	–	O	O	0	0
19	UTM	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
20	Concept	I-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
21	for	I-ORG	O	0	0
22	Africa	E-ORG	O	0	24
23	(	O	O	0	0
24	Kenya	S-GPE	O	1	33
25	)	O	O	0	0
26	;	O	O	0	0
27	Etihad	B-ORG	O	0	0
28	Cargo	I-ORG	O	0	0
29	–	I-ORG	O	0	0
30	Smart	I-ORG	O	0	0
31	Electric	I-ORG	O	0	0
32	Cool	I-ORG	O	0	0
33	Dolly	E-ORG	O	0	35
34	(	O	O	0	0
35	UAE	S-GPE	O	1	38
36	)	O	O	0	0
37	;	O	O	0	0
38	Gate	S-ORG	O	1	45
39	chain	O	O	0	0
40	–	O	O	0	0
41	Redefining	O	O	0	0
42	trade	O	O	0	0
43	with	O	O	0	0
44	block	O	B-TERM	0	0
45	chain	O	E-TERM	0	47
46	(	O	O	0	0
47	Switzerland	S-GPE	O	1	55
48	)	O	O	0	0
49	;	O	O	0	0
50	Jettainer	B-ORG	O	0	0
51	–	I-ORG	O	0	0
52	Innovative	I-ORG	O	0	0
53	Decision	I-ORG	O	0	0
54	Support	I-ORG	O	0	0
55	System	E-ORG	O	1	60
56	(	O	O	0	0
57	DSS	O	O	0	0
58	)	O	O	0	0
59	(	O	O	0	0
60	Germany	S-GPE	O	1	69
61	)	O	O	0	0
62	;	O	O	0	0
63	OpenAirlines	O	O	0	0
64	–	O	O	0	0
65	SkyBreathe	O	O	0	0
66	Fuel	O	O	0	0
67	Efficiency	O	O	0	0
68	(	O	O	0	0
69	France	S-GPE	O	0	0
70	)	O	O	0	0
71	.	O	O	0	0

1	Submissions	O	S-TERM	0	0
2	covered	O	O	0	0
3	a	O	O	0	0
4	wide-range	O	O	0	0
5	of	O	O	0	0
6	topics	O	O	0	0
7	including	O	O	0	0
8	drones	O	O	0	0
9	,	O	O	0	0
10	ULDs	O	O	0	0
11	,	O	O	0	0
12	special	O	O	0	0
13	cargo	O	O	0	0
14	and	O	O	0	0
15	dangerous	O	O	0	0
16	goods	O	O	0	0
17	.	O	O	0	0

1	IATA	S-ORG	O	0	0
2	said	O	O	0	0
3	that	O	O	0	0
4	applicants	O	O	0	0
5	used	O	O	0	0
6	"	O	O	0	0
7	cutting	O	O	0	0
8	edge	O	O	0	0
9	and	O	O	0	0
10	emerging	O	O	0	0
11	technologies	O	O	0	0
12	such	O	O	0	0
13	as	O	O	0	0
14	block	O	B-TERM	0	0
15	chain	O	E-TERM	0	0
16	and	O	O	0	0
17	big	O	O	0	0
18	data	O	O	0	0
19	to	O	O	0	0
20	develop	O	O	0	0
21	innovative	O	O	0	0
22	solutions	O	O	0	0
23	to	O	O	0	0
24	benefit	O	O	0	0
25	the	O	O	0	0
26	industry	O	O	0	0
27	"	O	O	0	0
28	.	O	O	0	0

1	Seven	S-CARDINAL	O	1	9
2	members	O	O	0	0
3	of	O	O	0	0
4	an	O	O	0	0
5	independent	O	O	0	0
6	jury	O	O	0	0
7	evaluated	O	O	0	0
8	the	O	O	0	0
9	submissions	O	S-TERM	0	0
10	based	O	O	0	0
11	upon	O	O	0	0
12	their	O	O	0	0
13	assessment	O	O	0	0
14	of	O	O	0	0
15	the	O	O	0	0
16	idea	O	O	0	0
17	,	O	O	0	0
18	its	O	O	0	0
19	coherence	O	O	0	0
20	to	O	O	0	0
21	the	O	O	0	0
22	program	O	O	0	0
23	objectives	O	O	0	0
24	,	O	O	0	0
25	its	O	O	0	0
26	potential	O	O	0	0
27	for	O	O	0	0
28	value	O	O	0	0
29	creation	O	O	0	0
30	,	O	O	0	0
31	and	O	O	0	0
32	the	O	O	0	0
33	likelihood	O	O	0	0
34	of	O	O	0	0
35	achieving	O	O	0	0
36	success	O	O	0	0
37	based	O	O	0	0
38	upon	O	O	0	0
39	the	O	O	0	0
40	submitting	O	O	0	0
41	team	O	O	0	0
42	's	O	O	0	0
43	plan	O	O	0	0
44	and	O	O	0	0
45	experience	O	O	0	0
46	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	finalists	O	O	0	0
3	will	O	O	0	0
4	present	O	O	0	0
5	their	O	O	0	0
6	project	O	O	0	0
7	at	O	O	0	0
8	the	O	O	0	0
9	11th	S-MISC	O	1	10
10	WCS	S-ORG	O	0	13
11	in	O	O	0	0
12	Abu	B-GPE	O	0	0
13	Dhabi	E-GPE	O	0	0
14	which	O	O	0	0
15	takes	O	O	0	0
16	place	O	O	0	0
17	March	B-DATE	O	0	0
18	14-16	E-DATE	O	0	0
19	.	O	O	0	0

1	Delegates	O	O	0	0
2	will	O	O	0	0
3	then	O	O	0	0
4	vote	O	O	0	0
5	for	O	O	0	0
6	their	O	O	0	0
7	preferred	O	O	0	0
8	innovation	O	O	0	0
9	and	O	O	0	0
10	the	O	O	0	0
11	winner	O	O	0	0
12	will	O	O	0	0
13	receive	O	O	0	0
14	$	O	O	0	0
15	20,000	S-MISC	O	0	0
16	during	O	O	0	0
17	the	O	O	0	0
18	conference	O	O	0	0
19	's	O	O	0	0
20	closing	O	O	0	0
21	plenary	O	O	0	0
22	.	O	O	0	0

1	You	O	O	0	0
2	have	O	O	0	0
3	got	O	O	0	0
4	to	O	O	0	0
5	be	O	O	0	0
6	in	O	O	0	0
7	it	O	O	0	0
8	,	O	O	0	0
9	to	O	O	0	0
10	win	O	O	0	0
11	it	O	O	0	0
12	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	B-MISC	O	0	0
2	Air	I-MISC	O	0	0
3	Cargo	I-MISC	O	0	0
4	News	I-MISC	O	0	0
5	Cargo	I-MISC	O	0	0
6	Airline	I-MISC	O	0	0
7	of	I-MISC	O	0	0
8	the	I-MISC	O	0	0
9	Year	E-MISC	O	1	15
10	awards	O	O	0	0
11	are	O	O	0	0
12	now	O	O	0	0
13	open	O	O	0	0
14	for	O	O	0	0
15	entries	O	S-TERM	0	0
16	.	O	O	0	0

1	There	O	O	0	0
2	are	O	O	0	0
3	six	S-CARDINAL	O	1	12
4	categories	O	O	0	0
5	in	O	O	0	0
6	total	O	O	0	0
7	to	O	O	0	0
8	enter	O	O	0	0
9	this	B-DATE	O	0	0
10	year	E-DATE	O	0	0
11	,	O	O	0	0
12	one	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
13	more	O	O	0	0
14	than	O	O	0	0
15	last	B-DATE	O	0	0
16	year	E-DATE	O	0	0
17	due	O	O	0	0
18	to	O	O	0	0
19	the	O	O	0	0
20	creation	O	O	0	0
21	of	O	O	0	0
22	the	O	O	0	0
23	innovation	O	O	0	0
24	award	O	O	0	0
25	,	O	O	0	0
26	sponsored	O	O	0	0
27	by	O	O	0	0
28	Heathrow	B-ORG	O	0	0
29	Cargo	E-ORG	O	0	0
30	.	O	O	0	0

1	Please	O	O	0	0
2	submit	O	O	0	0
3	your	O	O	0	0
4	entries	O	S-TERM	0	0
5	by	O	O	0	0
6	Monday	B-DATE	O	0	0
7	March	I-DATE	O	0	0
8	27	I-DATE	O	0	0
9	,	I-DATE	O	0	0
10	2017	E-DATE	O	0	0
11	.	O	O	0	0

1	Entries	O	S-TERM	0	0
2	submitted	O	O	0	0
3	after	O	O	0	0
4	this	O	O	0	0
5	time	O	O	0	0
6	will	O	O	0	0
7	not	O	O	0	0
8	be	O	O	0	0
9	eligible	O	O	0	0
10	.	O	O	0	0

1	Click	O	O	0	0
2	here	O	O	0	0
3	to	O	O	0	0
4	visit	O	O	0	0
5	the	O	O	0	0
6	awards	O	O	0	0
7	website	O	O	0	0
8	.	O	O	0	0

1	AA	B-ORG	O	0	0
2	Cargo	E-ORG	O	1	4
3	completes	O	O	0	0
4	first	S-MISC	O	0	0
5	phase	O	O	0	0
6	of	O	O	0	0
7	digital	O	B-TERM	0	0
8	upgrade	O	E-TERM	0	0

1	American	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Airlines	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
3	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	7
4	has	O	O	0	0
5	completed	O	O	0	0
6	the	O	O	0	0
7	first	S-MISC	O	1	12
8	phase	O	O	0	0
9	of	O	O	0	0
10	its	O	O	0	0
11	largest	O	B-TERM	0	0
12	investment	O	E-TERM	1	20
13	with	O	O	0	0
14	the	O	O	0	0
15	role	O	O	0	0
16	out	O	O	0	0
17	of	O	O	0	0
18	its	O	O	0	0
19	management	O	B-TERM	0	0
20	system	O	E-TERM	0	0
21	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	system	O	O	0	0
3	replaces	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	majority	O	O	0	0
6	of	O	O	0	0
7	legacy	O	B-TERM	0	0
8	technology	O	E-TERM	1	11
9	,	O	O	0	0
10	narrowing	O	O	0	0
11	90	S-CARDINAL	O	1	17
12	systems	O	O	0	0
13	down	O	O	0	0
14	to	O	O	0	0
15	less	B-CARDINAL	O	0	0
16	than	I-CARDINAL	O	0	0
17	10	E-CARDINAL	O	1	21
18	,	O	O	0	0
19	upgrading	O	O	0	0
20	customer	O	B-TERM	0	0
21	experience	O	E-TERM	0	0
22	and	O	O	0	0
23	modernising	O	O	0	0
24	the	O	O	0	0
25	business	O	O	0	0
26	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	transition	O	O	0	0
3	affects	O	O	0	0
4	more	B-CARDINAL	O	0	0
5	than	I-CARDINAL	O	0	0
6	8,000	E-CARDINAL	B-TERM	0	0
7	team	O	I-TERM	0	0
8	members	O	E-TERM	1	13
9	and	O	O	0	0
10	more	B-CARDINAL	O	0	0
11	than	I-CARDINAL	O	0	0
12	30,000	E-CARDINAL	B-TERM	0	0
13	customers	O	E-TERM	0	0
14	.	O	O	0	0

1	A	O	O	0	0
2	team	O	O	0	0
3	of	O	O	0	0
4	more	B-CARDINAL	O	0	0
5	than	I-CARDINAL	O	0	0
6	700	E-CARDINAL	B-TERM	0	0
7	people	O	E-TERM	1	9
8	across	O	O	0	0
9	300	S-CARDINAL	O	1	14
10	locations	O	O	0	0
11	and	O	O	0	0
12	more	B-CARDINAL	O	0	0
13	than	I-CARDINAL	O	0	0
14	150	E-CARDINAL	O	0	0
15	business	O	O	0	0
16	,	O	O	0	0
17	technology	O	O	0	0
18	and	O	O	0	0
19	vendor	O	O	0	0
20	partners	O	O	0	0
21	at	O	O	0	0
22	the	O	O	0	0
23	new	O	O	0	0
24	headquarters	O	O	0	0
25	in	O	O	0	0
26	Fort	B-GPE	O	0	0
27	Worth	E-GPE	O	0	29
28	,	O	O	0	0
29	Texas	S-GPE	O	0	0
30	supported	O	O	0	0
31	the	O	O	0	0
32	implementation	O	O	0	0
33	process	O	O	0	0
34	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	initiative	O	O	0	0
3	has	O	O	0	0
4	been	O	O	0	0
5	led	O	O	0	0
6	by	O	O	0	0
7	vice	O	O	0	0
8	president	O	O	0	0
9	strategy	O	O	0	0
10	and	O	O	0	0
11	development	O	O	0	0
12	Jessica	B-PERSON	O	0	0
13	Tyler	E-PERSON	O	0	0
14	,	O	O	0	0
15	and	O	O	0	0
16	her	O	O	0	0
17	team	O	O	0	0
18	have	O	O	0	0
19	been	O	O	0	0
20	united	O	O	0	0
21	in	O	O	0	0
22	a	O	O	0	0
23	people-first	O	O	0	0
24	philosophy	O	O	0	0
25	.	O	O	0	0

1	Tyler	S-PERSON	O	0	0
2	says	O	O	0	0
3	:	O	O	0	0
4	"	O	O	0	0
5	The	O	O	0	0
6	technology	O	O	0	0
7	changes	O	O	0	0
8	are	O	O	0	0
9	complex	O	O	0	0
10	and	O	O	0	0
11	massive	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	but	O	O	0	0
14	the	O	O	0	0
15	work	O	O	0	0
16	to	O	O	0	0
17	support	O	O	0	0
18	people	O	O	0	0
19	through	O	O	0	0
20	this	O	O	0	0
21	kind	O	O	0	0
22	of	O	O	0	0
23	journey	O	O	0	0
24	is	O	O	0	0
25	just	O	O	0	0
26	as	O	O	0	0
27	complex	O	O	0	0
28	and	O	O	0	0
29	has	O	O	0	0
30	been	O	O	0	0
31	a	O	O	0	0
32	priority	O	O	0	0
33	for	O	O	0	0
34	us	O	O	0	0
35	.	O	O	0	0

1	While	O	O	0	0
2	standing	O	O	0	0
3	up	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	new	O	O	0	0
6	system	O	O	0	0
7	has	O	O	0	0
8	been	O	O	0	0
9	a	O	O	0	0
10	huge	O	O	0	0
11	accomplishment	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	I	O	O	0	0
14	'm	O	O	0	0
15	most	O	O	0	0
16	proud	O	O	0	0
17	of	O	O	0	0
18	our	O	O	0	0
19	people	O	O	0	0
20	.	O	O	0	0

1	Even	O	O	0	0
2	with	O	O	0	0
3	the	O	O	0	0
4	challenges	O	O	0	0
5	of	O	O	0	0
6	a	O	O	0	0
7	project	O	O	0	0
8	this	O	O	0	0
9	size	O	O	0	0
10	,	O	O	0	0
11	we	O	O	0	0
12	continue	O	O	0	0
13	to	O	O	0	0
14	have	O	O	0	0
15	a	O	O	0	0
16	'	O	O	0	0
17	bring	O	O	0	0
18	it	O	O	0	0
19	on	O	O	0	0
20	'	O	O	0	0
21	attitude	O	O	0	0
22	and	O	O	0	0
23	remain	O	O	0	0
24	focused	O	O	0	0
25	on	O	O	0	0
26	moving	O	O	0	0
27	forward	O	O	0	0
28	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	way	O	O	0	0
3	the	O	O	0	0
4	team	O	O	0	0
5	cares	O	O	0	0
6	for	O	O	0	0
7	one	O	O	0	0
8	another	O	O	0	0
9	is	O	O	0	0
10	what	O	O	0	0
11	makes	O	O	0	0
12	us	O	O	0	0
13	uniquely	O	O	0	0
14	ready	O	O	0	0
15	for	O	O	0	0
16	change	O	O	0	0
17	.	O	O	0	0
18	"	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	system	O	O	0	0
3	is	O	O	0	0
4	powered	O	O	0	0
5	by	O	O	0	0
6	the	B-ORG	O	0	0
7	IBS	I-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
8	Software	I-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
9	's	E-ORG	O	1	10
10	iCargo	S-MISC	O	1	20
11	platform	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	which	O	O	0	0
14	improves	O	O	0	0
15	sales	O	O	0	0
16	,	O	O	0	0
17	operations	O	O	0	0
18	,	O	O	0	0
19	customer	O	B-TERM	0	0
20	experience	O	E-TERM	0	0
21	and	O	O	0	0
22	accounting	O	O	0	0
23	,	O	O	0	0
24	allowing	O	O	0	0
25	for	O	O	0	0
26	more	O	O	0	0
27	efficient	O	O	0	0
28	online	O	O	0	0
29	channels	O	O	0	0
30	,	O	O	0	0
31	better	O	O	0	0
32	tracking	O	O	0	0
33	,	O	O	0	0
34	greater	O	O	0	0
35	warehouse	O	O	0	0
36	efficiency	O	O	0	0
37	and	O	O	0	0
38	a	O	O	0	0
39	robust	O	O	0	0
40	back-end	O	O	0	0
41	system	O	O	0	0
42	.	O	O	0	0

1	Philip	B-PERSON	O	0	0
2	Scaria	E-PERSON	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	program	O	O	0	0
5	manager	O	O	0	0
6	for	O	O	0	0
7	IBS	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
8	Software	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	20
9	says	O	O	0	0
10	:	O	O	0	0
11	"	O	O	0	0
12	The	O	O	0	0
13	scale	O	O	0	0
14	and	O	O	0	0
15	size	O	O	0	0
16	of	O	O	0	0
17	the	O	O	0	0
18	American	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
19	Airlines	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
20	Cargo	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
21	enterprise	O	O	0	0
22	challenged	O	O	0	0
23	us	O	O	0	0
24	to	O	O	0	0
25	dig	O	O	0	0
26	deep	O	O	0	0
27	into	O	O	0	0
28	our	O	O	0	0
29	experience	O	O	0	0
30	and	O	O	0	0
31	skills	O	O	0	0
32	to	O	O	0	0
33	lead	O	O	0	0
34	this	O	O	0	0
35	implementation	O	O	0	0
36	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	commitment	O	O	0	0
3	of	O	O	0	0
4	team	O	O	0	0
5	members	O	O	0	0
6	across	O	O	0	0
7	the	O	O	0	0
8	globe	O	O	0	0
9	and	O	O	0	0
10	their	O	O	0	0
11	willingness	O	O	0	0
12	to	O	O	0	0
13	embrace	O	O	0	0
14	change	O	O	0	0
15	has	O	O	0	0
16	made	O	O	0	0
17	all	O	O	0	0
18	the	O	O	0	0
19	difference	O	O	0	0
20	.	O	O	0	0
21	"	O	O	0	0

1	Tigers	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	4
2	doubles	O	O	0	0
3	its	O	O	0	0
4	Miami	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
5	storage	O	O	0	0
6	capacity	O	S-TERM	0	0

1	Hong	B-GPE	B-TERM	0	0
2	Kong-based	E-GPE	I-TERM	1	5
3	logistics	O	I-TERM	0	0
4	company	O	E-TERM	0	0
5	Tigers	S-ORG	O	1	8
6	grows	O	O	0	0
7	North	B-MISC	B-TERM	0	0
8	American	E-MISC	I-TERM	1	15
9	presence	O	E-TERM	0	0
10	by	O	O	0	0
11	nearly	O	O	0	0
12	doubling	O	O	0	0
13	its	O	O	0	0
14	storage	O	B-TERM	0	0
15	capacity	O	E-TERM	0	17
16	in	O	O	0	0
17	Miami	S-GPE	O	1	22
18	to	O	O	0	0
19	about	B-MISC	O	0	0
20	31,000	I-MISC	B-TERM	0	0
21	square	I-MISC	I-TERM	0	0
22	feet	E-MISC	E-TERM	1	29
23	in	O	O	0	0
24	a	O	O	0	0
25	move	O	O	0	0
26	to	O	O	0	0
27	a	O	O	0	0
28	new	O	B-TERM	0	0
29	facility	O	E-TERM	0	0
30	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	investment	O	O	0	0
3	will	O	O	0	0
4	allow	O	O	0	0
5	Tigers	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	15
6	to	O	O	0	0
7	both	O	O	0	0
8	"	O	O	0	0
9	grow	O	O	0	0
10	our	O	O	0	0
11	focus	O	O	0	0
12	on	O	O	0	0
13	the	O	O	0	0
14	Latin	B-MISC	B-TERM	0	0
15	American	E-MISC	I-TERM	0	0
16	region	O	E-TERM	0	0
17	,	O	O	0	0
18	as	O	O	0	0
19	well	O	O	0	0
20	as	O	O	0	0
21	expand	O	O	0	0
22	our	O	O	0	0
23	capabilities	O	O	0	0
24	to	O	O	0	0
25	service	O	O	0	0
26	the	O	O	0	0
27	growing	O	O	0	0
28	e-commerce	O	B-TERM	0	0
29	market	O	E-TERM	0	0
30	,	O	O	0	0
31	"	O	O	0	0
32	branch	O	B-TERM	0	0
33	manager	O	I-TERM	0	0
34	Elena	B-PERSON	I-TERM	0	0
35	Varona	E-PERSON	E-TERM	0	0
36	said	O	O	0	0
37	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	facility	O	O	0	0
3	is	O	O	0	0
4	bonded	O	O	0	0
5	and	O	O	0	0
6	serves	O	O	0	0
7	as	O	O	0	0
8	a	B-ORG	O	0	0
9	Container	I-ORG	O	0	0
10	Freight	I-ORG	O	0	0
11	Station	E-ORG	O	1	20
12	(	O	O	0	0
13	CFS	O	O	0	0
14	)	O	O	0	0
15	and	O	O	0	0
16	as	O	O	0	0
17	an	O	O	0	0
18	In-Bond	B-ORG	O	0	0
19	Export	I-ORG	O	0	0
20	Consolidation	E-ORG	O	0	22
21	(	O	O	0	0
22	IBEC	S-ORG	O	0	0
23	)	O	O	0	0
24	warehouse	O	O	0	0
25	to	O	O	0	0
26	service	O	O	0	0
27	shippers	O	O	0	0
28	that	O	O	0	0
29	conduct	O	O	0	0
30	trade	O	O	0	0
31	through	O	O	0	0
32	the	O	O	0	0
33	prominent	O	O	0	0
34	cross-border	O	O	0	0
35	hub	O	O	0	0
36	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	The	O	O	0	0
3	team	O	O	0	0
4	will	O	O	0	0
5	play	O	O	0	0
6	a	O	O	0	0
7	key	O	O	0	0
8	role	O	O	0	0
9	in	O	O	0	0
10	further	O	O	0	0
11	growing	O	O	0	0
12	our	O	O	0	0
13	eTigers	O	O	0	0
14	product	O	O	0	0
15	,	O	O	0	0
16	providing	O	O	0	0
17	end-to-end	O	O	0	0
18	supply	O	O	0	0
19	chain	O	O	0	0
20	solutions	O	O	0	0
21	for	O	O	0	0
22	online	O	O	0	0
23	customers	O	O	0	0
24	around	O	O	0	0
25	the	O	O	0	0
26	world	O	O	0	0
27	,	O	O	0	0
28	"	O	O	0	0
29	Varona	S-ORG	O	0	0
30	said	O	O	0	0
31	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	"	O	O	0	0
3	eTigers	S-ORG	O	1	7
4	"	O	O	0	0
5	platform	O	O	0	0
6	,	O	O	0	0
7	one	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
8	of	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	company	O	O	0	0
11	's	O	O	0	0
12	more	O	O	0	0
13	unique	O	O	0	0
14	initiatives	O	O	0	0
15	,	O	O	0	0
16	is	O	O	0	0
17	a	O	O	0	0
18	platform	O	O	0	0
19	for	O	O	0	0
20	shippers	O	O	0	0
21	to	O	O	0	0
22	host	O	O	0	0
23	their	O	O	0	0
24	products	O	O	0	0
25	.	O	O	0	0

1	Currently	O	O	0	0
2	,	O	O	0	0
3	merchants	O	O	0	0
4	of	O	O	0	0
5	products	O	O	0	0
6	like	O	O	0	0
7	wine	O	O	0	0
8	and	O	O	0	0
9	spirits	O	O	0	0
10	,	O	O	0	0
11	as	O	O	0	0
12	well	O	O	0	0
13	items	O	O	0	0
14	like	O	O	0	0
15	barbeque	O	O	0	0
16	grills	O	O	0	0
17	,	O	O	0	0
18	have	O	O	0	0
19	their	O	O	0	0
20	products	O	O	0	0
21	available	O	O	0	0
22	for	O	O	0	0
23	purchase	O	O	0	0
24	on	O	O	0	0
25	the	O	O	0	0
26	website	O	O	0	0
27	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	All	O	O	0	0
3	of	O	O	0	0
4	this	O	O	0	0
5	is	O	O	0	0
6	boosted	O	O	0	0
7	by	O	O	0	0
8	our	O	O	0	0
9	unique	O	O	0	0
10	forwarding	O	O	0	0
11	and	O	O	0	0
12	consolidation	O	O	0	0
13	capabilities	O	O	0	0
14	into	O	O	0	0
15	Latin	B-MISC	O	0	0
16	America	E-MISC	O	1	19
17	and	O	O	0	0
18	the	O	O	0	0
19	Caribbean	S-MISC	O	0	26
20	,	O	O	0	0
21	as	O	O	0	0
22	well	O	O	0	0
23	as	O	O	0	0
24	out	O	O	0	0
25	of	O	O	0	0
26	China	S-GPE	O	0	0
27	.	O	O	0	0
28	"	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	company	O	O	0	0
3	has	O	O	0	0
4	invested	O	O	0	0
5	in	O	O	0	0
6	the	O	O	0	0
7	e-commerce	O	O	0	0
8	movement	O	O	0	0
9	through	O	O	0	0
10	various	O	O	0	0
11	initiatives	O	O	0	0
12	.	O	O	0	0

1	In	O	O	0	0
2	late	B-DATE	O	0	0
3	2018	E-DATE	O	0	0
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	Tigers	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	8
6	launched	O	O	0	0
7	Cloud-based	B-ORG	O	0	0
8	SmartHub:Connect	E-ORG	O	0	0
9	,	O	O	0	0
10	a	O	O	0	0
11	freight	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	e-commerce	O	O	0	0
14	,	O	O	0	0
15	and	O	O	0	0
16	logistics	O	O	0	0
17	portal	O	O	0	0
18	offering	O	O	0	0
19	end-to-end	O	O	0	0
20	supply	O	O	0	0
21	chain	O	O	0	0
22	visibility	O	O	0	0
23	.	O	O	0	0

1	Later	B-DATE	O	0	0
2	this	I-DATE	O	0	0
3	year	E-DATE	O	0	0
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	Tigers	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	15
6	plans	O	O	0	0
7	to	O	O	0	0
8	launch	O	O	0	0
9	a	O	O	0	0
10	new	O	O	0	0
11	cross-border	O	O	0	0
12	e-commerce	O	O	0	0
13	service	O	O	0	0
14	from	O	O	0	0
15	Miami	S-GPE	O	1	17
16	to	O	O	0	0
17	Europe	S-MISC	O	0	0
18	,	O	O	0	0
19	of	O	O	0	0
20	which	O	O	0	0
21	details	O	O	0	0
22	are	O	O	0	0
23	forthcoming	O	O	0	0
24	.	O	O	0	0

1	Shippers	O	O	0	0
2	can	O	O	0	0
3	compare	O	O	0	0
4	air	O	O	0	0
5	and	O	O	0	0
6	ocean	O	B-TERM	0	0
7	options	O	E-TERM	0	0
8	via	O	O	0	0
9	myDHLi	O	O	0	0

1	DHL	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Global	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
3	Forwarding	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	9
4	has	O	O	0	0
5	launched	O	O	0	0
6	myDHLi	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
7	Quote	I-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
8	&	I-ORG	O	0	0
9	Book	E-ORG	O	1	13
10	,	O	O	0	0
11	an	O	O	0	0
12	online	O	B-TERM	0	0
13	service	O	E-TERM	1	20
14	for	O	O	0	0
15	comparing	O	O	0	0
16	quotations	O	O	0	0
17	and	O	O	0	0
18	making	O	O	0	0
19	instant	O	B-TERM	0	0
20	bookings	O	E-TERM	1	25
21	for	O	O	0	0
22	air	O	O	0	0
23	and	O	O	0	0
24	ocean	O	B-TERM	0	0
25	freight	O	E-TERM	1	30
26	and	O	O	0	0
27	even	O	O	0	0
28	for	O	O	0	0
29	door-to-door	O	B-TERM	0	0
30	shipments	O	E-TERM	0	0
31	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	service	O	O	0	0
3	guides	O	O	0	0
4	customers	O	O	0	0
5	through	O	O	0	0
6	the	O	O	0	0
7	"	O	O	0	0
8	quotation	O	O	0	0
9	journey	O	O	0	0
10	"	O	O	0	0
11	,	O	O	0	0
12	says	O	O	0	0
13	the	O	O	0	0
14	company	O	O	0	0
15	,	O	O	0	0
16	and	O	O	0	0
17	enables	O	O	0	0
18	them	O	O	0	0
19	to	O	O	0	0
20	directly	O	O	0	0
21	compare	O	O	0	0
22	available	O	O	0	0
23	options	O	O	0	0
24	,	O	O	0	0
25	including	O	O	0	0
26	DHL	B-MISC	O	0	0
27	Ocean	I-MISC	O	0	0
28	Connect	E-MISC	O	0	0
29	LCL	E-MISC	O	0	36
30	(	O	O	0	0
31	less-than-container-load	O	O	0	0
32	)	O	O	0	0
33	as	O	O	0	0
34	well	O	O	0	0
35	as	O	O	0	0
36	two	S-CARDINAL	O	0	40
37	speeds	O	O	0	0
38	of	O	O	0	0
39	air	O	B-TERM	0	0
40	freight	O	E-TERM	0	44
41	,	O	O	0	0
42	DHL	B-MISC	B-TERM	0	0
43	Air	I-MISC	I-TERM	0	0
44	Connect	E-MISC	E-TERM	0	48
45	and	O	O	0	0
46	DHL	B-MISC	B-TERM	0	0
47	Air	I-MISC	I-TERM	0	0
48	Economy	E-MISC	E-TERM	0	0
49	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	Users	O	O	0	0
3	can	O	O	0	0
4	also	O	O	0	0
5	book	O	O	0	0
6	transport	O	O	0	0
7	insurance	O	O	0	0
8	for	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	shipment	O	O	0	0
11	in	O	O	0	0
12	just	O	O	0	0
13	a	O	O	0	0
14	few	O	O	0	0
15	clicks	O	O	0	0
16	.	O	O	0	0
17	"	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	service	O	O	0	0
3	is	O	O	0	0
4	now	O	O	0	0
5	available	O	O	0	0
6	24	B-MISC	O	0	0
7	hours	E-MISC	O	0	0
8	a	O	O	0	0
9	day	O	O	0	0
10	,	O	O	0	0
11	seven	B-DATE	O	0	0
12	days	E-DATE	O	0	0
13	a	O	O	0	0
14	week	O	O	0	0
15	at	O	O	0	0
16	https://quote.mydhli.com	O	O	0	0
17	in	O	O	0	0
18	more	B-CARDINAL	O	0	0
19	than	I-CARDINAL	O	0	0
20	60	E-CARDINAL	O	0	0
21	countries	O	O	0	0
22	.	O	O	0	0

1	Tim	B-PERSON	O	0	0
2	Scharwath	E-PERSON	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	ceo	O	O	0	0
5	DHL	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
6	Global	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
7	Forwarding	I-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
8	,	I-ORG	O	0	0
9	Freight	E-ORG	O	0	0
10	,	O	O	0	0
11	says	O	O	0	0
12	it	O	O	0	0
13	is	O	O	0	0
14	"	O	O	0	0
15	the	O	O	0	0
16	industry	O	O	0	0
17	's	O	O	0	0
18	most	O	O	0	0
19	user-friendly	O	O	0	0
20	online	O	O	0	0
21	quotation	O	O	0	0
22	and	O	O	0	0
23	booking	O	O	0	0
24	service	O	O	0	0
25	.	O	O	0	0

1	With	O	O	0	0
2	this	O	O	0	0
3	new	O	O	0	0
4	service	O	O	0	0
5	,	O	O	0	0
6	we	O	O	0	0
7	continue	O	O	0	0
8	our	O	O	0	0
9	digital	O	O	0	0
10	transformation	O	O	0	0
11	with	O	O	0	0
12	the	O	O	0	0
13	clear	O	O	0	0
14	aspiration	O	O	0	0
15	to	O	O	0	0
16	become	O	O	0	0
17	the	O	O	0	0
18	leading	O	O	0	0
19	global	O	O	0	0
20	logistics	O	O	0	0
21	provider	O	O	0	0
22	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	We	O	O	0	0
3	listened	O	O	0	0
4	to	O	O	0	0
5	our	O	O	0	0
6	customers	O	O	0	0
7	'	O	O	0	0
8	needs	O	O	0	0
9	and	O	O	0	0
10	improved	O	O	0	0
11	upon	O	O	0	0
12	our	O	O	0	0
13	prior	O	O	0	0
14	online	O	O	0	0
15	tool	O	O	0	0
16	.	O	O	0	0

1	We	O	O	0	0
2	added	O	O	0	0
3	new	O	O	0	0
4	features	O	O	0	0
5	,	O	O	0	0
6	increased	O	O	0	0
7	coverage	O	O	0	0
8	and	O	O	0	0
9	implemented	O	O	0	0
10	a	O	O	0	0
11	highly	O	O	0	0
12	intuitive	O	O	0	0
13	user	O	O	0	0
14	interface	O	O	0	0
15	to	O	O	0	0
16	achieve	O	O	0	0
17	a	O	O	0	0
18	simple	O	O	0	0
19	and	O	O	0	0
20	effective	O	O	0	0
21	customer	O	O	0	0
22	experience	O	O	0	0
23	.	O	O	0	0
24	"	O	O	0	0

1	Transparent	O	O	0	0
2	air	O	O	0	0
3	and	O	O	0	0
4	ocean	O	B-TERM	0	0
5	freight	O	E-TERM	0	0
6	quotes	O	O	0	0
7	allow	O	O	0	0
8	customers	O	O	0	0
9	to	O	O	0	0
10	compare	O	O	0	0
11	rates	O	O	0	0
12	and	O	O	0	0
13	lead	O	O	0	0
14	times	O	O	0	0
15	to	O	O	0	0
16	select	O	O	0	0
17	the	O	O	0	0
18	best	O	O	0	0
19	option	O	O	0	0
20	.	O	O	0	0

1	For	O	O	0	0
2	air	O	B-TERM	0	0
3	freight	O	E-TERM	1	11
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	customers	O	O	0	0
6	can	O	O	0	0
7	choose	O	O	0	0
8	between	O	O	0	0
9	DHL	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
10	Air	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
11	Connect	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	with	O	O	0	0
14	a	O	O	0	0
15	typical	O	O	0	0
16	delivery	O	O	0	0
17	time	O	O	0	0
18	of	O	O	0	0
19	3-5	B-DATE	O	0	0
20	days	E-DATE	O	0	0
21	,	O	O	0	0
22	and	O	O	0	0
23	DHL	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
24	Air	I-ORG	I-TERM	0	0
25	Economy	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
26	,	O	O	0	0
27	a	O	O	0	0
28	cost	O	O	0	0
29	effective	O	O	0	0
30	option	O	O	0	0
31	that	O	O	0	0
32	uses	O	O	0	0
33	alternative	O	O	0	0
34	carriers	O	O	0	0
35	and	O	O	0	0
36	routes	O	O	0	0
37	to	O	O	0	0
38	deliver	O	O	0	0
39	in	O	O	0	0
40	about	B-DATE	O	0	0
41	5-7	I-DATE	O	0	0
42	days	E-DATE	O	0	0
43	.	O	O	0	0

1	Both	O	O	0	0
2	booking	O	O	0	0
3	options	O	O	0	0
4	cover	O	O	0	0
5	general	O	O	0	0
6	cargo	O	O	0	0
7	up	O	O	0	0
8	to	O	O	0	0
9	2,000	B-MISC	O	0	0
10	kg	E-MISC	O	0	0
11	per	O	O	0	0
12	shipment	O	O	0	0
13	.	O	O	0	0

1	Customers	O	O	0	0
2	can	O	O	0	0
3	save	O	O	0	0
4	quotes	O	O	0	0
5	,	O	O	0	0
6	which	O	O	0	0
7	are	O	O	0	0
8	valid	O	O	0	0
9	for	O	O	0	0
10	30	B-DATE	O	0	0
11	days	E-DATE	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	and	O	O	0	0
14	share	O	O	0	0
15	them	O	O	0	0
16	with	O	O	0	0
17	selected	O	O	0	0
18	recipients	O	O	0	0
19	via	O	O	0	0
20	e-mail	O	O	0	0
21	.	O	O	0	0

1	In	O	O	0	0
2	addition	O	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	customers	O	O	0	0
5	may	O	O	0	0
6	request	O	O	0	0
7	a	O	O	0	0
8	quote	O	O	0	0
9	for	O	O	0	0
10	special	O	O	0	0
11	cargo	O	O	0	0
12	,	O	O	0	0
13	including	O	O	0	0
14	dangerous	O	O	0	0
15	goods	O	O	0	0
16	,	O	O	0	0
17	lithium	O	O	0	0
18	batteries	O	O	0	0
19	and	O	O	0	0
20	non-stackable	O	O	0	0
21	cargo	O	O	0	0
22	,	O	O	0	0
23	which	O	O	0	0
24	is	O	O	0	0
25	provided	O	O	0	0
26	in	O	O	0	0
27	a	O	O	0	0
28	separate	O	O	0	0
29	email	O	O	0	0
30	from	O	O	0	0
31	DHL	S-ORG	O	0	0
32	.	O	O	0	0

1	Wood	O	O	0	0
2	chopped	O	O	0	0
3	as	O	O	0	0
4	Cargolux	S-PERSON	S-TERM	0	0
5	goes	O	O	0	0
6	greener	O	O	0	0
7	with	O	O	0	0
8	cardboard	O	B-TERM	0	0
9	fibre	O	I-TERM	0	0
10	substitute	O	E-TERM	0	0

1	Cargolux	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Airlines	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	8
3	has	O	O	0	0
4	signed	O	O	0	0
5	an	O	O	0	0
6	agreement	O	O	0	0
7	with	O	O	0	0
8	Trinkaus-Solutions	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
9	to	O	O	0	0
10	use	O	O	0	0
11	its	O	O	0	0
12	squAIR-timber	O	B-TERM	0	0
13	product	O	E-TERM	0	0
14	that	O	O	0	0
15	results	O	O	0	0
16	in	O	O	0	0
17	more	O	O	0	0
18	payload	O	O	0	0
19	and	O	O	0	0
20	lower	O	B-TERM	0	0
21	aircraft	O	I-TERM	0	0
22	fuel	O	I-TERM	0	0
23	consumption	O	E-TERM	0	0
24	.	O	O	0	0

1	Cargolux	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	7
2	said	O	O	0	0
3	that	O	O	0	0
4	it	O	O	0	0
5	is	O	O	0	0
6	the	O	O	0	0
7	first	S-MISC	O	1	14
8	airline	O	O	0	0
9	worldwide	O	O	0	0
10	to	O	O	0	0
11	introduce	O	O	0	0
12	the	O	O	0	0
13	lightweight	O	B-TERM	0	0
14	material	O	E-TERM	0	0
15	in	O	O	0	0
16	its	O	O	0	0
17	operations	O	O	0	0
18	,	O	O	0	0
19	and	O	O	0	0
20	currently	O	O	0	0
21	uses	O	O	0	0
22	it	O	O	0	0
23	on	O	O	0	0
24	all	O	O	0	0
25	pharma	O	O	0	0
26	shipments	O	O	0	0
27	out	O	O	0	0
28	of	O	O	0	0
29	its	O	O	0	0
30	home	O	O	0	0
31	hub	O	O	0	0
32	in	O	O	0	0
33	Luxembourg	S-GPE	O	0	0
34	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	all	O	O	0	0
3	cargo	O	O	0	0
4	carrier	O	O	0	0
5	said	O	O	0	0
6	that	O	O	0	0
7	the	O	O	0	0
8	cardboard	O	O	0	0
9	fiber	O	O	0	0
10	composite	O	O	0	0
11	beams	O	O	0	0
12	contain	O	O	0	0
13	only	O	O	0	0
14	raw	O	O	0	0
15	materials	O	O	0	0
16	from	O	O	0	0
17	sustainable	O	O	0	0
18	sources	O	O	0	0
19	that	O	O	0	0
20	differ	O	O	0	0
21	significantly	O	O	0	0
22	from	O	O	0	0
23	conventional	O	O	0	0
24	corrugated	O	O	0	0
25	products	O	O	0	0
26	and	O	O	0	0
27	provides	O	O	0	0
28	an	O	O	0	0
29	excellent	O	O	0	0
30	economic	O	O	0	0
31	and	O	O	0	0
32	ecological	O	O	0	0
33	long	O	O	0	0
34	term	O	O	0	0
35	replacement	O	O	0	0
36	for	O	O	0	0
37	wooden	O	B-TERM	0	0
38	material	O	E-TERM	0	0
39	.	O	O	0	0

1	Trinkaus-Solutions	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	14
2	says	O	O	0	0
3	that	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	beams	O	O	0	0
6	have	O	O	0	0
7	a	O	O	0	0
8	load	O	O	0	0
9	capacity	O	O	0	0
10	of	O	O	0	0
11	up	B-MISC	O	0	0
12	to	I-MISC	O	0	0
13	10	I-MISC	O	0	0
14	tons	E-MISC	O	0	0
15	.	O	O	0	0

1	At	O	O	0	0
2	the	O	O	0	0
3	same	O	O	0	0
4	time	O	O	0	0
5	,	O	O	0	0
6	they	O	O	0	0
7	are	O	O	0	0
8	significantly	O	O	0	0
9	lighter	O	O	0	0
10	than	O	O	0	0
11	the	O	O	0	0
12	conventional	O	O	0	0
13	wooden	O	O	0	0
14	beams	O	O	0	0
15	they	O	O	0	0
16	replace	O	O	0	0
17	,	O	O	0	0
18	with	O	O	0	0
19	a	O	O	0	0
20	weight	O	O	0	0
21	of	O	O	0	0
22	only	B-MISC	O	0	0
23	1.2	I-MISC	O	0	0
24	kg	I-MISC	O	0	0
25	per	I-MISC	O	0	0
26	meter	E-MISC	O	0	0
27	.	O	O	0	0

1	They	O	O	0	0
2	are	O	O	0	0
3	also	O	O	0	0
4	resistant	O	O	0	0
5	to	O	O	0	0
6	humidity	O	O	0	0
7	.	O	O	0	0

1	At	O	O	0	0
2	the	O	O	0	0
3	same	O	O	0	0
4	time	O	O	0	0
5	,	O	O	0	0
6	it	O	O	0	0
7	is	O	O	0	0
8	80	B-MISC	O	0	0
9	%	E-MISC	O	0	0
10	lighter	O	O	0	0
11	than	O	O	0	0
12	the	O	O	0	0
13	conventional	O	O	0	0
14	wood	O	O	0	0
15	it	O	O	0	0
16	replaces	O	O	0	0
17	,	O	O	0	0
18	thus	O	O	0	0
19	allowing	O	O	0	0
20	more	O	O	0	0
21	payload	O	O	0	0
22	and	O	O	0	0
23	a	O	O	0	0
24	lower	O	B-TERM	0	0
25	fuel	O	I-TERM	0	0
26	consumption	O	E-TERM	1	28
27	of	O	O	0	0
28	Cargolux	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	39
29	's	O	O	0	0
30	aircraft	O	O	0	0
31	,	O	O	0	0
32	which	O	O	0	0
33	directly	O	O	0	0
34	translates	O	O	0	0
35	to	O	O	0	0
36	lower	O	B-TERM	0	0
37	aircraft	O	I-TERM	0	0
38	engine	O	I-TERM	0	0
39	emissions	O	E-TERM	0	0
40	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	Cargolux	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
3	is	O	O	0	0
4	proud	O	O	0	0
5	to	O	O	0	0
6	be	O	O	0	0
7	at	O	O	0	0
8	the	O	O	0	0
9	forefront	O	O	0	0
10	of	O	O	0	0
11	developments	O	O	0	0
12	again	O	O	0	0
13	with	O	O	0	0
14	Trinkaus-Solutions	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	27
15	'	O	O	0	0
16	innovative	O	O	0	0
17	products	O	O	0	0
18	"	O	O	0	0
19	,	O	O	0	0
20	says	O	O	0	0
21	Lars	B-PERSON	O	0	0
22	Syberg	E-PERSON	O	0	0
23	,	O	O	0	0
24	Cargolux	B-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
25	EVP	I-ORG	O	0	0
26	Global	I-ORG	O	0	0
27	Logistics	E-ORG	O	0	0
28	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	The	O	O	0	0
3	use	O	O	0	0
4	of	O	O	0	0
5	modern	O	O	0	0
6	,	O	O	0	0
7	environmentally-conscious	O	O	0	0
8	tools	O	O	0	0
9	in	O	O	0	0
10	air	O	O	0	0
11	cargo	O	O	0	0
12	underlines	O	O	0	0
13	our	O	O	0	0
14	standing	O	O	0	0
15	as	O	O	0	0
16	a	O	O	0	0
17	green	O	O	0	0
18	cargo	O	O	0	0
19	carrier	O	O	0	0
20	at	O	O	0	0
21	a	O	O	0	0
22	time	O	O	0	0
23	when	O	O	0	0
24	many	O	O	0	0
25	of	O	O	0	0
26	our	O	O	0	0
27	customers	O	O	0	0
28	put	O	O	0	0
29	more	O	O	0	0
30	emphasis	O	O	0	0
31	on	O	O	0	0
32	working	O	O	0	0
33	with	O	O	0	0
34	a	O	O	0	0
35	partner	O	O	0	0
36	who	O	O	0	0
37	is	O	O	0	0
38	aware	O	O	0	0
39	of	O	O	0	0
40	its	O	O	0	0
41	responsibility	O	O	0	0
42	towards	O	O	0	0
43	the	O	O	0	0
44	world	O	O	0	0
45	we	O	O	0	0
46	live	O	O	0	0
47	in	O	O	0	0
48	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	In	O	O	0	0
3	addition	O	O	0	0
4	,	O	O	0	0
5	Trinkaus-Solutions	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	12
6	provides	O	O	0	0
7	us	O	O	0	0
8	with	O	O	0	0
9	products	O	O	0	0
10	that	O	O	0	0
11	make	O	O	0	0
12	Cargolux	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
13	more	O	O	0	0
14	efficient	O	O	0	0
15	and	O	O	0	0
16	faster	O	O	0	0
17	with	O	O	0	0
18	the	O	O	0	0
19	added	O	O	0	0
20	advantage	O	O	0	0
21	of	O	O	0	0
22	lower	O	O	0	0
23	costs	O	O	0	0
24	.	O	O	0	0

1	It	O	O	0	0
2	's	O	O	0	0
3	an	O	O	0	0
4	all-round	O	O	0	0
5	winner	O	O	0	0
6	for	O	O	0	0
7	us	O	O	0	0
8	.	O	O	0	0
9	"	O	O	0	0

1	Cargolux	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	38
2	estimates	O	O	0	0
3	that	O	O	0	0
4	the	O	O	0	0
5	use	O	O	0	0
6	of	O	O	0	0
7	squAIR-timber	O	O	0	0
8	has	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	potential	O	O	0	0
11	to	O	O	0	0
12	reduce	O	O	0	0
13	its	O	O	0	0
14	fuel	O	O	0	0
15	consumption	O	O	0	0
16	by	O	O	0	0
17	roughly	B-MISC	O	0	0
18	1,200	I-MISC	O	0	0
19	tons	E-MISC	O	1	25
20	per	O	O	0	0
21	year	O	O	0	0
22	,	O	O	0	0
23	lower	O	B-TERM	0	0
24	fuel	O	I-TERM	0	0
25	consumption	O	E-TERM	1	1
26	of	O	O	0	0
27	Cargolux	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
28	's	O	O	0	0
29	aircraft	O	O	0	0
30	,	O	O	0	0
31	which	O	O	0	0
32	directly	O	O	0	0
33	results	O	O	0	0
34	in	O	O	0	0
35	lower	O	B-TERM	0	0
36	aircraft	O	I-TERM	0	0
37	engine	O	I-TERM	0	0
38	emissions	O	E-TERM	0	0
39	.	O	O	0	0

1	In	O	O	0	0
2	addition	O	O	0	0
3	,	O	O	0	0
4	said	O	O	0	0
5	Cargolux	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
6	,	O	O	0	0
7	squAIR-timber	O	O	0	0
8	solution	O	O	0	0
9	"	O	O	0	0
10	enables	O	O	0	0
11	shorter	O	O	0	0
12	build-up	O	O	0	0
13	times	O	O	0	0
14	,	O	O	0	0
15	eliminating	O	O	0	0
16	the	O	O	0	0
17	need	O	O	0	0
18	for	O	O	0	0
19	forklifts	O	O	0	0
20	as	O	O	0	0
21	they	O	O	0	0
22	can	O	O	0	0
23	easily	O	O	0	0
24	be	O	O	0	0
25	handled	O	O	0	0
26	by	O	O	0	0
27	one	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
28	person	O	O	0	0
29	"	O	O	0	0
30	.	O	O	0	0

1	They	O	O	0	0
2	can	O	O	0	0
3	be	O	O	0	0
4	reused	O	O	0	0
5	and	O	O	0	0
6	are	O	O	0	0
7	100	B-MISC	O	0	0
8	%	E-MISC	O	0	0
9	recyclable	O	O	0	0
10	with	O	O	0	0
11	lower	O	O	0	0
12	disposal	O	O	0	0
13	costs	O	O	0	0
14	than	O	O	0	0
15	wooden	O	B-TERM	0	0
16	materials	O	E-TERM	0	0
17	.	O	O	0	0

1	Brussels	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
2	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	1	6
3	to	O	O	0	0
4	invest	O	O	0	0
5	€	B-MISC	O	0	0
6	100m	E-MISC	O	0	0
7	in	O	O	0	0
8	modernising	O	O	0	0
9	logistics	O	S-TERM	0	0
10	buildings	O	O	0	0

1	Brussels	B-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
2	Airport	I-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
3	Company	E-ORG	E-TERM	1	7
4	will	O	O	0	0
5	invest	O	O	0	0
6	€100	B-MISC	O	0	0
7	million	E-MISC	O	1	15
8	over	O	O	0	0
9	three	B-DATE	O	0	0
10	years	E-DATE	O	0	0
11	in	O	O	0	0
12	ultra	O	B-TERM	0	0
13	modern	O	E-TERM	0	0
14	logistics	O	O	0	0
15	buildings	O	S-TERM	1	24
16	to	O	O	0	0
17	strengthen	O	O	0	0
18	its	O	O	0	0
19	position	O	O	0	0
20	as	O	O	0	0
21	a	O	O	0	0
22	vital	O	B-TERM	0	0
23	logistics	O	I-TERM	0	0
24	cluster	O	E-TERM	0	26
25	in	O	O	0	0
26	Belgium	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
27	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	buildings	O	S-TERM	1	5
3	will	O	O	0	0
4	cover	O	O	0	0
5	50,000m2	S-CARDINAL	O	1	11
6	on	O	O	0	0
7	the	O	O	0	0
8	West	O	O	0	0
9	side	O	O	0	0
10	of	O	O	0	0
11	Brucargo	S-ORG	S-TERM	1	17
12	with	O	O	0	0
13	direct	O	O	0	0
14	apron	O	O	0	0
15	connection	O	O	0	0
16	for	O	O	0	0
17	four	S-CARDINAL	O	1	24
18	different	O	O	0	0
19	companies	O	O	0	0
20	,	O	O	0	0
21	with	O	O	0	0
22	Kuehne	B-ORG	O	0	0
23	+	I-ORG	O	0	0
24	Nagel	E-ORG	O	1	28
25	,	O	O	0	0
26	dnata	O	O	0	0
27	and	O	O	0	0
28	WFS	S-ORG	O	0	0
29	among	O	O	0	0
30	the	O	O	0	0
31	companies	O	O	0	0
32	making	O	O	0	0
33	use	O	O	0	0
34	of	O	O	0	0
35	these	O	O	0	0
36	buildings	O	S-TERM	0	0
37	for	O	O	0	0
38	shipping	O	O	0	0
39	,	O	O	0	0
40	packaging	O	O	0	0
41	and	O	O	0	0
42	stocking	O	O	0	0
43	cargo	O	O	0	0
44	.	O	O	0	0

1	The	O	O	0	0
2	new	O	O	0	0
3	infrastructure	O	O	0	0
4	will	O	O	0	0
5	be	O	O	0	0
6	specifically	O	O	0	0
7	suited	O	O	0	0
8	for	O	O	0	0
9	the	O	O	0	0
10	handling	O	O	0	0
11	of	O	O	0	0
12	high-quality	O	O	0	0
13	and	O	O	0	0
14	temperature	O	O	0	0
15	sensitive	O	O	0	0
16	products	O	O	0	0
17	including	O	O	0	0
18	pharmaceuticals	O	O	0	0
19	,	O	O	0	0
20	products	O	O	0	0
21	which	O	O	0	0
22	are	O	O	0	0
23	important	O	O	0	0
24	to	O	O	0	0
25	Brussels	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
26	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	0	28
27	and	O	O	0	0
28	Belgium	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
29	as	O	O	0	0
30	a	O	O	0	0
31	whole	O	O	0	0
32	.	O	O	0	0

1	Brussels	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
2	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	1	8
3	will	O	O	0	0
4	also	O	O	0	0
5	redevelop	O	O	0	0
6	existing	O	O	0	0
7	handling	O	O	0	0
8	buildings	O	S-TERM	0	0
9	that	O	O	0	0
10	have	O	O	0	0
11	direct	O	O	0	0
12	access	O	O	0	0
13	to	O	O	0	0
14	the	O	O	0	0
15	tarmac	O	O	0	0
16	,	O	O	0	0
17	with	O	O	0	0
18	the	O	O	0	0
19	building	O	O	0	0
20	Swissport	S-GPE	O	0	0
21	is	O	O	0	0
22	active	O	O	0	0
23	in	O	O	0	0
24	being	O	O	0	0
25	systematically	O	O	0	0
26	transformed	O	O	0	0
27	into	O	O	0	0
28	a	O	O	0	0
29	modern	O	O	0	0
30	and	O	O	0	0
31	energy	O	O	0	0
32	efficient	O	O	0	0
33	storage	O	O	0	0
34	and	O	O	0	0
35	office	O	O	0	0
36	space	O	O	0	0
37	with	O	O	0	0
38	a	O	O	0	0
39	surface	O	O	0	0
40	area	O	O	0	0
41	of	O	O	0	0
42	30,000m2	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
43	.	O	O	0	0

1	An	O	O	0	0
2	additional	O	O	0	0
3	new	O	O	0	0
4	building	O	O	0	0
5	will	O	O	0	0
6	provide	O	O	0	0
7	a	O	O	0	0
8	secured	O	O	0	0
9	area	O	O	0	0
10	for	O	O	0	0
11	the	O	O	0	0
12	specific	O	O	0	0
13	transport	O	O	0	0
14	of	O	O	0	0
15	extremely	O	O	0	0
16	valuable	O	O	0	0
17	goods	O	O	0	0
18	,	O	O	0	0
19	with	O	O	0	0
20	Brinks	S-ORG	O	0	0
21	moving	O	O	0	0
22	into	O	O	0	0
23	this	O	O	0	0
24	building	O	O	0	0
25	in	O	O	0	0
26	2019	S-DATE	O	0	0
27	.	O	O	0	0

1	Part	O	O	0	0
2	of	O	O	0	0
3	the	O	O	0	0
4	investment	O	O	0	0
5	will	O	O	0	0
6	go	O	O	0	0
7	to	O	O	0	0
8	an	O	O	0	0
9	exclusive	O	O	0	0
10	animal	O	O	0	0
11	border	O	O	0	0
12	inspection	O	O	0	0
13	area	O	O	0	0
14	of	O	O	0	0
15	more	B-CARDINAL	O	0	0
16	than	I-CARDINAL	O	0	0
17	2,500m2	E-CARDINAL	O	0	0
18	,	O	O	0	0
19	fitted	O	O	0	0
20	out	O	O	0	0
21	in	O	O	0	0
22	various	O	O	0	0
23	temperature	O	O	0	0
24	and/or	O	O	0	0
25	light	O	O	0	0
26	areas	O	O	0	0
27	to	O	O	0	0
28	create	O	O	0	0
29	the	O	O	0	0
30	perfect	O	O	0	0
31	environment	O	O	0	0
32	for	O	O	0	0
33	all	O	O	0	0
34	types	O	O	0	0
35	of	O	O	0	0
36	animals	O	O	0	0
37	.	O	O	0	0

1	Brussels	B-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
2	Airport	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
3	head	O	O	0	0
4	of	O	O	0	0
5	cargo	O	O	0	0
6	and	O	O	0	0
7	logistics	O	O	0	0
8	,	O	O	0	0
9	Steven	B-PERSON	O	0	0
10	Polmans	E-PERSON	O	0	0
11	says	O	O	0	0
12	:	O	O	0	0
13	"	O	O	0	0
14	It	O	O	0	0
15	is	O	O	0	0
16	our	O	O	0	0
17	ambition	O	S-TERM	0	0
18	to	O	O	0	0
19	remain	O	O	0	0
20	an	O	O	0	0
21	import	O	O	0	0
22	cargo	O	O	0	0
23	hub	O	O	0	0
24	in	O	O	0	0
25	future	O	O	0	0
26	and	O	O	0	0
27	strengthen	O	O	0	0
28	the	O	O	0	0
29	position	O	O	0	0
30	of	O	O	0	0
31	BRUcargo	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
32	as	O	O	0	0
33	an	O	O	0	0
34	efficient	O	O	0	0
35	and	O	O	0	0
36	important	O	O	0	0
37	logistical	O	O	0	0
38	platform	O	O	0	0
39	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	In	O	O	0	0
3	recent	B-DATE	O	0	0
4	years	E-DATE	O	0	0
5	we	O	O	0	0
6	have	O	O	0	0
7	proven	O	O	0	0
8	our	O	O	0	0
9	commitment	O	O	0	0
10	to	O	O	0	0
11	cargo	O	O	0	0
12	and	O	O	0	0
13	we	O	O	0	0
14	reconfirmed	O	O	0	0
15	this	O	O	0	0
16	in	O	O	0	0
17	our	O	O	0	0
18	Strategic	B-MISC	B-TERM	0	0
19	Vision	I-MISC	E-TERM	0	0
20	2040	E-MISC	O	0	0
21	launched	O	O	0	0
22	last	B-DATE	O	0	0
23	year	E-DATE	O	0	0
24	.	O	O	0	0

1	This	O	O	0	0
2	investment	O	O	0	0
3	is	O	O	0	0
4	another	O	O	0	0
5	step	O	O	0	0
6	in	O	O	0	0
7	realising	O	O	0	0
8	this	O	O	0	0
9	ambition	O	S-TERM	0	0
10	together	O	O	0	0
11	with	O	O	0	0
12	all	O	O	0	0
13	our	O	O	0	0
14	stakeholders	O	O	0	0
15	and	O	O	0	0
16	customers	O	O	0	0
17	.	O	O	0	0
18	"	O	O	0	0

1	Brussels	B-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
2	Airport	I-ORG	B-TERM	0	0
3	Company	E-ORG	E-TERM	0	0
4	chief	O	O	0	0
5	executive	O	O	0	0
6	officer	O	O	0	0
7	,	O	O	0	0
8	Arnaud	B-PERSON	O	0	0
9	Feist	E-PERSON	O	0	0
10	adds	O	O	0	0
11	:	O	O	0	0
12	"	O	O	0	0
13	These	O	O	0	0
14	investments	O	O	0	0
15	are	O	O	0	0
16	of	O	O	0	0
17	huge	O	O	0	0
18	importance	O	O	0	0
19	for	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	logistics	O	O	0	0
22	landscape	O	O	0	0
23	in	O	O	0	0
24	Belgium	S-GPE	S-TERM	0	0
25	and	O	O	0	0
26	are	O	O	0	0
27	entirely	O	O	0	0
28	in	O	O	0	0
29	line	O	O	0	0
30	with	O	O	0	0
31	our	O	O	0	0
32	Strategic	O	B-TERM	0	0
33	Vision	O	E-TERM	0	0
34	for	O	O	0	0
35	2040	S-DATE	O	0	0
36	.	O	O	0	0

1	"	O	O	0	0
2	With	O	O	0	0
3	these	O	O	0	0
4	investments	O	O	0	0
5	,	O	O	0	0
6	Brussels	B-FAC	B-TERM	0	0
7	Airport	E-FAC	E-TERM	0	0
8	will	O	O	0	0
9	remain	O	O	0	0
10	in	O	O	0	0
11	the	O	O	0	0
12	future	O	O	0	0
13	a	O	O	0	0
14	crucial	O	O	0	0
15	hub	O	O	0	0
16	for	O	O	0	0
17	air	O	O	0	0
18	transport	O	O	0	0
19	and	O	O	0	0
20	the	O	O	0	0
21	logistic	O	O	0	0
22	chains	O	O	0	0
23	in	O	O	0	0
24	Europe	S-MISC	O	1	31
25	,	O	O	0	0
26	at	O	O	0	0
27	the	O	O	0	0
28	service	O	O	0	0
29	of	O	O	0	0
30	many	O	O	0	0
31	hundreds	S-CARDINAL	O	0	0
32	of	O	O	0	0
33	companies	O	O	0	0
34	in	O	O	0	0
35	our	O	O	0	0
36	country	O	O	0	0
37	.	O	O	0	0
38	"	O	O	0	0

1	WCS17	O	O	0	0
2	:	O	O	0	0
3	Mercator	S-ORG	S-TERM	0	0
4	promises	O	O	0	0
5	revolution	O	O	0	0
6	in	O	O	0	0
7	airfreight	O	B-TERM	0	0
8	systems	O	E-TERM	0	0

1	Transport	O	B-TERM	0	0
2	software	O	I-TERM	0	0
3	specialist	O	E-TERM	0	0
4	Mercator	S-ORG	O	1	10
5	is	O	O	0	0
6	offering	O	O	0	0
7	an	O	O	0	0
8	Intelligent	B-MISC	B-TERM	0	0
9	Cargo	I-MISC	I-TERM	0	0
10	Ecosystem	E-MISC	E-TERM	1	19
11	,	O	O	0	0
12	which	O	O	0	0
13	it	O	O	0	0
14	describes	O	O	0	0
15	as	O	O	0	0
16	the	O	O	0	0
17	industry	O	O	0	0
18	's	O	O	0	0
19	first	S-MISC	O	0	21
20	open	O	O	0	0
21	API	S-MISC	O	1	26
22	platform	O	O	0	0
23	for	O	O	0	0
24	air	O	B-TERM	0	0
25	cargo	O	I-TERM	0	0
26	management	O	E-TERM	0	29
27	and	O	O	0	0
28	ground	O	B-TERM	0	0
29	handling	O	E-TERM	0	0
30	.	O	O	0	0

1	APIs	O	O	0	0
2	(	O	O	0	0
3	application	O	B-TERM	0	0
4	programming	O	I-TERM	0	0
5	interfaces	O	E-TERM	0	0
6	)	O	O	0	0
7	are	O	O	0	0
8	used	O	O	0	0
9	to	O	O	0	0
10	provide	O	O	0	0
11	the	O	O	0	0
12	'	O	O	0	0
13	building	O	O	0	0
14	blocks	O	O	0	0
15	'	O	O	0	0
16	which	O	O	0	0
17	simplify	O	O	0	0
18	the	O	O	0	0
19	task	O	O	0	0
20	of	O	O	0	0
21	writing	O	O	0	0
22	computer	O	B-TERM	0	0
23	programs	O	E-TERM	0	0
24	.	O	O	0	0
